<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Language>
    <goTo>Go To</goTo>
    <NewPage>New Page</NewPage>
    <DeletePage>Delete Page</DeletePage>
    <Setting>Page Settings</Setting>
    <AddText>Add Text</AddText>
    <AddVideo>Add Video</AddVideo>
    <AddSound>Add Sound</AddSound>
    <AddImage>Add Image</AddImage>
    <Action>Actions</Action>
    <Video>Video</Video>
    <Sound>Sound</Sound>
    <URL>URL</URL>
    <Quiz>Quiz</Quiz>
    <Save>Save</Save>
    <Exit>Exit</Exit>
    <Text>Text</Text>
    <Image>Image</Image>
    <YoutubeURL>Youtube URL</YoutubeURL>
    <Disable>Disabled</Disable>
    <Enabled>Enabled</Enabled>
    <Admin>Admin</Admin>
    <User>User</User>
    <Status>Status</Status>
    <Permession>Permission</Permession>
    <FullName>Full Name</FullName>
    <Mail>E-mail</Mail>
    <Name>Name</Name>
    <title>Title</title>
    <Phone>Phone</Phone>
    <Mobile>Mobile</Mobile>
    <Password>Password</Password>
    <UserName>Username</UserName>
    <EditUser>Edit User</EditUser>
    <IdUser>User ID</IdUser>
    <User>User</User>
    <EMail>E-mail</EMail>
    <Message>Message</Message>
    <Date>Date</Date>
    <Action>Actions</Action>
    <CreateUser>Add User</CreateUser>
    <Modifiedsuccessfully>Updated Successfully</Modifiedsuccessfully>
    <Usernamealreadyexists>Username already exists</Usernamealreadyexists>
    <TheuserwascreatedsuccessfullyThe>Added Successfully</TheuserwascreatedsuccessfullyThe>
    <Areyousure>Are you sure you want to delete this user?</Areyousure>
    <Youwillnotbeabletorecoverthispage>Are you sure you want to delete this page?</Youwillnotbeabletorecoverthispage>
    <Youwillnotbeabletorecoverthisstory>Are you sure you want to delete this story?</Youwillnotbeabletorecoverthisstory>
    <Youwillnotbeabletorecoverthisseries>Are you sure you want to delete this series?
    </Youwillnotbeabletorecoverthisseries>
    <Youwillnotbeabletorecoverthisuser>You will not be able to recover it!</Youwillnotbeabletorecoverthisuser>
    <warning>Warning</warning>
    <Yesdeleteit>Yes</Yesdeleteit>
    <Nocancel>No</Nocancel>
    <Deleted>Deleted</Deleted>
    <userhasbeendeleted>Deleted Successfully</userhasbeendeleted>
    <success>Success</success>
    <Cancelled>Canceled</Cancelled>
    <Youruserissafe>Your user is safe</Youruserissafe>
    <error>Error</error>
    <SignInError>Invalid username or password</SignInError>
    <SignInErrorMsg>Please try again</SignInErrorMsg>
    <No>No.</No>
    <Category>Category</Category>
    <BookTitle>Book Title</BookTitle>
    <teacherBooksT>  teacher Books </teacherBooksT>
    <CreatedDate>Created</CreatedDate>
    <Width>Width</Width>
    <Height>Height</Height>
    <Update>Update</Update>
    <SelectSound>Select Sound</SelectSound>
    <PleaseSelectFile>Please select a file to upload</PleaseSelectFile>
    <Error>Error</Error>
    <CanNotUpload>Cannot upload this file</CanNotUpload>
    <uploadSound>Upload Sound</uploadSound>
    <uploadvideo>Upload Video</uploadvideo>
    <Edit>Edit</Edit>
    <Delete>Delete</Delete>
    <Download>Download</Download>
    <bookhasbeendeleted>Deleted Successfully</bookhasbeendeleted>
    <EditBook>Edit Book Information</EditBook>
    <BookName>Book Title</BookName>
    <BookWidth>Book Width</BookWidth>
    <BookHeight>Book Height</BookHeight>
    <AddBook>Add Book</AddBook>
    <Thebookcreatedsuccessfully>Added Successfully</Thebookcreatedsuccessfully>
    <search>Search</search>
    <Youmustfillinallfields>Empty fields are required</Youmustfillinallfields>
    <uploadImage>Upload Image</uploadImage>
    <UpdateURL>Update URL</UpdateURL>
    <Title>Title</Title>
    <Width>Width</Width>
    <Width>Width</Width>
    <uploadBackground>Upload Background</uploadBackground>
    <categoryname_ar>Arabic Name</categoryname_ar>
    <categoryname_en>English Name</categoryname_en>
    <categorythumbnail>Thumbnail</categorythumbnail>
    <AddCategory>Add Category</AddCategory>
    <categoryhasbeendeleted>Deleted Successfully</categoryhasbeendeleted>
    <EditCategory>Edit Category</EditCategory>
    <arabicname>Arabic Name</arabicname>
    <englishname>English Name</englishname>
    <Thecategorycreatedsuccessfully>Added Successfully</Thecategorycreatedsuccessfully>
    <Categorynamealreadyexists>Category name already exists</Categorynamealreadyexists>
    <Pages>Pages</Pages>
    <TitlePage>Page Title</TitlePage>
    <SubTitle>Subtitle</SubTitle>
    <BackgroundPage>Background</BackgroundPage>
    <AddPage>Add Page</AddPage>
    <AreYouSure>Are you sure you want to delete this page?</AreYouSure>
    <DoYouWantDeletePage></DoYouWantDeletePage>
    <YesDeletePage>Yes</YesDeletePage>
    <Publish>Publish</Publish>
    <BooksDesc1>Dar Al Manhal makes your kid</BooksDesc1>
    <Categories>Categories</Categories>
    <SignOut>Sign Out</SignOut>
    <Users>Users</Users>
    <Login>Sign In</Login>
    <Login1>Login</Login1>
    <View>View</View>
    <Index>Index</Index>
    <Addindex>Add Index</Addindex>
    <bookPublished>Published Successfully</bookPublished>
    <uploadIcon>Upload Icon</uploadIcon>
    <BookInfo>Book Information</BookInfo>    <!--New By Hussam 25-1-2016 -->
    <PleaseInsertBookName>Please enter book title</PleaseInsertBookName>
    <PleaseInsertBookWidth>Please enter book width</PleaseInsertBookWidth>
    <InvalidBookWidth>Invalid book width</InvalidBookWidth>
    <PleaseInsertBookHeight>Please enter book height</PleaseInsertBookHeight>
    <InvalidBookHeight>Invalid book height</InvalidBookHeight>
    <PleaseInsertUsername>Please enter your username</PleaseInsertUsername>
    <PleaseInsertPassword>Please enter password</PleaseInsertPassword>
    <InvalidEmailAddress>Invalid e-mail address</InvalidEmailAddress>
    <PleaseInsertFullName>Please enter your full name</PleaseInsertFullName>
    <QuizTitle>Quiz Title</QuizTitle>
    <Preview>Preview</Preview>
    <quistions>Questions</quistions>
    <QuizType>Quiz Type</QuizType>
    <ViewQuiz>Preview</ViewQuiz>
    <AddQuiz>Add Quiz</AddQuiz>
    <Yourquistionissafe>Your question is safe</Yourquistionissafe>
    <Correct>Correct</Correct>
    <PLaySound>Play Sound</PLaySound>
    <PLayVidio>Play Video</PLayVidio>
    <Correctanswer>correct Answer</Correctanswer>
    <WrongAnswer>Wrong Answer</WrongAnswer>
    <Introduction>Introduction</Introduction>
    <Introduction>Introduction</Introduction>
    <PassingRate>Pass Rate</PassingRate>
    <QuizResult>Quiz Result</QuizResult>
    <QuizPass>Quiz Pass</QuizPass>
    <QuizFailed>Quiz Failed</QuizFailed>
    <QuizFeedback>Quiz Feedback</QuizFeedback>
    <Passed>Passed</Passed>
    <Failed>Failed</Failed>
    <Age>Age</Age>    <!--new 26-1-2016-->
    <EditQuiz>Quiz Information</EditQuiz>
    <duplicate>Duplicate</duplicate>
    <Font>Page Font</Font>
    <Correct>Correct</Correct>
    <CorrectFeedBack>Correct Answer Feedback</CorrectFeedBack>
    <InCorrect>Incorrect</InCorrect>
    <InCorrectFeedBack>Incorrect Answer Feedback</InCorrectFeedBack>
    <Points>Points</Points>
    <AddAnswer>Add Answer</AddAnswer>
    <Copy>Copy</Copy>
    <TraceQuiz>Trace and Color</TraceQuiz>
    <Submit>Submit</Submit>
    <Send>Send</Send>
    <Reset>Reset</Reset>
    <TotalQuestion>Total Questions</TotalQuestion>
    <fullscore>Full score</fullscore>
    <PassingRate>Pass Rate</PassingRate>
    <passingscore>Passing Score</passingscore>
    <YourScore>Your Score</YourScore>
    <elapsed>Elapsed</elapsed>
    <NumberBox>Number Box</NumberBox>
    <uploadNegative>Upload Negative</uploadNegative>
    <Circle>ضع دائرة</Circle>
    <Add>Add</Add>
    <page>Yqhtme</page>
    <widget>Widget</widget>
    <Trace>Trace</Trace>
    <AnimationImage>Animation Image</AnimationImage>
    <Language>Language</Language>
    <Arabic>Arabic</Arabic>
    <English>English</English>
    <France>French</France>
    <BookCover>Book Cover</BookCover>
    <UnexpectedError>An unexpected error occurred</UnexpectedError>
    <AddQuestion>Add Question</AddQuestion>
    <AreyousureDeleteQuestion>Are you sure you want delete this question?</AreyousureDeleteQuestion>
    <DeleteQuestion>Delete Question</DeleteQuestion>
    <AreyousureDeleteQuiz>Are you sure you want delete this quiz?</AreyousureDeleteQuiz>
    <QuizInformation>Quiz Information</QuizInformation>
    <ChangePassword>Change Password</ChangePassword>
    <Enteryourpasswordbelow>Enter your new password</Enteryourpasswordbelow>
    <OldPassword>Current Password</OldPassword>
    <NewPassword>New Password</NewPassword>
    <RetypeNewPassword>Confirm Password</RetypeNewPassword>
    <gobacktoLogin>Back</gobacktoLogin>
    <processComplete>Process Completed</processComplete>
    <passwordChanged>Updated Successfully</passwordChanged>
    <incorrectPassword>Incorrect password</incorrectPassword>
    <oldpasswordincorrect>Current password is incorrect</oldpasswordincorrect>
    <EmptyPassword>Empty Field</EmptyPassword>
    <NewPasswordCannotEmpty>New password cannot be empty</NewPasswordCannotEmpty>
    <PasswordNotMatch>Password does not match the confirm password</PasswordNotMatch>.    <newPasswordNotMatch>Password
    does not match the confirm password
</newPasswordNotMatch>
    <WelcomeLogin>Please enter username and password. You can also sign in with Facebook, Google+ or Twitter.
    </WelcomeLogin>
    <Facebook>Facebook</Facebook>
    <Google>Google+</Google>
    <Twitter>Twitter</Twitter>
    <Or>Or</Or>
    <Keepmesignin>Remember Me</Keepmesignin>
    <ForgetMyPass>Forgot your password?</ForgetMyPass>
    <loginFaild>Sign In Error</loginFaild>
    <Incorrectuserorpass>Invalid username or password</Incorrectuserorpass>
    <logOut>Sign Out</logOut>
    <Createnewaccount>Create a new account</Createnewaccount>
    <EmailAddress>E-mail</EmailAddress>
    <Cpassword>Confirm Password</Cpassword>
    <SignUp>Sign Up</SignUp>
    <Bycreatingaccountyouagree>By clicking on “Sign Up”, you agree and consent to the</Bycreatingaccountyouagree>
    <TermsofUse>Terms and Conditions</TermsofUse>
    <PasswordEmpty>Sign Up Error</PasswordEmpty>
    <CannotPasswordEmpty>Password cannot be empty</CannotPasswordEmpty>
    <EmailExist>E-mail already exists</EmailExist>
    <YourEmailExist>E-mail already exists</YourEmailExist>
    <ErrorNum>Error Number :</ErrorNum>
    <WrongEmail>Error</WrongEmail>
    <WrongEmailMsg>Invalid e-mail address</WrongEmailMsg>
    <NewBooks>Recent Books</NewBooks>
    <BestSeller>Best Seller</BestSeller>
    <TopRated>Top Rated</TopRated>
    <TopFavorite>Top Favorite</TopFavorite>
    <Popular>Most Viewed</Popular>
    <NewStories>Recent Stories</NewStories>
    <storyIntro1>Short stories are adventurous and interesting ways to teach your children about good morals and right
        conduct. As children, they are at their formative years; that’s why they need to be educated with good values to
        make them good fit for society and family.
    </storyIntro1>
    <storyIntro2>Therefore we let your children go through a host of fascinating stories and fill their bookshelf with
        endless possibilities of interesting stories.
    </storyIntro2>
    <storyIntro3>With Us, Children Read Stories They'll Always Remember!</storyIntro3>
    <Benefits>Products</Benefits>
    <BenefitSsubTitle>Professional book publishing and services</BenefitSsubTitle>
    <benifitsIntro>We offer a comprehensive range of best books and E-learning technologies; so we can be an effective
        element in your child learning success.
    </benifitsIntro>
    <signin>Sign In</signin>
    <More>More...</More>
    <BooksStories>Books and Stories</BooksStories>
    <BooksStoriesDesc>
        <![CDATA[We at <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> make your child a reader in childhood, through producing cultural programs, educational contents, and high level projects that are enriching his knowledge, and expanding his horizon.        <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> aims to help you develop your child by offering the widest collection of kindergarten and school books, which are created by experts to help learners achieve specific academic or occupational goals. All you need is to browse our library of books to find an engaging book for your child.        Reading is a world of pleasure and knowledge enrichment, therefore; we offer a comprehensive and successful range of stories that are specialized in children’s literature in different languages (Arabic, English and even French). Our stories develop the child's love for daily reading habit and direct him to acquire the correct habits and values.        We also provide stories packages which contain various picked short stories from our great editions. These packages are divided into levels according to the age group.       Whether you’re looking for a book to share with your youngest child or something to keep your ten year old motivated, we’re here to help.        ]]></BooksStoriesDesc>
    <EBooksEStories>E-Books and E-Stories</EBooksEStories>
    <EBooksEStoriesDesc>
        <![CDATA[Are you looking for a great reading experience? Do you want to build your online library? Simply, you are in the right place!        We are going strong in our mission to provide a valuable service to help you make the best use of studying time, therefore; <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> becomes a central place to discover E-books. It provides one of the best reading tools, so reading stories or studying will be more efficient.        You can browse any of our editions right on your smart phone or tablet, so your favorite books or stories can be read on computers or other electronic devices. With us reading is a pleasure, and learning becomes easier!        In addition to, we provide a simple way to create electronic books, using our quick and easy online book creator. No programming knowledge is required; we offer powerful tools that could help you make your own electronic book without the need to write a single code, you will already know how to create a book.        <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> provides a good collection of electronic stories for the young minds using the great combination of graphics, narration, sound effects and background music, children are attracted to. When a story is being read or narrated by a person, there is always the risk of the child losing interest at some point. With our great electronic stories it is a totally different scenario. Children get glued to it and will surely watch it to the end.          ]]></EBooksEStoriesDesc>
    <EducationalGames>Games and Exercises</EducationalGames>
    <EducationalGamesDesc>
        <![CDATA[What sounds more fun: homework or games? Want educational games that help build skills and educate students? You are in the right place at the right time!        Our passion is helping teachers and students to find fun and meaningful ways to integrate technology with learning. We are working hardly to provide the suitable environment for that!        Educational games are great tools for building foundation to learn and develop skills that today’s school curriculum require. We offer amazing online learning games for children that are fun and teach important skills for preschool, elementary school and even secondary school.        Try our educational games and combine lesson time with playtime. These colorful, animated games make it easy and fun to practice fundamental math, reading skills, language, science, and more at home or on the go. Choose from educational games that use colorful animations and music to bring important lessons to life and aid memory. No matter where you are or what device you are on; just enjoy our online games which are available for Android devices, iPhone, mobile, tablets, iPad and PC.        We believe that games have the potential to help children learn in a way that's not possible with other, therefore; we offer a brilliant virtual world for students, to study without getting bored and allow them to learn wherever and whenever they want.        We want you to love learning - no more boring study sessions, you should play games instead!        ]]></EducationalGamesDesc>
    <EducationalGamesDesc1>Which is more fun: homework or educational games?</EducationalGamesDesc1>
    <EducationalTools>Educational Tools</EducationalTools>
    <EducationalToolsDesc1>In Dar Al Manhal, we expand our circle constantly</EducationalToolsDesc1>
    <EducationalToolsDesc>
        <![CDATA[We at <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> are constantly expanding our products range to reflect the needs of today's education process.        We help you discover and develop your children's abilities in modern and innovative ways by offering a wide range of great educational tools to improve children's mental and linguistic skills. Our educational tools are represented as eye catching flash cards, powerful audio versions, and rich educational posters.        Teaching and learning have never been more efficient or easier than with our educational flash cards. <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> is dedicated to bring the best selection of unique educational flash cards in both Arabic and English.        Audio versions issued by <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> are considered as a special achievement which helps to teach children listening skills that come before reading and writing in learning skills. It also includes beautiful stories, wonderful melodic songs, performed by group of children with beautiful voices, which give them an educational dimension, and contribute to improve reading and pronunciation.        In addition to, we provide amazing educational classroom posters to create a unique teaching environment filled with visual cues for the students.        A series of curriculum multimedia CDs in Arabic and English are also available. The series is professionally designed to easily use by children. Our content is developed with the aid of experts who understand the realities of classroom teaching, so we can create visually stimulating products that add real value to the classroom.    ]]>    </EducationalToolsDesc>
    <Application>Applications</Application>
    <ApplicationDesc>
        <![CDATA[There is no doubt that the technical development plays a huge role in our daily lives, especially in developing skills and capacities of our children.        But how can our children take the whole benefit of this great technical development in an easy and fun way? How it helps them to develop their abilities and acquire new skills? That’s why we have the challenge to turn our thoughts and ideas into real applications.        Our vision is to be the source for childhood learning on the internet available from anywhere. We are dedicating to fun and online learning on the internet for children from all ages through offering the best interactive stories applications and attractive games applications.        Building you the best educational apps possible is critical and so is the process it takes to get there. That’s where we come in. We are driven by a simple goal; deliver high quality software, and ensure it runs smoothly, strategically, and predictably. Our passion and creativity come together to bring out awesome stories and games applications to life, so we serve the educational process and the development of children's skills, the result is, learn and fun with awesome interactive content and graphics.        Our highly experienced team transforms apps into experiences for a wide range of connected devices you hold in your hand, wear on your wrist, and use in your home and car weather they are iOS, Android or web.        ]]>    </ApplicationDesc>
    <Furniture>Children’s Furniture</Furniture>
    <FurnitureDesc1>Both playing environment and learning environment</FurnitureDesc1>
    <FurnitureDesc>
        <![CDATA[<b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> seeks to be pioneer in all what is concerning with children, and giving them the best. Being the exclusive agent for Edu Fun - an international brand specialized in preschools supplies and furniture - is our way to reach our goal.        The environment children play and learn in, have a great effect on them. Therefore we believe in the importance of providing practical, suitable and comfortable designs to fulfill the demands of this critical stage.        We provide a complete solution for preschool education and homes, so you can find a full range of furniture which suits the requirements of children in their early years. Modular designs, elegance, and accurate manufacturing all come together to set up unique configurations to suit children needs. The colorful, attractive and durable designs encourage good posture and ensure years of safe and enjoyable use, this means that everything will last for years and years and can be even passed on from one generation to the next. All this we offer at affordable and compatible prices.        Edu Fun provides us with full range of products starting with chairs, tables, storage units and reading corners passing through play corners and role play furniture ending with play screens, boards and carpets.        If you have any questions about any item, there will always be someone ready and willing to get you the assistance you need. Your complete satisfaction is always our number one priority.    ]]>    </FurnitureDesc>
    <CrossPlatform>Cross Platform</CrossPlatform>
    <CrossPlatformDesc>For many years, all you needed was a desktop, but as technology evolved; smart phones began to
        make an appearance, along with tablets. Customers increasingly are viewing websites and products from a number
        of mobile devices (iOS, Android) and on various browsers (Google Chrome, Internet Explorer, and Mozilla
        Firefox); it's an important goal to achieve. This goal is possible through "responsive web design," meaning web
        design for multiple devices. which enables customers to find us no matter where they are or what device they are
        on. With our responsive designs for website, editors, apps, E-books… etc, you are going to view any of our
        products at any screen size and look absolutely great on any device, whether it's an Android device, an iPad or
        a desktop computer. Our products are really professional and of high standard made to run on various platforms
        and operating systems. Our highly qualified team use minimum number of programming codes necessary to run the
        work and reach to the perfection. We have taken up the challenge of responsive design and have built our
        software to meet that demand.
    </CrossPlatformDesc>
    <ReadingOnline>Reading Online</ReadingOnline>
    <ReadingOnlineDesc>
        <![CDATA[One of the most important ways we can help children succeed in life is instilling in them the love of reading. With more and more content going digital, you don’t have to go to bookstore to preview the book before buying it to your child; with us any book will be available for you for online reading.        If you ever wanted a reliable source for useful and valuable online content, look no further, our extensive library has everything you need!        <b>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers</b> offers an online library with huge number of digitized books, which make our website a very good place for finding good books specializes in children’s literature. We put over thousands books and stories at your fingertips and let your children find a world of online reading and storytelling right from smart phone or tablet.        Our website is categorized very well and can browse through very easily to find your child favorite story or book -including new releases-.        Reading is a passion! Our website is the right place for every reader.        ]]>    </ReadingOnlineDesc>
    <EShop>E-Shop</EShop>
    <EShopDesc>
        <![CDATA[In an online store it is very difficult to get the same quality of service that in a physical retailer, but we at <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> Publishers have managed to bring you the shopping experience to the highest level.        <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> provides the largest online books store, offering thousands of titles in different languages (Arabic, English and even French), and selling a huge variety of products online! Our offered products are ranging from books, stories, E-books, E-stories, interactive books, interactive stories, apps, educational games, educational tools, children’s furniture and much more.        Our strategic thinking is not limited to be just another sales channel. It goes beyond, always thinking about how to sell more and better.        The transformation of our E-shopping experience is not just about bringing the convenience and speed of the online shopping into the store. The real goal is to find ways to help consumers reduce the scope of their search on other bookstores and simplify their shopping on us.        Because your trust and satisfaction is our first priority, we ensure that all transactions are conducted on Dar Al-Manhal platform. Whether a buyer uses a credit card, PayPal or other form of payments, we handle everything, and ensure the security of your personal details. Besides, we offer very save and fast shipping to your products.        We look forward to a future filled with many new opportunities, new innovations, and, of course, new books!    ]]></EShopDesc>
    <ReadMore>Read More</ReadMore>
    <OurEvent>Our Events</OurEvent>
    <firstday>24</firstday>
    <firstMonth>March</firstMonth>
    <firstTitle>Bahrain International Book Fair</firstTitle>
    <firstDesc>The 17th Bahrain International Book Fair is a biennial event that showcases publishers and booksellers in
        all subject areas under one roof.
    </firstDesc>
    <secoundday>27</secoundday>
    <secoundMonth>April</secoundMonth>
    <secoundTitle>Abu Dhabi International Book Fair</secoundTitle>
    <secoundDesc>Abu Dhabi International Book Fair (ADIBF), in its 26th edition is one of the most prominent cultural
        events specializing in books, reading and knowledge.
    </secoundDesc>
    <thirdday>18</thirdday>
    <thirdMonth>July</thirdMonth>
    <thirdTitle>Arabic Book Fair in Istanbul</thirdTitle>
    <thirdDesc>Arabic Book Fair in Istanbul aims to provide Arab Books to Arabs and Turkish-speaking Arabic-, academics
        and Arab tourists.
    </thirdDesc>
    <ViewMoreNews>View More News</ViewMoreNews>
    <newsyear>2016</newsyear>
    <OurEventParagraph>Be the first to get the latest company events and other stuff.</OurEventParagraph>
    <applicationParagraph>We believe that apps should not only be eye catching but actually provide a great experience
        that users will remember. Therefore we provide a world of education, creativity and fun with our great cross
        platform apps. So what you are waiting for?
    </applicationParagraph>
    <MOREALLPRODUCTS>All Editors</MOREALLPRODUCTS>
    <OurPartners>Our Partners</OurPartners>
    <OurPartnersParagraph>
        <![CDATA[At <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> we are always looking for the added value in potential partnerships with like –minded organizations with a commitment to quality and making a positive difference to the lives of others. We have built strong partner relationships with major companies in order to bring the right solution to the right place at the right time for the customers.]]>    </OurPartnersParagraph>
    <ViewAll>View All</ViewAll>
    <Editors>Editors</Editors>
    <editors>editors</editors>
    <EditorsParagraph>
        <![CDATA[Whether you're a teacher who wants to enrich the educational process or a writer who is looking for an efficient solution to create and publish his works, we've got you covered. <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> provides professional editors that meet all users' needs and keep customers happy, through hundreds of rich features and options.]]>    </EditorsParagraph>
    <Addingcontent>Adding content</Addingcontent>
    <isfastandeasy>is fast and easy</isfastandeasy>
    <Draganddrop>Drag and drop</Draganddrop>
    <Optimizedfor>Optimized for</Optimizedfor>
    <everyplatform>every platform</everyplatform>
    <FeaturesTitle>With us … achieve your goal quickly and flexibly</FeaturesTitle>
    <FeaturesParagraph>
        <![CDATA[<B>Dar Al-Manhal</B> mission is to continuously innovate in publishing, leading the dynamic publishing market, to let children find electronic books and interactive books easily, and helping them to enjoy electronic stories and interactive stories.]]></FeaturesParagraph>
    <Whatweoffer>Services</Whatweoffer>
    <WhatweofferParagraph1>
        <![CDATA[Do you have a personal interest in children’s literature? Are you an author who is looking for a website to quickly and effortlessly launch your book? With <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b>, you've got the solution!]]>    </WhatweofferParagraph1>
    <WhatweofferParagraph2>
        <![CDATA[<b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> provides distinctive solutions which are powerful, helpful and useful for all, such as authors, publishers, schools, and even families.]]>    </WhatweofferParagraph2>
    <WhatweofferParagraph3>
        <![CDATA[<b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> where are more opportunities and a wider array of options than ever before!]]>    </WhatweofferParagraph3>
    <WhatweofferParagraph4>Our services include:</WhatweofferParagraph4>
    <WhatweofferParagraph5>Dar Al-Manhal where are more opportunities and a wider array of options than ever before!
    </WhatweofferParagraph5>
    <Schools>Schools</Schools>
    <Families>Parents</Families>
    <Publishers>Publishers</Publishers>
    <Authors>Authors</Authors>
    <IpadandMobileApps>Ipad and Mobile App</IpadandMobileApps>
    <MakeMoney>Make Money Online</MakeMoney>
    <MakeMoneyTitle1>Looking to make money online?</MakeMoneyTitle1>
    <MakeMoneyTitle2>Looking for ways to earn extra income on the internet but have no clue on how to start?
    </MakeMoneyTitle2>
    <MakeMoneyParagraph1>Internet is so important nowadays that it becomes a part of your daily routine. You can read
        the newspaper, check your email, update your Facebook status, shop online, skype with friends, search on Google
        and so on. You can almost do anything through the internet. But did you know you can also make money online? If
        you didn’t, then congratulations! This is a great opportunity for you.
    </MakeMoneyParagraph1>
    <Slider1Text1>With Us</Slider1Text1>
    <Slider1Text2>There Are E-Books</Slider1Text2>
    <Slider1Text3>For Everyone !</Slider1Text3>
    <Slider2Text1>The Best</Slider2Text1>
    <Slider2Text2>Online Shopping</Slider2Text2>
    <Slider2Text3>Experience</Slider2Text3>
    <Slider4Text1><![CDATA[Build <b>awesome</b>]]></Slider4Text1>
    <Slider4Text2><![CDATA[interactive stories]]></Slider4Text2>
    <Slider3Text1>We Are</Slider3Text1>
    <Slider3Text2>Leaders in the Field</Slider3Text2>
    <Slider3Text3>of Children's Literature</Slider3Text3>
    <Slider5Text1>Best</Slider5Text1>
    <Slider5Text2>Educational Apps</Slider5Text2>
    <Slider6Text1>Fun</Slider6Text1>
    <Slider6Text2>Easy,</Slider6Text2>
    <Slider6Text3>and Fast</Slider6Text3>
    <Slider6Text4>Way to Learn</Slider6Text4>
    <bookEditor>Books Editor</bookEditor>
    <bookEditorDesc>A perfect tool that provides the possibility to create E-books</bookEditorDesc>
    <storyEditor>Illustrated Stories Editor</storyEditor>
    <storyEditorDesc>Create graphic stories in professional and attractive way</storyEditorDesc>
    <QuizEditor>Quiz Creator</QuizEditor>
    <QuizEditorDesc>Build your own highly customized quizzes without any programming</QuizEditorDesc>
    <InteractiveStoriesEditor>Interactive Stories Editor</InteractiveStoriesEditor>
    <InteractiveStoriesEditorDesc>A great tool that is specialized with creating interactive graphic stories
    </InteractiveStoriesEditorDesc>
    <ebook>E-Books</ebook>
    <InteractiveBooks>Interactive Books</InteractiveBooks>
    <EnrichmentBooksDesc1>Dar Al Manhal seeks to provide interactive books for kids</EnrichmentBooksDesc1>
    <estories>Electronic Stories</estories>
    <estoriesDesc1>What is the best than using technology in education</estoriesDesc1>
    <storiesDesc1>Reading is a world of fun and knowledge enriching</storiesDesc1>
    <InteractiveStories>Interactive Stories</InteractiveStories>
    <InteractiveStoriesDesc1>Children's stories are their window for the outside</InteractiveStoriesDesc1>
    <forAuthors>Authors</forAuthors>
    <forAuthorsDesc>We provide distinctive solution for authors to create their books</forAuthorsDesc>
    <forSchools>Schools</forSchools>
    <forSchoolsDesc>We enrich the educational process for all students at all levels</forSchoolsDesc>
    <forParents>Parents</forParents>
    <forParentsDesc>We introduce a wide variety of stories and books that suit children of any age</forParentsDesc>
    <forStudents>Publishers</forStudents>
    <forStudentsDesc>We provide the most appropriate place to publish your work online</forStudentsDesc>
    <ebooks>Electronic Books</ebooks>
    <ebooksDesc1>Dar al Manhal believes in the importance</ebooksDesc1>
    <Thumb>Thumb</Thumb>
    <Editaccount>Edit Profile</Editaccount>
    <SignOut>Sign Out</SignOut>
    <En>English</En>
    <Ar>عربي</Ar>
    <DarAlmanhal>Dar Al-Manhal</DarAlmanhal>
    <BookType>Book Type</BookType>
    <PaperBook>Paper Book</PaperBook>
    <EnrichmentBook>Interactive Book</EnrichmentBook>
    <BookDescriptionAr>Arabic Desc.</BookDescriptionAr>
    <BookDescriptionEn>English Desc.</BookDescriptionEn>
    <Home>Home</Home>
    <Books>Books</Books>
    <Stories>Stories</Stories>
    <EStories>E-Stories</EStories>
    <Products>Products</Products>
    <Services>Services</Services>
    <Galleries>Gallery</Galleries>
    <AboutUs>About Us</AboutUs>
    <FINDUS>Find Us</FINDUS>
    <GoogleMaps>Google Maps</GoogleMaps>
    <CALLUS>Call Us</CALLUS>
    <EMAILUS>E-mail Us</EMAILUS>
    <DarAlManhalPublishers>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers</DarAlManhalPublishers>
    <DarAlManhalPublishersParagraph>Dar Al-Manhal is one of the largest Arab publishing houses which are specialized in
        the field of children's literature. It was established in 1990 and since that it is a pioneer in publishing
        books and educational programs.
    </DarAlManhalPublishersParagraph>
    <MainOffice>Main Office:</MainOffice>
    <MainOfficep1>Areej Commercial Complex, near Al-Assaf traffic lights, Wasfi al-tal Str.</MainOfficep1>
    <Showroom>Showroom:</Showroom>
    <Showroomp1>Al-Daddu Complex, King Al Hussein Str. Al- Abdali - Amman - Jordan</Showroomp1>
    <USEFULLINKS>Useful Links</USEFULLINKS>
    <Homepage>Home</Homepage>
    <SupportCenter>Support Center</SupportCenter>
    <ContectUs>Contact Us</ContectUs>
    <FAQs>FaQs</FAQs>
    <Sitemap>Sitemap</Sitemap>
    <News>News</News>
    <Events>Events</Events>
    <BookStore>Store</BookStore>
    <Apps>Apps</Apps>
    <FOLLOWUS>Follow Us</FOLLOWUS>
    <Copyrite>All Rights Reserved for Dar Al-Manhal Publishers</Copyrite>
    <NEWSLETTER>Newsletter</NEWSLETTER>
    <Enteryouremailaddress>Enter your e-mail</Enteryouremailaddress>
    <privacyPolicy>Privacy Policy</privacyPolicy>
    <TermsConditions>Terms and Conditions</TermsConditions>
    <WelcometoDarAlManhalPlatform>Welcome to Dar Al-Manhal Platform</WelcometoDarAlManhalPlatform>
    <WelcometoDarAlManhalP1>Enter signing in details to sign in, or register with our website.</WelcometoDarAlManhalP1>
    <WelcometoDarAlManhalP2>Our website gives you the ability to browse more books and stories, bookmark your favorite
        editions, get our professional apps, and start creating your own publishing work with us and more …
    </WelcometoDarAlManhalP2>
    <Donthaveanaccount>Don't have an account?</Donthaveanaccount>
    <Alreadyhaveanaccount>Already have an account?</Alreadyhaveanaccount>
    <SigninhereA>Sign in here</SigninhereA>
    <ResetYourPassword>Reset Your Password</ResetYourPassword>
    <resetyourpasswordtitle>Enter your email and we'll send you a link to reset your password</resetyourpasswordtitle>
    <gobacktoLoginpage>Back</gobacktoLoginpage>
    <Address>Address:</Address>
    <TechnicalSupport>Technical Support:</TechnicalSupport>
    <Marketingdepartment>Marketing Department:</Marketingdepartment>
    <manage>Admin:</manage>
    <ContactInfo>Contact Information</ContactInfo>
    <Contactform>Contact Form</Contactform>
    <PleaseenteryourEmail>Please enter your e-mail</PleaseenteryourEmail>
    <Pleaseenteryourname>Please enter your name</Pleaseenteryourname>
    <InvalidEmailaddress>Invalid e-mail address</InvalidEmailaddress>
    <Pleaseenterphone>Please enter mobile number</Pleaseenterphone>
    <PleaseenterSubject>Please enter subject</PleaseenterSubject>
    <Pleaseentermessage>Please enter message</Pleaseentermessage>
    <msgsent>Sent Successfully</msgsent>
    <Subject>Subject</Subject>
    <All>All Categories</All>
    <All1>All Companies</All1>
    <AllSeries>All Series</AllSeries>
    <SearchYourItem>Search</SearchYourItem>
    <FAQ>FAQs</FAQ>
    <Features>Features</Features>
    <EditProfile>Edit Profile</EditProfile>
    <Purchased>Purchased</Purchased>
    <Profits>Profits</Profits>
    <offers>Offers</offers>
    <MakeMony>Make Money Online</MakeMony>
    <Series>Series</Series>
    <CheckOut>Check Out</CheckOut>
    <Quantity>Quantity</Quantity>
    <ItemsAdded>Item(s) added:</ItemsAdded>
    <Type>Type</Type>
    <Price>Price</Price>
    <TotalPrice>Total Price</TotalPrice>
    <GetInTouch>Get in Touch</GetInTouch>
    <Idea>Idea</Idea>
    <Sugestion>Suggestion</Sugestion>
    <Note>Note</Note>
    <Others>Others</Others>
    <Feedback>Feedback</Feedback>
    <Favorites>Favorites</Favorites>
    <subTotal>Subtotal</subTotal>
    <Tax>Tax</Tax>
    <Shipping>Shipping</Shipping>
    <changepass>Change Password</changepass>
    <feedbackSent>Feedback has been sent successfully, thank you.</feedbackSent>
    <LoginName>Username</LoginName>
    <FirstName>First Name</FirstName>
    <LastName>Last Name</LastName>
    <FullName>Full Name</FullName>
    <Male>Male</Male>
    <Female>Female</Female>
    <AddressA>Address</AddressA>
    <bodate>Birth of Date</bodate>
    <ProfileUpdated>Updated Successfully</ProfileUpdated>
    <passwordUpdated>Updated Successfully</passwordUpdated>
    <ForgetSuccess>Please follow instructions sent to your email address to reset your password</ForgetSuccess>
    <ScreenShoots>Screenshots</ScreenShoots>
    <Author>Author</Author>
    <ISBN>ISBN</ISBN>
    <CoverType>Cover Type</CoverType>
    <PaperCover>Paper Cover</PaperCover>
    <BookWeight>Book Weight</BookWeight>
    <iteminyourcart>item(s) in your cart</iteminyourcart>
    <Enrichment>Interactive</Enrichment>
    <Electronic>Electronic</Electronic>
    <Paper>Paper</Paper>
    <Manhal>Manhal</Manhal>
    <DHL>DHL</DHL>
    <Aramex>Aramex</Aramex>
    <privacyPolicy1>
        <![CDATA[<b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> Publishers respects your privacy and values the relationship we have with you. This privacy policy describes the types of information we may collect from you, how we use the information, with whom we share it, and the choices available to you regarding our use of the information. We also describe the measures we take to protect the security of the information and how users of this website and our customers can contact us about our privacy practices.]]>
        This privacy policy applies to personal and other information that may be collected when you interact with Dar
        Al-Manhal website.
    </privacyPolicy1>
    <Whatinformationwecollectaboutyou>What information we collect about you</Whatinformationwecollectaboutyou>
    <privacyPolicy2>
        <![CDATA[We collect two basic types of information from you in conjunction with your use of our website: (1) Personally Identifiable Information (PII), which is any information that individually identifies you (e.g., your name, email address, telephone number, postal address, credit card information) and (2) Non-Personally Identifiable Information (NPII), which is information that does not personally identify you but may include information about your interests, demographics (e.g., age, gender, 5-digit zip code) and use of the website.]]> </privacyPolicy2>
    <privacyPolicy3>
        <![CDATA[We collect, retain and use only the information about our customers that is required in registration page, or other pages in <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b>. We are committed to maintaining the privacy and security of your information. This information is limited to your email address, username, country, phone number, credit card and payment information. All these information are important to activate our service and clients. Your password is stored securely; all transmitted credit card information is also handled securely. We do not share this data unless with competent governmental authorities in the case of a binding court order, otherwise, all the data is kept in the strictest confidence.]]> </privacyPolicy3>
    <privacyPolicy4>The email in the client account is the basic identity for him, in the case of client account
        password changes, the change will be confirmed via email for his account only.
    </privacyPolicy4>
    <privacyPolicy5>If authorized by you, we may also access profile and other information from services like Facebook,
        Google or Twitter.
    </privacyPolicy5>
    <Sharingwiththirdparties>Sharing with third parties</Sharingwiththirdparties>
    <privacyPolicy6>All personally identifiable data provided by individuals is maintained in confidence by Dar
        Al-Manhal. There are instances, however, in which personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable
        information is shared with third parties, as described below.
    </privacyPolicy6>
    <privacyPolic7>With respect to personally identifiable information provided to Dar Al-Manhal, we may, from time to
        time, provide information to certain third-party for efficiency purposes in providing administrative services
        such as billing, delivery and pay-outs, or for other related services. Third parties are required to keep
        confidential the information received, and may not use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services
        they perform on our behalf.
    </privacyPolic7>
    <Thirdpartysites>Third party sites</Thirdpartysites>
    <privacyPolic8>
        <![CDATA[Third party sites This website contains links to other websites. <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.]]> </privacyPolic8>
    <GoogleAnalyticstheirprivacypolicycanbefoundhere>
        <![CDATA[Google Analytics; their privacy policy can be found here <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> website makes use of: ]]></GoogleAnalyticstheirprivacypolicycanbefoundhere>
    <privacyPolicLI1>Google Analytics; their privacy policy can be found</privacyPolicLI1>
    <privacyPolicLI2>PayPal; their privacy policy can be found</privacyPolicLI2>
    <here>Here</here>
    <Dataretentionpolicy>Data retention policy</Dataretentionpolicy>
    <privacyPolicy9>We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you
        with services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations,
        resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
    </privacyPolicy9>
    <DataSecurity>Data Security</DataSecurity>
    <privacyPolicy10>Our website incorporates physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard the
        confidentiality of your personal information. We protect your personal information online, and we also take
        several steps to protect your personal information in our facilities.
    </privacyPolicy10>
    <privacyPolicy11>While we use industry-standard precautions to safeguard your personal information, due to the
        nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee complete security.
    </privacyPolicy11>
    <Changestothisprivacypolicy>Changes to this privacy policy</Changestothisprivacypolicy>
    <privacyPolicy12>We may add new services and features to this website. In the event that these additions affect our
        privacy policy, or if other changes in our privacy practices or applicable laws necessitate changes to the
        privacy policy, this document will be updated accordingly. If we make a material change in the way we use your
        personal information, we will provide prominent notice of the change on this website.
    </privacyPolicy12>
    <privacyPolicy13>
        <![CDATA[If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this website, or your dealings with it, you can contact <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> at the address below.]]></privacyPolicy13>
    <privacyPolicy14>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers</privacyPolicy14>
    <TitleOne>Al -Taiseer Bldg No. (75), S. Nabulsi Str. Al – Abdali</TitleOne>
    <Titletwo>P.O.Box: 926428 – Amman 11190 Jordan</Titletwo>
    <Titlethree>Tel: +962 (6) 5698308 Fax: +962 (6) 5639185</Titlethree>
    <Titlefour>E-mail: info@manhal.com</Titlefour>
    <country>Country</country>
    <Gender>Gender</Gender>
    <TermsConditionsp1>
        <![CDATA[This website is owned and operated by <b>Dar Al-ManhalPublishers</b>, and is made available on the following terms and conditions. Please read these terms of use carefully because, by using our website, you confirm that you accept these terms of use and that you agree to comply with them.]]></TermsConditionsp1>
    <Copyrightandownership>Copyright and ownership</Copyrightandownership>
    <TermsConditionsp2>
        <![CDATA[All of the content featured, displayed or offered for sale on the website, including, but not limited to, text, graphics, photographs, images, moving images, sound, illustrations, software and any other content (collectively, the “Content”), is owned by <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b>, its licensors, vendors and/or its content providers. All elements of the website, including but not limited to the general design and the content, are protected by trade dress, copyright, moral rights, trademark and other laws relating to intellectual property rights. You may not modify any of the materials and you may not copy, distribute, transmit, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, create derivative works from, transfer or sell any information or work contained on the website. Except as permitted under applicable copyright laws, you are responsible for obtaining permission before re-using any copyrighted material that is available on the website. For purposes of these terms, the use of any such material on any other website or networked computer environment is prohibited. You shall comply with all applicable domestic and international laws, statutes, ordinances and regulations regarding your use of the website. The website, the content and all related rights shall remain the exclusive property of <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> Publishers unless otherwise expressly agreed in writing. You will not remove any copyright, trademark or other proprietary notices from material found on this website.]]></TermsConditionsp2>
    <Siteaccesslicense>Site access license</Siteaccesslicense>
    <TermsConditionsp3>
        <![CDATA[<b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> grants you a limited, revocable, non-exclusive, non-transferable license to access and make personal, noncommercial use of the website or its content and not to download (other than page caching or unless otherwise allowed by <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> or permitted by law) or modify all or any portion of the website and its content. This license does not include any re-sale or commercial use of the website and its content; any collection and use of any product listings, descriptions, or prices; any derivative use of the website and its content; any downloading or copying of account information for the benefit of another merchant; or any use of data mining, robots, or similar data gathering and extraction tools. The website and/or any portion of the website or its content may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose without <b>Dar Al-Manhal’</b>s express prior written consent. You shall not frame or utilize framing techniques to enclose any trademark, logo or other proprietary information (including images, text, page layout or form) of Dar Al-Manhal, its content providers or its affiliates without express prior written consent. You shall not use any meta tags or any other “hidden text” utilizing our name or trademarks without our express prior written consent. Additionally, you agree that you will not: (i) take any action that imposes, or may impose in our sole discretion an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on our infrastructure; (ii) interfere or attempt to interfere with the proper working of the website or any activities conducted on the website; or (iii) bypass any measures we may use to prevent or restrict access to the website. Any unauthorized use automatically terminates the permissions and/or licenses granted by us to you.]]></TermsConditionsp3>
    <Corporateidentificationtrademarks>Corporate identification &amp; trademarks</Corporateidentificationtrademarks>
    <TermsConditionsp4>
        <![CDATA[ All of our trademarks, service marks and trade names used herein (including but not limited to the corporate names and logos of <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> and its publishing divisions and imprints, names and designs of the website, and any logos) are trademarks or registered trademarks of<b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> or its affiliates and partners. You may not use, copy, reproduce, republish, upload, post, transmit, distribute, or modify such trademarks in any way, including in advertising or publicity pertaining to distribution of materials on the website, without Dar Al-Manhal’s express prior written consent. The use of our trademarks on any other website or network computer environment is not allowed. You are granted a limited, revocable, non-exclusive, non-transferable right to create a link to any page of the website so long as the link does not portray us, our content providers, our licensors, our affiliates, or our products or services in a false, misleading, derogatory or otherwise offensive manner. You may not use any <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> logo or other proprietary graphic or trademark as part of the link without express written permission. Except as expressly stated herein, no rights or licenses are granted hereunder.]]></TermsConditionsp4>
    <Linkstothirdpartiesnoendorsement>Links to third parties &amp; no endorsement</Linkstothirdpartiesnoendorsement>
    <TermsConditionsp5>
        <![CDATA[ The website contains links to other websites controlled by third parties. These links are provided solely as a convenience to you and do not imply endorsement by <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> of, or any affiliation with, or endorsement by, the owner of the linked website.<b> Dar Al-Manhal</b> is not responsible for the contents or use of any linked website, or any consequence of making the link. The websites may also include a tool that allows you to sign in or register using information from your account with a third party service (e.g., Facebook, Twitter). These third party services are unrelated to the websites, and your use of such third party services is subject to the terms and policies of those services. You shall not use <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b>’s name or any language, pictures or symbols which could, in <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b>’s judgment, imply <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b>’s endorsement in any (i) written or oral advertising or presentation, or (ii) brochure, newsletter, book, or other written material of whatever nature, without prior written consent.]]></TermsConditionsp5>
    <Fees>Fees</Fees>
    <TermsConditionsp6>
        <![CDATA[ For all charges for any products and services sold on the website, <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> or its vendors or agents will bill your credit card or an alternative payment method. When you provide credit card information to us or our vendors, you represent to us that you are the authorized user of the credit card that is used to pay for the products and services. In the event legal action is necessary to collect on balances due, you agree to reimburse <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> and its vendors or agents for all expenses incurred to recover sums due, including attorney’s fees and other legal expenses. You are responsible for purchase of, and payment of charges for, all Internet access services and telecommunications services needed for use of the websites.]]></TermsConditionsp6>
    <TermsConditionsp7>
        <![CDATA[Data collection and use, including data collection and use of personal information is governed by <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b>’s Privacy Policy which is incorporated into and is a part of this agreement. ]]></TermsConditionsp7>
    <Usersubmissions>User submissions</Usersubmissions>
    <TermsConditionsp8>
        <![CDATA[Where we have specifically invited or requested user submitted content of any kind, we encourage members of the public to submit such content (e.g., user generated content, comments on content) to <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> that they have created for consideration in connection with the website and any related programs (“User Submissions”). User Submissions remain the intellectual property of the individual user. By posting your content on the website, you expressly grant <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> a non-exclusive, perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, fully paid-up worldwide, fully sub-licensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, transmit, perform and display such content and your name, voice, and/or likeness as contained in your user submission, in whole or in part, and in any form throughout the world in any media or technology, whether now known or hereafter discovered, including all promotion, advertising, marketing, merchandising, publicity and any other ancillary uses thereof, and including the unfettered right to sublicense such rights, in perpetuity throughout the universe. We may refuse or remove user submissions for any reason and without notice. All user submissions are deemed non-confidential and <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> shall be under no obligation to maintain the confidentiality of any information, in whatever form, contained in any user submission. ]]></TermsConditionsp8>
    <TermsConditionsp9>
        <![CDATA[By submitting any user submissions, you consent to the following rules: ]]></TermsConditionsp9>
    <TermsConditionsp10>
        <![CDATA[User submissions must not infringe on the copyright, trademark, patent or other intellectual property right of any third party. If your user submission is not your original work, you must obtain all necessary permissions from any persons who contributed to or otherwise may control rights in all or part of the user submission to submit the user submission in accordance with these terms.]]></TermsConditionsp10>
    <TermsConditionsp11>
        <![CDATA[User submissions must not violate a third party’s right to privacy or publicity. You must obtain all necessary permissions from any individuals identified in or implicated by your User submission, including those shown in photographic content, and, in the case of minors, also from their parents or legal guardians, as appropriate. ]]></TermsConditionsp11>
    <TermsConditionsp12>
        <![CDATA[User submissions must be respectful of others. Epithets or other language or material intended to intimidate or to incite violence are strictly prohibited. Your user submission may not include any negative comments that are connected to race, national origin, gender, sexual orientation or physical handicap or that are defamatory, slanderous, indecent, obscene, pornographic or sexually explicit. ]]></TermsConditionsp12>
    <TermsConditionsp13>
        <![CDATA[User submissions may not contain any commercial material. You may not solicit funds, promote commercial entities or otherwise engage in commercial activity through your user submission. ]]></TermsConditionsp13>
    <TermsConditionsp14>
        <![CDATA[Soliciting other users to join or become members of any commercial online service or other organization is expressly prohibited. ]]></TermsConditionsp14>
    <TermsConditionsp15>
        <![CDATA[Do not impersonate any other person or entity or falsely state or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with any person or entity.]]></TermsConditionsp15>
    <TermsConditionsp16>
        <![CDATA[Remember that forums and other areas of the website are public. Do not post personal information (e.g., full name, password, phone number, address, email address or other personally identifiable information or contact information) in these areas.]]></TermsConditionsp16>
    <TermsConditionsp17>
        <![CDATA[All user submissions must comply with these rules and any additional guidelines posted on the website, as applicable. User submissions do not represent the views of <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> or any individual associated with <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b>, and we do not control this content. In no event shall you represent or suggest, directly or indirectly, <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b>’s endorsement of user submissions. <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> does not vouch for the accuracy or credibility of any user submissions, and does not take any responsibility or assume any liability for any actions you may take as a result of reading user submissions on the website. Through your use of the website, you may be exposed to content and user submissions that you may find offensive, objectionable, harmful, inaccurate or deceptive. There may also be risks of dealing with underage persons, people acting under false pretense, international trade issues and foreign nationals. By using the website, you assume all associated risks.]]></TermsConditionsp17>
    <Removalofusersubmissions>Removal of user submissions</Removalofusersubmissions>
    <TermsConditionsp18>
        <![CDATA[We will not monitor, edit, or disclose the contents of a user’s email unless required in the course of normal maintenance of the website and its systems or unless required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) comply with the law or comply with legal process served on <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b>; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b>, the website, or the users of <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b>; or (3) act in an emergency to protect the personal safety of our guests, the website, or the public. Users shall remain solely responsible for the content of their messages and <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> shall have no obligation to pre-screen any such content. However, we shall have the right in our sole discretion to edit, refuse to post or remove any material submitted to or posted on the website. Without limiting the foregoing, we shall have the right to remove any material that we find to be in violation of the provisions hereof or otherwise objectionable, and the additional right to deny any user who fails to conform to any provision of these terms access to the website.]]></TermsConditionsp18>
    <Accountregistrationandsecurity>Account registration and security</Accountregistrationandsecurity>
    <TermsConditionsp19>
        <![CDATA[If you decide to register as a member of a website, you may receive or establish one or more user names, passwords and accounts. In consideration of use of your registration, you will: (a) provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself as prompted by the applicable registration form (such information being the “Registration Data”) and (b) maintain and promptly update the Registration Data to keep it true, accurate, current and complete. If you provide any information that is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, or <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> has grounds to suspect that such information is untrue, inaccurate, not current or incomplete, <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> has the right to suspend or terminate your account and refuse any and all current or future use of the website (or any portion thereof). You are entirely responsible for the security and confidentiality of your password and account. Furthermore, you are entirely responsible for any and all activities that occur under your account. You agree to immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your account or any other breach of security of which you become aware. You are responsible for taking precautions and providing security measures best suited for your situation and intended use of the registration and website. We have the right to provide user billing, account, content or user records, and related information under certain circumstances (such as in response to legal responsibility, lawful process, orders, subpoenas, or warrants, or to protect our rights, customers or business) to third parties.]]></TermsConditionsp19>
    <Termination>Termination</Termination>
    <TermsConditionsp20>
        <![CDATA[<b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> may suspend or terminate any user’s access to all or any part of the website including any account thereon, without notice, for any reason in <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b>’s sole discretion, including without limitation <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b>’s belief that such access would violate any applicable law or would be harmful to the interests of <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> or another user. Upon termination, you will lose access to the website and all content thereon. The obligations that you have to <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> under these terms will continue even after we suspend or terminate your access to the website.]]></TermsConditionsp20>
    <Forcemajeure>Force majeure</Forcemajeure>
    <TermsConditionsp21>
        <![CDATA[Neither <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> nor you shall be responsible for damages or for delays or failures in performance resulting from acts or occurrences beyond their respective reasonable control, including, without limitation: fire, lightning, explosion, power surge or failure, water, war, revolution, civil commotion or acts of civil or military authorities or public enemies: any law, order, regulation, ordinance, or requirement of any government or legal body or any representative of any such government or legal body; or labor unrest, including without limitation, strikes, slowdowns, picketing, or boycotts; inability to secure raw materials, transportation facilities, fuel or energy shortages, or acts or omissions of other common carriers.]]></TermsConditionsp21>
    <Entireagreement>Entire agreement</Entireagreement>
    <TermsConditionsp22>
        <![CDATA[This agreement is the entire agreement between the user and <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> and supersedes any prior understandings or agreements (written or oral).]]></TermsConditionsp22>
    <Games>Games</Games>
    <livedemo>Demo</livedemo>
    <Interactive>Interactive</Interactive>
    <PaperCopy>Paper Copy</PaperCopy>
    <ElectronicCopy>Electronic Copy</ElectronicCopy>
    <EnrichmentCopy>Enrichment Copy</EnrichmentCopy>
    <InteractiveCopy>Interactive Copy</InteractiveCopy>
    <Item>Item</Item>
    <Description>Description</Description>
    <Comments>Comments</Comments>
    <Share>Share</Share>
    <ScreenShots>Screen Shots</ScreenShots>
    <Comment>Comment</Comment>
    <Addtofavorite>Add to Favorite</Addtofavorite>
    <Numberofpages>No. of Pages</Numberofpages>
    <Binding>Binding</Binding>
    <ProductDimensions>Product Dimensions and Weight</ProductDimensions>
    <Weight>Weight</Weight>
    <Cm>cm</Cm>
    <writecomment>write a comment</writecomment>
    <SignInToAddComment>Please sign in here to add comment</SignInToAddComment>
    <Year>Year</Year>
    <Month>Month</Month>
    <AboutUs1>
        <![CDATA[<b>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers</b> is one of the largest Arab publishing houses which are specialized in the field of children's literature. It was established in 1990 and since that it is a pioneer Arabic publishing house in publishing children's books and various educational programs. <b>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers</b> is a distinctive in the production of integrated cultural programs, teaching aids in both Arabic and English languages, and powerful audio versions.]]></AboutUs1>
    <AboutUs2>
        <![CDATA[Our mission is to provide high quality books and products that help children to grow educationally strong, and enrich their knowledge. For more than 25 years, <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> has delivered experiences through its bestselling books, curriculum, stories, academic resources and newly its digital products. We are committed to provide your children with excellent services and resources to meet their unique needs. Some of our resources will educate children and increase the positive thinking, others may inspire them to try something new, but most of all; we can help to find a resource that will increase your child passion for learning.]]></AboutUs2>
    <AboutUs3>
        <![CDATA[We are located in Amman, Jordan. Our books are available in both print and e-book editions, and are sold internationally.]]></AboutUs3>
    <PublishYear>Publication Year</PublishYear>
    <BuyNow>Buy Now</BuyNow>
    <AddCart>Add to Cart</AddCart>
    <BackCover>Back Cover</BackCover>
    <BookRWidth>Actual Width</BookRWidth>
    <BookRHeight>Actual Height</BookRHeight>
    <Grade>Grade</Grade>
    <SoftCover>Soft Cover</SoftCover>
    <HardCover>Hard Cover</HardCover>
    <Semester>Semester</Semester>
    <all>All</all>
    <One>One</One>
    <Tow>Two</Tow>
    <iprice>Interactive Price</iprice>
    <eprice>Electronic Price</eprice>
    <Kindergarten>Kindergarten</Kindergarten>
    <AddStory>Add Story</AddStory>
    <StoryInfo>Story Information</StoryInfo>
    <StoryWidth>Story Width</StoryWidth>
    <StoryHeight>Story Height</StoryHeight>
    <FrontCover>Front Cover</FrontCover>
    <ParentAdvice>Parents Advice</ParentAdvice>
    <ParentAdviceSound>Parents Advice Sound</ParentAdviceSound>
    <PleaseInsertTitle>Please enter title</PleaseInsertTitle>
    <PaperStory>Paper Story</PaperStory>
    <estory>Electronic Story</estory>
    <StoryWeight>Story Weight</StoryWeight>
    <TitleSound>Title Sound</TitleSound>
    <NewsTitle1>New Edition</NewsTitle1>
    <Newsparagraph1>The wonderful educational book for non-Arabic speakers        <b>“Friends of Arabia 4”</b>        is
        now released from Dar Al-Manhal Publishers.
    </Newsparagraph1>
    <NewsTitle2>New Arrival</NewsTitle2>
    <Newsparagraph2>A large selection of indoor and outdoor classroom and nursery equipment and essentials is now
        available at Dar Al-Manhal showroom – Al-Abdali.
    </Newsparagraph2>
    <ReadMores>...Read More</ReadMores>
    <AddSeries>Add Series</AddSeries>
    <donthavepermession>You don't have permissions</donthavepermession>
    <AdviceSound>Advice Sound</AdviceSound>
    <BackgroundSound>Background Sound</BackgroundSound>
    <Thumbnail>Thumbnail</Thumbnail>
    <Big_Thumbnail>Big Thumbnail</Big_Thumbnail>
    <Small_Thumbnail>Small Thumbnail</Small_Thumbnail>
    <NoFiling>Register No.</NoFiling>
    <Gm>Gm</Gm>
    <Other>Others</Other>
    <youMustLogin>You must sign in to do this process</youMustLogin>
    <RelatedProduct>Related Products</RelatedProduct>
    <Rating>Rating</Rating>
    <statistics>Statistics</statistics>
    <Bysubject>By subject</Bysubject>
    <ByGrade>By Grade</ByGrade>
    <Kindergarten>Kindergarten</Kindergarten>
    <ByAge>By Age</ByAge>
    <Publishingyears>Publication Year</Publishingyears>
    <Years>Years</Years>
    <ISBNNumber>ISBN Number</ISBNNumber>
    <ISBNNo>ISBN No.</ISBNNo>
    <ISBN>ISBN No.</ISBN>
    <From>From</From>
    <TO>to</TO>
    <FirstSemester>First Semester</FirstSemester>
    <SecondSemester>Second Semester</SecondSemester>
    <ThirdSemester>Third Semester</ThirdSemester>
    <Option>Type</Option>
    <Paperbooks>Paper Books</Paperbooks>
    <Ebooks>Electronic Books</Ebooks>
    <Enrichmentbook>Interactive Books</Enrichmentbook>
    <SortBy>Sorting</SortBy>
    <Sortalphabetically>Alphabetically</Sortalphabetically>
    <DefaultSorting>Default</DefaultSorting>
    <Sortbypopularity>Most Viewed</Sortbypopularity>
    <Sortbyaveragerating>Most Rated</Sortbyaveragerating>
    <Sortbynewness>Most Recent</Sortbynewness>
    <Sortbypricelowtohigh>Sort by price : low to high</Sortbypricelowtohigh>
    <Sortbypricehightolow>Sort by price : high to low</Sortbypricehightolow>
    <Cart>Cart</Cart>
    <ItemAddSuccess>Added to your cart successfully</ItemAddSuccess>
    <RemoveFromCart>Remove from Cart</RemoveFromCart>
    <Leaveyourcomments>Comments</Leaveyourcomments>
    <Address1>Address 1</Address1>
    <Address2>Address 2</Address2>
    <City>City</City>
    <Shippingmethod>Shipping Method</Shippingmethod>
    <PaymentMethod>Payment Method</PaymentMethod>
    <CashOnDelivery>Cash on Delivery</CashOnDelivery>
    <PayPalVisaMasterCard><![CDATA[PayPal, Visa Card, Master Card]]></PayPalVisaMasterCard>
    <ViewMoreEvents>View More Events</ViewMoreEvents>
    <ReviewYourOrder>Review Your Order</ReviewYourOrder>
    <Product>Product</Product>
    <QTY>Quantity</QTY>
    <GrandTotal>Grand Total</GrandTotal>
    <en>en</en>
    <PayNow>Buy Now</PayNow>    <!--10-9-2016-->
    <indexTitle>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers | Arab publishing house | Home</indexTitle>
    <booksTitle>Dar Al-Manhal Books | E-Books | Online Books | Curricula</booksTitle>
    <storyTitle>Stories for kids</storyTitle>
    <editorTitle>Editors | Online Books Editors | Online Stories Editor | Online Books Editor</editorTitle>
    <productsTitle>Products | Books | Stories | Editors | Interactive Games | Educational Tools | School Furnitures
    </productsTitle>
    <servicesTitle>Services | Publishing | School Furnitures | Interactive Games | Books | Stories</servicesTitle>
    <gamesTitle>Games | Interactive Games | Exercises</gamesTitle>
    <contactusTitle>Contact Us</contactusTitle>
    <aboutusTitle>About Us</aboutusTitle>
    <sitemapTitle>Sitemap</sitemapTitle>
    <newsTitle>News</newsTitle>
    <newsDetailsTitle>News</newsDetailsTitle>
    <eventsTitle>Events</eventsTitle>
    <eventsDetailsTitle>Events</eventsDetailsTitle>
    <applicationsTitle>Application | Stories Application | Educational Application | Android | IOS</applicationsTitle>
    <privacyTitle>Privacy Policy</privacyTitle>
    <termsTitle>Terms and Conditions</termsTitle>
    <favoritesTitle>Favorites</favoritesTitle>
    <purchasedTitle>Purchased Items</purchasedTitle>
    <editaccountTitle>Edit Account</editaccountTitle>
    <changepassTitle>Change Password</changepassTitle>
    <cartTitle>Check Out</cartTitle>
    <benifitsTitle>Products | Books | Stories | Online Books | Online Stories | Eduactional Games</benifitsTitle>
    <featuresTitle>Features</featuresTitle>
    <galleriesTitle>Gallery</galleriesTitle>
    <makeMoneyTitle>Make Moeny Online</makeMoneyTitle>
    <ourpartnersTitle>Our Partners</ourpartnersTitle>
    <whatofferTitle>Services | Dar Al-manhal</whatofferTitle>
    <schooldesc>
        <![CDATA[We enable teachers to enrich the educational process with interactive and educational contents for all students at all levels. They can add questions and exercises as part of the E-book. In addition to, <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> platform enable students to enter the E-learning world through what we offer from applications, educational games, and digital contents.]]></schooldesc>
    <Familiesdesc>
        <![CDATA[We offer a wide variety of stories and books that suit children of any age group, which makes our website a complete and integrated library for them and their families. All content is controlled and censored so there is no fear to contain any material that is not suitable for your children. ]]></Familiesdesc>
    <Publishersdesc>
        <![CDATA[Publishing books or stories and delivering them to a large number of people is the main goal of the publishers, and as a publisher, <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> is the most appropriate place to publish your work online. Let users come to you rather than going to them, all you need is just publishing on our store so thousands of users will visit our store every day and reach you easily.]]></Publishersdesc>
    <Authorsdesc>
        <![CDATA[Stories and books contain a large number of images, colors, and tools, etc… therefore; writing and making them require a lot of time and effort. <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> offers authors all what they need; our intuitive editors enable any user to become an author and allow him to make his own professional book without the need for any technical knowledge.]]></Authorsdesc>
    <IpadandMobileAppsdesc>
        <![CDATA[<b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> App is an incredible application that is running on tablets and smart phones with Android and IOS operating systems. Its complement to the main platform, so that any user can buy any product from <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> store and has the ability to browse it on his smart device. Also he can browse the store, buy and browse it all by this application.]]></IpadandMobileAppsdesc>
    <indexDescription>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers Home Page, Best Website to buy educational Books and stories, educational
        games,worksheets,Interactive worksheet.
    </indexDescription>
    <booksDescription>Contains Dar Almanhal books (curricula, kids’ books, ..) whether they are Arabic books, English
        books, math books, .., and offer them for sale online.
    </booksDescription>
    <booksDescriptionT1>**** books interested in teaching **** for kids, offered **** lessons simply and supported by
        practical activities and **** exercises.
    </booksDescriptionT1>
    <booksDescriptionT2>**** books teach **** lessons for kids supported by activities and exercises. Books includes
        variety topics like: ---- that aims to teach ---- .
    </booksDescriptionT2>
    <booksDescriptionT3>Contains Dar Almanhal books (curricula, kids books, ..), offer them for sale online. Books
        include many topics like: ---- ; aims to teach ---- .
    </booksDescriptionT3>
    <teacherbooksDescription>Contains teachers guides for Dar Almanhal books whether they are Arabic, math, science..,
        and offer them for sale online in an electronic version
    </teacherbooksDescription>
    <teacherbooksDescriptionT1>Teachers guides help teachers to teach **** for kids, offered **** lessons simply and
        supported by activities and math exercises.
    </teacherbooksDescriptionT1>
    <teacherbooksDescriptionT2>Teachers guides help teachers to teach **** lesson for kids. Books includes variety
        topics like: ---- that aims to teach ----.
    </teacherbooksDescriptionT2>
    <teacherbooksDescriptionT3>Contains teachers guides for Dar Almanhal books in an electronic version. Books include
        topics like ----; aims to teach ----.
    </teacherbooksDescriptionT3>
    <storyDescription>Contains kid’s stories offered from Dar Almanhal includes short stories, stories in Arabic,
        English and even French, and offer them for sale online.
    </storyDescription>
    <storyDescriptionT1>**** stories from Dar Almanhal offer stories for kids, short stories, Arabic stories, English
        stories and even French stories.
    </storyDescriptionT1>
    <storyDescriptionT2>Contains kid’s stories from Dar Almanhal includes short stories, stories in Arabic, English, and
        offer them to sale online like ====.
    </storyDescriptionT2>
    <storyDescriptionT3>====series from Dar Almanhal comes within **** stories include kids stories, short stories,
        Arabic stories, English stories.
    </storyDescriptionT3>
    <storyDescriptionT4>The story ---- comes within **** stories from Dar Almanhal that include kids' stories, short
        stories, Arabic stories, English stories.
    </storyDescriptionT4>
    <storyDescriptionT5>story comes in ==== series from Dar Almanhal that include kids stories, short stories, Arabic
        stories, English stories.
    </storyDescriptionT5>
    <storyDescriptionT6>---- story comes in ==== within **** stories from Dar Almanhal that include kids stories, Arabic
        and English stories.
    </storyDescriptionT6>
    <storyDescriptionT7>---- story is one of Dar Almanhal stories which include kids stories, Arabic and English
        stories, and offered for sale online.
    </storyDescriptionT7>
    <editorDescription>with dar almanhal editors, you can create books using Books Editor, or craete stories using
        Stories Editor, and enjoy with our Drag Drop books Editor,Drag Drop Stories Editor,Online books editor,online
        stories editor,interactive books editor,interactive stories editor,Stories Applications editor,Quiz
        Creator,Online Quiz Editor
    </editorDescription>
    <productsDescription>Books,Stories,Games,Educational Tools,Educational Furnitures,Electronic Books,Interactive
        Books,Electronic Stories,Interactive Stories,Educational Applications,Games Applications
    </productsDescription>
    <servicesDescription>Books Publishing,Editors For Authors,Educational and Interactive Books for schools,Educational
        Tools,children's Furnitures
    </servicesDescription>
    <gamesDescription>Contains online games offered from Dar Almanhal that teach children, and develop their skills in
        curricula through purposeful educational games.
    </gamesDescription>
    <gamesDescriptionT1>**** games interested in teaching **** for kids, offered **** lessons simply using e-learning
        techniques through educational games.
    </gamesDescriptionT1>
    <gamesDescriptionT2>**** games teach **** lessons for kids using e-learning through educational games. Games include
        topics like: ---- that aims to teach ----.
    </gamesDescriptionT2>
    <gamesDescriptionT3>Contains online games that teach children, develop skills in curricula through educational
        games. Games include topics like: ----; teach ----.
    </gamesDescriptionT3>
    <contactusDescription>Dar Al-Manhal Contact Information,telephone,fax,mobile,address,email,map
    </contactusDescription>
    <aboutusDescription>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers,About Us,Information</aboutusDescription>
    <sitemapDescription>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers Website Sitemap,Sitemap</sitemapDescription>
    <newsDescription>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers News,News</newsDescription>
    <newsDetailsDescription>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers News,News</newsDetailsDescription>
    <eventsDescription>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers Events</eventsDescription>
    <eventsDetailsDescription>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers Events</eventsDetailsDescription>
    <applicationsDescription>Applications Editor,Android Applications,iOS Applications,Educational
        Applications,Interactive Applications,Online Applications
    </applicationsDescription>
    <privacyDescription>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers Privacy Policy</privacyDescription>
    <favoritesDescription>Dar Almanhal Publishers Favorites</favoritesDescription>
    <purchasedDescription>Dar Almanhal Publishers Purchased Items</purchasedDescription>
    <editaccountDescription>Dar Almanhal Publishers Edit Account</editaccountDescription>
    <changepassDescription>Dar Almanhal Publishers Change Password</changepassDescription>
    <featuresDescription>Dar Almanhal Publishers Features</featuresDescription>
    <galleriesDescription>Dar Almanhal Publishers Gallery</galleriesDescription>
    <makeMoneyDescription>Make Money Online,How To make Money,Make Money</makeMoneyDescription>
    <ourpartnersDescription>Dar Almanhal Publishers Our Partner</ourpartnersDescription>
    <whatofferDescription>Dar Almanhal Publishers Services,What we offer</whatofferDescription>
    <indexKeywords>Dar Al-manhal Publishers,Home Page,Educational Books,Educational Stories,Educational
        Games,Educational Tools,Educational Furnitures,Electronic Books,Interactive Books,Electronic Stories,Interactive
        Stories,Worksheets,Interactive Worksheets
    </indexKeywords>
    <booksKeywords>Books,Electronic Books,Interactive Books,Online Books,Educational Books,kids Books,buy books online
    </booksKeywords>
    <storyKeywords>Stories,Electronic Stories,Interactive Stories,Online Stories,Educational Stories,kids Stories,buy
        Stories online
    </storyKeywords>
    <editorKeywords>Books Editor,Stories Editor,Drag Drop books Editor,Drag Drop Stories Editor,Online books
        editor,online stories editor,interactive books editor,interactive stories editor,Stories Applications
        editor,Quiz creator,Online Quiz Editor
    </editorKeywords>
    <productsKeywords>Books,Stories,Games,Educational Tools,Educational Furnitures,Electronic Books,Interactive
        Books,Electronic Stories,Interactive Stories,Educational Application,Games Application
    </productsKeywords>
    <servicesKeywords>Books Publishing,Editors For Authors,Educational and Interactive Books for schools,Educational
        Tools,children's Furnitures
    </servicesKeywords>
    <gamesKeywords>Online Games,Interactive Games,Educational Games</gamesKeywords>
    <contactusKeywords>Dar Al-Manhal Contact Information,telephone,fax,mobile,address,email,map</contactusKeywords>
    <aboutusKeywords>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers,About Us,Information</aboutusKeywords>
    <sitemapKeywords>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers Website Sitemap,Sitemap</sitemapKeywords>
    <newsKeywords>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers News,News</newsKeywords>
    <newsDetailsKeywords>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers News,News</newsDetailsKeywords>
    <eventsKeywords>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers Events</eventsKeywords>
    <eventsDetailsKeywords>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers Events</eventsDetailsKeywords>
    <applicationsKeywords>Applications Editor,Android Applications,iOS Applications,Educational Applications,Interactive
        Applications,Online Applications
    </applicationsKeywords>
    <privacyKeywords>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers Privacy Policy</privacyKeywords>
    <favoritesKeywords>Dar Almanhal Publishers Favorites</favoritesKeywords>
    <purchasedKeywords>Dar Almanhal Publishers Purchased Items</purchasedKeywords>
    <editaccountKeywords>Dar Almanhal Publishers Edit Account</editaccountKeywords>
    <changepassKeywords>Dar Almanhal Publishers Change Password</changepassKeywords>
    <featuresKeywords>Dar Almanhal Publishers Features</featuresKeywords>
    <galleriesKeywords>Dar Almanhal Publishers Gallery</galleriesKeywords>
    <makeMoneyKeywords>Make Money Online,How To make Money,Make Money</makeMoneyKeywords>
    <ourpartnersKeywords>Dar Almanhal Publishers Our Partner</ourpartnersKeywords>
    <whatofferKeywords>Dar Almanhal Publishers Services,What we offer</whatofferKeywords>
    <ChildSound>Child Sound</ChildSound>
    <Storytextpage>Page Text</Storytextpage>
    <PageSound>Page Sound</PageSound>
    <EditPageStory>Edit Story</EditPageStory>
    <Fax>Fax</Fax>
    <SiteName>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers</SiteName>
    <Book>Book</Book>
    <InteractiveBook>Interactive Book</InteractiveBook>
    <ElectronicBook>Electronic Book</ElectronicBook>
    <OnlineBook>Online Book</OnlineBook>
    <Story>Story</Story>
    <ElectronicStory>Electronic Story</ElectronicStory>
    <InteractiveStory>Interactive Story</InteractiveStory>
    <EnrichmentStory>Enrichment Story</EnrichmentStory>
    <OnlineStory>Online Story</OnlineStory>
    <Game>Game</Game>
    <OnlineGame>Online Game</OnlineGame>
    <InteractiveGame>Interactive Game</InteractiveGame>
    <isPublished>Published</isPublished>
    <ChoseCountry>Choose Country</ChoseCountry>
    <ChoseCity>Choose City</ChoseCity>
    <DescriptionAr>Arabic Description</DescriptionAr>
    <DescriptionEn>English Description</DescriptionEn>
    <PostCode>Zip Code</PostCode>
    <State>State</State>
    <Partners>Partners</Partners>
    <MakeMoneyParagraph2>With Dar Al-Manhal platform, share your creativity, publish and make money by selling your own
        online stories! Our intuitive editors are designed to let you create stunning interactive stories yourself with
        absolute ease then publish for all platforms. As well as enriching your stories with fascinating animations, you
        can also add interactivity, sounds, and even games – all completely intuitively and with absolutely no coding
        required.
    </MakeMoneyParagraph2>
    <MakeMoneyParagraph3>Does it sound easy as drinking a glass of water? Yes, piece of cake! It’s that simple; no
        programming knowledge, no excellent technical skills and no PHD required. You just need to share your thoughts
        and make your electronic story using features and options that provided in our powerful interactive and
        illustrated story editors which will be soon available online.
    </MakeMoneyParagraph3>
    <MakeMoneyParagraph4>Once you're happy with your story, share it instantly with the world, then sell and make money
        online.
    </MakeMoneyParagraph4>
    <MakeMoneyParagraph5>Our platform is now available on almost any device (laptops, iPads, smart phones and personal
        computers) so your global market is huge!
    </MakeMoneyParagraph5>
    <MakeMoneyParagraph6>The best thing about this lucrative idea is that once you’ve invested the time, you’ll earn a
        passive income for years to come!
    </MakeMoneyParagraph6>
    <MakeMoneyParagraph7>With us, simply publish and earn</MakeMoneyParagraph7>
    <Clear>Clear</Clear>
    <AllStories>All Stories</AllStories>
    <BetaVersion>Beta Version</BetaVersion>
    <ProductsParagraph1>Professional book publishing and services</ProductsParagraph1>
    <ProductsParagraph2>We offer a comprehensive range of best books and E-learning technologies; so we can be an
        effective element in your child learning success.
    </ProductsParagraph2>
    <ProductsBookDesc>
        <![CDATA[We at <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> make your child a reader in childhood, through producing cultural programs, educational contents, and high level projects that are enriching his knowledge, and expanding his horizon. <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> aims to help you develop your child by offering the widest collection of kindergarten and school books, which are created by experts to help learners achieve specific academic or occupational goals. All you need is to browse our library of books to find an engaging book for your child. ]]></ProductsBookDesc>
    <ProductsEbookDesc>
        <![CDATA[Are you looking for a great reading experience? Do want to build your online library? Simply, you are in the right place! We are going strong in our mission to provide a valuable service to help you make the best use of studying time, therefore; <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> becomes a central place to discover E-books. It provides one of the best reading tools, so reading books or studying will be more efficient. You can browse any of our editions right on your smart phone or tablet, so your favorite books can be read on computers or other electronic devices. With us reading is a pleasure, and learning becomes easier! In addition to, we provide a simple way to create electronic books, using our quick and easy online book creator. No programming knowledge is required; we offer powerful tools that could help you make your own electronic book without the need to write a single code, you will already know how to create a book. ]]></ProductsEbookDesc>
    <ProductsInteractiveBooksDesc>
        <![CDATA[Our new interactive books is a fantastic way for your little ones to interact with the exciting world they live in. <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> wants to help make studying fun and more efficient with interactive books covering all sorts of subjects. Our goal is to create premium interactive digital books by paying close attention to the reading experience, and using innovative interactivity that captivates and delights our readers. Your child will absolutely love touching objects to see what happens next, besides; sound effects, changing colors, activates, music and animations and all sorts of fun surprises await your reader on each page. ]]></ProductsInteractiveBooksDesc>
    <ProductsStoriesDesc>
        <![CDATA[Reading is a world of pleasure and knowledge enrichment, therefore; we offer a comprehensive and successful range of stories that are specialized in children’s literature in different languages (Arabic, English and even French). Our stories develop the child's love for daily reading habit and direct him to acquire the correct habits and values. We also provide stories packages which contain various picked short stories from our great editions. These packages are divided into levels according to the age group. Whether you’re looking for a story to share with your youngest child or something to keep your ten years old motivated, we’re here to help. ]]></ProductsStoriesDesc>
    <ProductsEstoriesDesc>
        <![CDATA[What can be better than putting the technology in good use to develop the reading habit among children? E-stories are the best entertainment options available for children to develop their reading habit! Dar Al-Manhal provides a good collection of electronic stories for the young minds using the great combination of graphics, narration, sound effects and background music, children are attracted to. When a story is being read or narrated by a person, there is always the risk of the child losing interest at some point. With our great electronic stories it is a totally different scenario. Children get glued to it and will surely watch it to the end.]]></ProductsEstoriesDesc>
    <ProductsInteractivestoriesDesc>
        <![CDATA[For children, stories are the window to the outside world. Stories continue to tell generations that the world outside is filled with great adventures. Do you act out the stories to your child? With our interactive stories you haven’t been able to yet! Your children will be able to browse stories interactively. It’s perfect for writers who want to try out interactivity, but also for teachers and students looking to mix computer skills and creative writing. For more efficiency and ease of use, all of our products are available for all operating systems (iOS, Android, Windows), whether you are using (iPad, iPhone, Windows phones or other smart devices). ]]></ProductsInteractivestoriesDesc>
    <ProductsEducationalgamesDesc>
        <![CDATA[What sounds more fun: homework or games? Want educational games that help build skills and educate students? You are in the right place at the right time! Our passion is helping teachers and students to find fun and meaningful ways to integrate technology with learning. We are working hardly to provide the suitable environment for that! Educational games are great tools for building foundation to learn and develop skills that today’s school curriculum require. We offer amazing online learning games for children that are fun and teach important skills for preschool, elementary school and even secondary school. Try our educational games and combine lesson time with playtime. These colorful, animated games make it easy and fun to practice fundamental math, reading skills, language, science, and more at home or on the go. Choose from our educational games that use colorful animations and music to bring important lessons to life and aid memory. No matter where you are or what device you are on; just enjoy our online games which are available for Android devices, iPhone, mobile, tablets, iPad and PC. We believe that games have the potential to help children learn in a way that's not possible with other, therefore; we offer a brilliant virtual world for students, to study without getting bored and allow them to learn wherever and whenever they want. We want you to love learning - no more boring study sessions, you should play games instead! ]]></ProductsEducationalgamesDesc>
    <ProductsEducationalToolsDesc>
        <![CDATA[We at <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> are constantly expanding our products range to reflect the needs of today's education process. We help you discover and develop your children's abilities in modern and innovative ways, by offering a wide range of great educational tools to improve children's mental and linguistic skills. Our educational tools are represented as eye catching flash cards, powerful audio versions, and rich educational posters. Teaching and learning have never been more efficient or easier than with our educational flash cards. <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> is dedicated to bring the best selection of unique educational flash cards in both Arabic and English. Audio versions issued by <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> are considered as a special achievement which helps to teach children listening skills that come before reading and writing in learning skills. It also includes beautiful stories, wonderful melodic songs, performed by group of children with beautiful voices, which give them an educational dimension, and contribute to improve reading and pronunciation. In addition to, we provide amazing educational classroom posters to create a unique teaching environment filled with visual cues for the students. A series of curriculum multimedia CDs in Arabic and English are also available. The series is professionally designed to easily use by children. Our content is developed with the aid of experts who understand the realities of classroom teaching, so we can create visually stimulating products that add real value to the classroom. ]]></ProductsEducationalToolsDesc>
    <ProductsFurnitureDesc>
        <![CDATA[<b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> seeks to be pioneer in all what is concerning with children, and giving them the best. Being the exclusive agent for Edu Fun - an international brand specialized in preschools supplies and furniture - is our way to reach our goal. The environment children play and learn in, have a great effect on them. Therefore we believe in the importance of providing practical, suitable and comfortable designs to fulfill the demands of this critical stage. We provide a complete solution for preschool education and homes, so you can find a full range of furniture which suits the requirements of children in their early years. Modular designs, elegance, and accurate manufacturing all come together to set up unique configurations to suit children needs. The colorful, attractive and durable designs encourage good posture and ensure years of safe and enjoyable use, this means that everything will last for years and years and can be even passed on from one generation to the next. All this we offer at affordable and compatible prices. Edu Fun provides us with full range of products starting with chairs, tables, storage units and reading corners passing through play corners and role play furniture ending with play screens, boards and carpets. If you have any questions about any item, there will always be someone ready and willing to get you the assistance you need. Your complete satisfaction is always our number one priority. ]]></ProductsFurnitureDesc>
    <PagenotFound>Page not found</PagenotFound>
    <HmHarcourt>Houghton Mifflin Harcourt</HmHarcourt>
    <CambridgeDictionary>Cambridge</CambridgeDictionary>
    <CengageLearning>Cengage Learning</CengageLearning>
    <Penguin>Penguin</Penguin>
    <IBID>IBID</IBID>
    <Capstone>Capstone</Capstone>
    <McgrowHill>McGraw-Hill</McgrowHill>
    <OXSFORD>Oxford</OXSFORD>
    <BarronsEducationalSeries>Barrons Educational Series</BarronsEducationalSeries>
    <hoddereducation>Hodder Education</hoddereducation>
    <Longman>Longman</Longman>
    <Letterland>Letterland</Letterland>
    <HarperCollinsPublishers>Harper Collins Publishers</HarperCollinsPublishers>
    <Scholastic>Scholastic</Scholastic>
    <HaeseHarrisPublishers>Haese and Harris Publishers</HaeseHarrisPublishers>
    <Applications>Applications</Applications>
    <Ref>REF</Ref>
    <Close>CLOSED</Close>
    <Open>PENDING</Open>
    <PROCESS>PROCESS</PROCESS>
    <Warehouse>Warehouse</Warehouse>
    <shippingCompany>Shipping Company</shippingCompany>
    <Shippingwarehouse>Shipping</Shippingwarehouse>
    <ExportedDHL>Exported DHL</ExportedDHL>
    <Exported>Exported</Exported>
    <PackageInfo>Package Information</PackageInfo>
    <Shippinginfo>Shipping information</Shippinginfo>
    <ShipperId>SHIPPER ID</ShipperId>
    <RecieverCompanyName>RECIEVER COMPANY NAME</RecieverCompanyName>
    <RecieverId>RECIEVER ID</RecieverId>
    <RecieverAttention>RECIEVER ATTENTION</RecieverAttention>
    <Address3>Address 3</Address3>
    <StateProvince>STATE/PROVINCE</StateProvince>
    <Refrence>Refrence</Refrence>
    <Productcode>Productcode</Productcode>
    <Contents>Contents</Contents>
    <DeclaredValue>Declared Value</DeclaredValue>
    <EditShipping>Edit Shipping</EditShipping>
    <EditorsParagraph1>Whether you're a teacher who wants to enrich the educational process or a writer who is looking
        for an efficient solution to create and publish his works, we've got you covered. Dar Al-Manhal provides
        professional editors that meet all users' needs and keep customers happy, through hundreds of rich features and
        options.
    </EditorsParagraph1>
    <EbooksEditor>E-books Editor</EbooksEditor>
    <EditorsEBookDesc1>
        <![CDATA[<b>Books Editor</b> is a perfect tool that provides the possibility to build professional online books. It allows you to add your book content and turn it into a digital form easily through a set of professional options and interactive tools. All you need is just picking images, placing text, and choosing background colors, and then you can have your electronic book live in minutes. Our online books creator is ideal for making all kinds of E-books, including children's books, photo books, curricula, textbooks and more. <b>Books Editor</b> is also optimized for every platform, so you can browse your interactive book weather you are using iOS, Android or web.]]></EditorsEBookDesc1>
    <pleaseInsertFirstName>Please enter first name</pleaseInsertFirstName>
    <pleaseInsertLastName>Please enter last name</pleaseInsertLastName>
    <pleaseChoseCountry>Please choose country</pleaseChoseCountry>
    <pleaseChoseCity>Please choose city</pleaseChoseCity>
    <PleaseInsertState>Please enter state name</PleaseInsertState>
    <PleaseInsertZip>Please enter zip code</PleaseInsertZip>
    <PleaseInsertAddress1>Please enter address 1</PleaseInsertAddress1>
    <paypalTitle>paypal</paypalTitle>
    <DarManhalPayments>Dar Al-Manhal Publisher</DarManhalPayments>
    <More1>More</More1>
    <Editor>Editor :</Editor>
    <EditorsEBookfeatures1>Easy to create professional electronic books</EditorsEBookfeatures1>
    <EditorsEBookfeatures2>Online books (anytime, anywhere, any device)</EditorsEBookfeatures2>
    <EditorsEBookfeatures3>Visual drag and drop editor</EditorsEBookfeatures3>
    <EditorsEBookfeatures4>Animate any element on page</EditorsEBookfeatures4>
    <EditorsEBookfeatures5>Adding content is fast and easy</EditorsEBookfeatures5>
    <EditorsEBookfeatures6>Enrichment (videos, images, URLs, quizzes, educational games, trace, color and more)
    </EditorsEBookfeatures6>
    <EditorsEBookfeatures7>Provides interactive tools</EditorsEBookfeatures7>
    <EditorsEBookfeatures8>No technical knowledge is required</EditorsEBookfeatures8>
    <EditorsEBookfeatures9>WYSIWYG text editor</EditorsEBookfeatures9>
    <EditorsEBookfeatures10>Build E-book using HTML5, JavaScript, CSS3</EditorsEBookfeatures10>
    <EditorsEBookfeatures11>More …</EditorsEBookfeatures11>
    <Viewer>Viewer</Viewer>
    <EditorsEBookViewer1>Offers lots of ways to customize the appearance of your interactive book</EditorsEBookViewer1>
    <EditorsEBookViewer2>Display and navigate the digital book easily</EditorsEBookViewer2>
    <EditorsEBookViewer3>Search options</EditorsEBookViewer3>
    <EditorsEBookViewer4>Add bookmark</EditorsEBookViewer4>
    <EditorsEBookViewer5>Add note</EditorsEBookViewer5>
    <EditorsEBookViewer6>Single and double page view supported</EditorsEBookViewer6>
    <EditorsEBookViewer7>Interactive pages</EditorsEBookViewer7>
    <EditorsEBookViewer8>Navigation options</EditorsEBookViewer8>
    <EditorsEBookViewer9>Thumbnails (books and pages)</EditorsEBookViewer9>
    <EditorsEBookViewer10>Social share</EditorsEBookViewer10>
    <EditorsEBookViewer11>Publish books in Arabic, English and other languages</EditorsEBookViewer11>
    <EditorsEBookViewer12>More …</EditorsEBookViewer12>
    <QuizCreator>Quiz Creator</QuizCreator>
    <EditorsQuizDesc1>
        <![CDATA[Can you really build your own highly customized quizzes without any programming? You can with the great <b>Quiz Creator!</b> The whole reason we built this online quiz editor was to give you a powerful tool to create quizzes without needing to know any programming or have any experience with coding to get started. Our quiz builder is easy to use, it contains beautiful various designs and powerful tools. It is also the simple way to make your own quizzes, right on your PC, tablet or mobile whatever it is the operating system you are using (iOS, Android or web).]]></EditorsQuizDesc1>
    <EditorsQuizfeatures1>Easy to create interactive and powerful quizzes</EditorsQuizfeatures1>
    <EditorsQuizfeatures2>Online quizzes (anytime, anywhere, any device)</EditorsQuizfeatures2>
    <EditorsQuizfeatures3>Visual drag and drop editor</EditorsQuizfeatures3>
    <EditorsQuizfeatures4>No technical knowledge is required</EditorsQuizfeatures4>
    <EditorsQuizfeatures5>Adding content is fast and easy</EditorsQuizfeatures5>
    <EditorsQuizfeatures6>Various categories to choose from</EditorsQuizfeatures6>
    <EditorsQuizfeatures7>Unlimited quizzes and questions</EditorsQuizfeatures7>
    <EditorsQuizfeatures8>Different types of interactive quizzes models</EditorsQuizfeatures8>
    <EditorsQuizfeatures9>Different question types: Multiple Choice, Fill in the Blanks, Matching, Ordering, True or
        False and more
    </EditorsQuizfeatures9>
    <EditorsQuizfeatures10>Properties edit options</EditorsQuizfeatures10>
    <EditorsQuizfeatures11>Enhanced multimedia capability</EditorsQuizfeatures11>
    <EditorsQuizfeatures12>Randomize questions and answers</EditorsQuizfeatures12>
    <EditorsQuizfeatures13>Provides you with quizzes feedbacks and reports</EditorsQuizfeatures13>
    <EditorsQuizfeatures14>Add time limits and preset test availability dates</EditorsQuizfeatures14>
    <EditorsQuizfeatures15>Create quizzes using HTML5, Java Script, CSS3</EditorsQuizfeatures15>
    <EditorsQuizfeatures16>Publish quizzes in Arabic, English and other languages</EditorsQuizfeatures16>
    <EditorsQuizfeatures17>More …</EditorsQuizfeatures17>
    <EditorsIllustratedDesc1>
        <![CDATA[<b>Stories Maker</b> is specialized with creating stunning graphic stories in professional and attractive way. Have your special story without the need to be a developer using various categories of backgrounds, characters, scenes, images, icons and sound effects, besides adding different forms of callouts, and objects that can be displayed with different movements.<b>Stories Maker</b> is also optimized for all smart devices.]]></EditorsIllustratedDesc1>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures1>Easy and attractive ways to create your own graphic online stories
    </Editorsllustratedfeatures1>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures2>Online stories (anytime, anywhere, any device)</Editorsllustratedfeatures2>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures3>Visual drag and drop editor</Editorsllustratedfeatures3>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures4>No technical knowledge is required</Editorsllustratedfeatures4>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures5>Various categories of backgrounds, scenes, images, icons and sound effects
    </Editorsllustratedfeatures5>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures6>Plenty of amazing effects and themes</Editorsllustratedfeatures6>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures7>Cute characters with variety of actions, states and moods</Editorsllustratedfeatures7>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures8>Adding content is fast and easy</Editorsllustratedfeatures8>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures9>Add characters, images, sound effects, texts, clip arts, hyperlinks
    </Editorsllustratedfeatures9>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures10>Combine images, texts, and backgrounds items into one storyline
    </Editorsllustratedfeatures10>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures11>Wave editor</Editorsllustratedfeatures11>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures12>Free drawing</Editorsllustratedfeatures12>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures13>File manager</Editorsllustratedfeatures13>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures14>Storage space</Editorsllustratedfeatures14>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures15>Edit images, apply effects, rotate and add text on images</Editorsllustratedfeatures15>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures16>Different options: fine-tune colors, fonts and transitions
    </Editorsllustratedfeatures16>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures17>Dynamic customization</Editorsllustratedfeatures17>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures18>Set time of story</Editorsllustratedfeatures18>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures19>Set transitions between story slides</Editorsllustratedfeatures19>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures20>Full screen mode</Editorsllustratedfeatures20>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures21>Publish stories in Arabic, English and other languages</Editorsllustratedfeatures21>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures22>Create stories using HTML5, JavaScript, CSS3</Editorsllustratedfeatures22>
    <Editorsllustratedfeatures23>More …</Editorsllustratedfeatures23>
    <BooksEditor>Books Editor</BooksEditor>
    <StoriesEditor>Stories Maker</StoriesEditor>
    <InteractiveStoriesBuilder>Interactive Stories Editor</InteractiveStoriesBuilder>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesDesc1>
        <![CDATA[<b>Interactive Stories Editor</b> is specialized with creating interactive graphic stories in professional and attractive way using a huge range of features, options and designs. It's that easy, just drag and drop till you like it. <b>Interactive Stories Editor</b> provides you the ability to animate any object, personalize your content using characters, and even add music of your choosing, and when you finish you can share your final product with others. <b>Interactive Stories Editor</b> is also optimized for all smart devices.]]> </EditorsInteractiveStoriesDesc1>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures1>Easy and attractive ways to create your own interactive stories
    </EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures1>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures2>Visual drag and drop editor: just drag and drop item to specific position,
        change order of each item as you need
    </EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures2>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures3>No technical knowledge is required</EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures3>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures4>Animate any object in the story</EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures4>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures5>Various categories of backgrounds, scenes, images, icons and sound effects to
        help you create cute interactive stories in the fastest way
    </EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures5>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures6>Plenty of amazing effects and themes</EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures6>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures7>Many of pre-made layout templates</EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures7>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures8>Cute characters with variety of action, state and mood
    </EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures8>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures9>Adding content is fast and easy</EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures9>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures10>Add characters, images, sound effects, texts, clip arts, hyperlinks
    </EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures10>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures11>Combine images, texts, and backgrounds items into one storyline
    </EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures11>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures12>Wave editor</EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures12>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures13>Free drawing</EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures13>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures14>File uploader with support for image, video and sound
    </EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures14>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures15>Edit images, apply effects, rotate and add text on images
    </EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures15>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures16>Different options: fine-tune colors, fonts and transitions
    </EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures16>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures17>Dynamic customization</EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures17>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures18>Set time of story</EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures18>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures19>Set transitions between story slides</EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures19>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures20>Full screen mode</EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures20>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures21>Publish interactive stories in Arabic, English and other languages
    </EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures21>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures22>Create stories using HTML5, JavaScript, CSS3
    </EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures22>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures23>More …</EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures23>
    <EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures24>More …</EditorsInteractiveStoriesfeatures24>    <!--new 12-20-2016-->
    <CompanyName>Company Name</CompanyName>
    <ShippingPrice>Shipping Price</ShippingPrice>
    <Print>Print</Print>
    <Reserve>Reserve</Reserve>
    <Areyousureshipping>Are you sure you want to close this shipping?</Areyousureshipping>
    <UploadDHL>Upload DHL</UploadDHL>
    <AuthorEn>Author En</AuthorEn>
    <AuthorAr>Author Ar</AuthorAr>
    <Completed>Completed</Completed>
    <PurchasedSuccess>Purchasing process has been completed successfully</PurchasedSuccess>
    <AreyousureReserveShipping>Are you sure Reserve Shipping</AreyousureReserveShipping>
    <Pleaseentervalidemail>Please enter a valid email address.</Pleaseentervalidemail>
    <Pleaseentervaliduser>Please enter a valid user name.</Pleaseentervaliduser>
    <Pleaseentervalidmessage>Please enter a valid message</Pleaseentervalidmessage>
    <CannotUsernameEmpty>Username cannot be empty</CannotUsernameEmpty>
    <UsernameExist>Username already exist</UsernameExist>
    <Lang>en</Lang>
    <Continue>Continue</Continue>
    <applicationparagraph1>We make apps, we love to have fun!</applicationparagraph1>
    <applicationparagraph2>
        <![CDATA[In this day and age, our smart devices are the perfect way to engage children with stories and games apps that can capture their imagination.        Here’s our section of the best stories and educational applications which are perfect for keeping children mentally active. These apps allow completing all that hard work in the classroom with after school fun that continues the learning process.        Discover our unique series of stories and educational apps that encourage children to celebrate being different. Our games applications are perfect for children of all ages to help widen their knowledge, strengthen their problem solving abilities and heighten their association skills.        In addition to, <b>Dar Al-Manhal</b> brings life to the most beloved children’s stories from its great editions through the best stories apps. Kids will love the vivid storytelling through our interactive stories apps that actually read themselves. Older children can read along with the narrator, getting a literary head start through a combination of text, images, listening and activities.        We aim to help parents find the best apps for their children. Whether they have an iPhone, iPad, or any other smart device – they will find that kids are taken to our apps like a duck to water.        Your children’s potential is endless and so are the possibilities with our awesome educational apps!]]>    </applicationparagraph2>
    <OurApplications>Our Applications</OurApplications>
    <ComingSoon>Coming Soon</ComingSoon>
    <WeeksDeleverNote>Domestic Shipping (In Jordan): Your order will be delivered within 3 - 6 Working days from order placement date
    </WeeksDeleverNote>
    <Manhalplatform>Manhal platform</Manhalplatform>
    <ManhalEbook>Manhal E-book</ManhalEbook>
    <Masa>مغامرات دينو</Masa>
    <ChoseType>Chose Type</ChoseType>
    <PleaseSelectItemType>Please select item type</PleaseSelectItemType>
    <LinkedIn>Linked In</LinkedIn>
    <Googleplus>Google plus</Googleplus>
    <Pinterest>Pinterest</Pinterest>
    <Flickr>Flickr</Flickr>
    <Vimeo>Vimeo</Vimeo>
    <Youtube>Youtube</Youtube>
    <WhatClientsSay>What Clients Say?</WhatClientsSay>
    <WhatClientsSayparagraph>"تقديراً لما قدمتموه من جهود مباركة، وإسهامات متميزة، وتعاون كريم في تنفيذ فعاليات الاحتفال
        الكرنفالي للأطفال ......... أتقدم منكم وأسرة دار المنهل بعظيم الشكر والامتنان على تبرعكم السخي بكمية كبيرة من
        إصداراتكم الخاصة بالطفل، ومثمنة ومقدرة حسن التنسيق والتواصل والمتابعة"
    </WhatClientsSayparagraph>
    <GameEditorDesc>A great tool that is specialized with creating interactive graphic stories</GameEditorDesc>
    <Subscribe>Subscribe</Subscribe>
    <CartIsEmpty>Cart is empty</CartIsEmpty>
    <PleaseSelectItems>Please select items before check out</PleaseSelectItems>
    <AllBooks>All Books</AllBooks>
    <WhatClientsSayparagraph2>وزيرة الثقافة</WhatClientsSayparagraph2>
    <WhatClientsSayparagraph3>الدكتورة لانا مامكغ</WhatClientsSayparagraph3>
    <WhatClientsSayparagraph4>27/05/2015</WhatClientsSayparagraph4>
    <Views>Views</Views>
    <Back>Back</Back>
    <BillingAddress>Billing Address</BillingAddress>
    <ShippingAddress>Shipping Address</ShippingAddress>
    <WeeksDeleverNote2>Cargo Shipping (Outside Jordan): Your order will be delivered within 4 - 9 working days from order placement date
    </WeeksDeleverNote2>
    <MacMilan>Macmillan</MacMilan>
    <PLeaseWriteComment>Please write comment</PLeaseWriteComment>
    <ForgetPasswordTitle>Forgotten Password Reset</ForgetPasswordTitle>
    <ExpierResetLink>This password reset link has expired. Each reset link could only be used once.</ExpierResetLink>
    <passwordResetSuccess>Success</passwordResetSuccess>
    <passwordResetSuccess>Reset Successfully</passwordResetSuccess>
    <EditPage>Edit Page</EditPage>
    <PleaseInsertText>Please enter text</PleaseInsertText>
    <PleaseEnterEmailAddress>E-mail cannot be empty</PleaseEnterEmailAddress>
    <RequiredField>Required Field</RequiredField>
    <partnersinlearning>Partners in learning</partnersinlearning>
    <AllApplication>All Applications</AllApplication>
    <PLeaseWriteComment>PLease write comment</PLeaseWriteComment>
    <ForgetPasswordTitle>Forgotten password reset</ForgetPasswordTitle>
    <PasswordReset>Password Reset</PasswordReset>
    <ExpierResetLink>This password reset link has expired. each link may only be used once</ExpierResetLink>
    <ResetPassword>Reset Password</ResetPassword>
    <passwordResetSuccess>You have been reset your password successfully</passwordResetSuccess>
    <EducationalInquiries>Educational Inquiries</EducationalInquiries>
    <SignInToAddPost>Sign in here to add post</SignInToAddPost>
    <writepost>Write a post</writepost>
    <Inquiry>Inquiry</Inquiry>
    <mediaTitle>Media Title</mediaTitle>
    <Addmedia>Add Media</Addmedia>
    <mediaInfo>Media Info</mediaInfo>
    <media>Media</media>
    <Youwillnotbeabletorecoverthismedia>Are you sure you want to delete this page?</Youwillnotbeabletorecoverthismedia>
    <mediahasbeendeleted>Deleted Successfully</mediahasbeendeleted>
    <arabictitle>Arabic Title</arabictitle>
    <englishtitle>English Title</englishtitle>
    <image_larg>Image Large</image_larg>
    <Filemedia>File Media</Filemedia>
    <PleaseInsertTitle_ar>Please insert Arabic title</PleaseInsertTitle_ar>
    <PleaseInsertTitle_en>Please insert English title</PleaseInsertTitle_en>
    <worksheets>Worksheets</worksheets>
    <coloringsheets>coloring</coloringsheets>
    <lessons>Lessons</lessons>
    <sound>sound</sound>
    <video>video</video>
    <teachersbook>Teacher's book</teachersbook>
    <quize>Quizzes</quize>
    <CD>CD</CD>
    <flash>Flash</flash>
    <flashcard>Flash card</flashcard>
    <lectures>lectures</lectures>
    <worksheetinteractive>worksheet interactive</worksheetinteractive>
    <educationtools>education tools</educationtools>
    <TeachersGuide>Teacher's Guide</TeachersGuide>
    <ministryapprovals>Ministry Approvals</ministryapprovals>
    <curriculumplans>curriculum Plans</curriculumplans>
    <Education>Education</Education>
    <FirstPage>First Page</FirstPage>
    <LastPage>Last Page</LastPage>
    <PaintPicture>Paint Pictures</PaintPicture>
    <GamesPictures>Games Pictures</GamesPictures>
    <ShortDesc>Short Description</ShortDesc>
    <Free>Free</Free>
    <New>New</New>
    <favpurch>Filtering</favpurch>
    <play>Play</play>
    <KidsAdvice>Kid's Advice</KidsAdvice>
    <KidsAdviceSound>Kid's Advice Sound</KidsAdviceSound>
    <Worksheet>Worksheet</Worksheet>
    <OnlineWorksheet>Online Worksheet</OnlineWorksheet>
    <InteractiveWorksheet>Interactive Worksheet</InteractiveWorksheet>
    <Play>Play</Play>
    <Video>Video</Video>
    <OnlineVideo>Online Video</OnlineVideo>
    <InteractiveVideo>Interactive Video</InteractiveVideo>
    <Audio>Audio</Audio>
    <audio>Audio</audio>
    <OnlineAudio>Online Audio</OnlineAudio>
    <InteractiveAudio>Interactive Audio</InteractiveAudio>
    <worksheetsDesc>The diversifying the means and methods</worksheetsDesc>
    <InteractiveWorksheets>Interactive Worksheets</InteractiveWorksheets>
    <InteractiveWorksheetsDesc>Dar Al Manhal allows students and teachers</InteractiveWorksheetsDesc>
    <EducationalTools>Educational Tools</EducationalTools>
    <EducationalToolsDesc>We offer a range of educational and useful tools that enable the student to get educational
        materials in an innovative way.
    </EducationalToolsDesc>
    <IllustrativeLessons>Illustrative Lessons</IllustrativeLessons>
    <IllustrativeLessonsDesc>We support the educational process through a series of illustrative lessons and courses
        that serve all grades.
    </IllustrativeLessonsDesc>
    <soundDesc>We are in Dar Manhal care about the integration</soundDesc>
    <EducationalGamesDesc2>We provide wonderful educational games which develop children's thinking skills and enhance
        their abilities.
    </EducationalGamesDesc2>
    <Quizzes>Quizzes</Quizzes>
    <QuizzesDesc>Dar Al Manhal has always sought to provide the utmost</QuizzesDesc>
    <galleriesDetailsDescription>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers Galleries,Galleries</galleriesDetailsDescription>
    <galleriesDetailsKeywords>Dar Al-Manhal Publishers galleries,galleries</galleriesDetailsKeywords>
    <galleriesDetailsTitle>Galleries</galleriesDetailsTitle>
    <videoDetailsDescription>video Description</videoDetailsDescription>
    <Photos>Photos</Photos>
    <video>video</video>
    <Online>Online</Online>
    <CurriculaRequirements>Curricula Requirements</CurriculaRequirements>
    <CurriculaRequirementsDesc>The teacher's guides provide new ways and ideas</CurriculaRequirementsDesc>
    <SoundText>Higlighted Text</SoundText>
    <AddGame>Add Game</AddGame>
    <GameType>Game Type</GameType>
    <discussions>Discussions</discussions>
    <filter>Filtering</filter>
    <AddPost>Add Qustion</AddPost>
    <AddPostQustion>Your Question</AddPostQustion>
    <Educationalinquiries>Educational inquiries</Educationalinquiries>
    <OpenDiscussions>Open Discussions</OpenDiscussions>
    <CloseDiscussions>Closed Discussions</CloseDiscussions>
    <postme>My Questions</postme>
    <AllDiscussions>All</AllDiscussions>
    <posthidden>Hidden Discussions</posthidden>
    <notificationDiscussions>Notifications</notificationDiscussions>
    <PostyourQuestion>Post your Question</PostyourQuestion>
    <Discussions>Discussions</Discussions>
    <Raply>Raply</Raply>
    <yourComment>Post your Question</yourComment>
    <Hide>Hide</Hide>
    <CLOSED>Close</CLOSED>
    <UNCLOSED>Unclose</UNCLOSED>
    <UnHide>Unhide</UnHide>
    <Areyousureyouwanttodeletethisquestion>Are you sure you want to delete this question?
    </Areyousureyouwanttodeletethisquestion>
    <Areyousureyouwanttoupdatethisquestion>Are you sure you want to update this text?
    </Areyousureyouwanttoupdatethisquestion>
    <Youhavenewmodification>You have new notification</Youhavenewmodification>
    <cocieesMessage>Cookies are disabled on your browser, please enable them to use full functions in our website.
    </cocieesMessage>
    <ColoringWorksheet>Coloring Worksheet</ColoringWorksheet>
    <ColoringWorksheetDesc>Dar Al Manhal is concerned with the young kids' education</ColoringWorksheetDesc>
    <DarAlmanhalStories>Dar Al-manhal Stories</DarAlmanhalStories>
    <DarAlmanhalBooks>Dar Al-manhal Books</DarAlmanhalBooks>
    <Approvals>Approvals</Approvals>
    <Lessonplans>Lesson plans</Lessonplans>
    <Booksh1>Books</Booksh1>
    <Story1>Stories</Story1>
    <Audio1>Audio</Audio1>
    <Sounds1>Sounds</Sounds1>
    <Videos1>Videos</Videos1>
    <Worksheets1>Worksheets</Worksheets1>
    <ApprovalsoftheMinistryofEducation>Ministry of Education Approvals</ApprovalsoftheMinistryofEducation>
    <StudyPlans>Curricula Plans</StudyPlans>
    <Teachersbook>Teacher's Guide</Teachersbook>
    <Programs>Educational Programs</Programs>
    <Related>Related</Related>
    <SEODescriptionEn>SEO En</SEODescriptionEn>
    <SEODescriptionAr>SEO Ar</SEODescriptionAr>
    <ReturnPolicy>Return Policy</ReturnPolicy>
    <ReturnsandExchanges>Returns and Exchanges</ReturnsandExchanges>
    <ChangedyourMind>Changed your Mind?</ChangedyourMind>
    <Wheniscancelingnotpossible>When is “canceling” not possible?</Wheniscancelingnotpossible>
    <ReturnPolicy1>If something isn’t right or you just change your mind, we are happy to accept a return or cancel the
        order. Take a moment to read through our policy, and then head to the instructions below.
    </ReturnPolicy1>
    <ReturnPolicy2>If you change your mind about the products you have ordered, and want to cancel the order, you can
        cancel it within 60 minutes of placing the order.
    </ReturnPolicy2>
    <ReturnPolicy3>There are a few certain scenarios where it is difficult for us to support cancels:</ReturnPolicy3>
    <ReturnPolicyone>1. If the order is software copy the, it can’t be canceled.</ReturnPolicyone>
    <ReturnPolicytow>2. Once the order gets out of the warehouse, it can’t be canceled.</ReturnPolicytow>
    <CustomerName>Customer Name</CustomerName>
    <billnumber>Invoice Number</billnumber>
    <ShippingNumber>Shipping Number</ShippingNumber>
    <Pub>Pub</Pub>
    <disc>Disc %</disc>
    <VAT>VAT</VAT>
    <Netval>Net Value</Netval>
    <orders>My Orders</orders>
    <ordernum>Order #</ordernum>
    <Created>Created</Created>
    <Recipient>Recipient</Recipient>
    <Shipment>Shipment #</Shipment>
    <Total>Total</Total>
    <BooksT>Books</BooksT>
    <StoriesT>Stories</StoriesT>
    <Shiptothesameaddress>Ship to the same address</Shiptothesameaddress>
    <Done>Done</Done>
    <ChooseProducts>Choose Products</ChooseProducts>
    <CreditCards>Credit Cards (visa,master card)</CreditCards>
    <CardHolderName>Card Holder's Name</CardHolderName>
    <CardNumber>Card Number</CardNumber>
    <ExpDate>Exp . Date</ExpDate>
    <CVCNumber>Security Code</CVCNumber>
    <Paypal>Paypal</Paypal>
    <Sadad>Sadad</Sadad>
    <Installments>Installments</Installments>
    <NAPS>NAPS</NAPS>
    <Extrachargingonyourinvoice>(Extra charging)</Extrachargingonyourinvoice>
    <CachOnDeliveryCost>Cach On Delivery Cost</CachOnDeliveryCost>
    <SafeSecure><![CDATA[Safe & Secure]]> </SafeSecure>
    <SafeSecureP>The transaction is safe and secured, using the latest encryption technologies</SafeSecureP>
    <Invoice>Invoice</Invoice>
    <Tel>Phone</Tel>
    <Mob>Mobile</Mob>
    <Billto>Bill to</Billto>
    <Shipto>Ship to</Shipto>
    <FullNameTooShort>Full name is too short</FullNameTooShort>
    <WrongInfo>Wrong Informations</WrongInfo>
    <PleaseInsertPost>Please input postal code</PleaseInsertPost>
    <requiedinformation>Required information</requiedinformation>
    <opening>Opening :</opening>
    <Headoffice>Head office</Headoffice>
    <Ammanalabdali>Jordan - Amman - al abdali</Ammanalabdali>
    <Showroom1>Showroom 1</Showroom1>
    <Showroom2>Showroom 2</Showroom2>
    <Elearningoffice><![CDATA[Website support & elearning]]></Elearningoffice>
    <AmmanKhalda>Jordan - Amman -Khalda</AmmanKhalda>
    <Showroom1pos>Al-Daddu Complex, King Al Hussein Str.</Showroom1pos>
    <Showroom2pos>Opposite to Sadeen Hotel, near Arab Bank traffic lights, Wasfi al-tal Str.</Showroom2pos>
    <Elearningofficepos>Areej Commercial Complex, near Al-Assaf traffic lights, Wasfi al-tal Str.</Elearningofficepos>
    <workingtimeA>8:00 AM - 4:30 PM ( Sun - Thurs)</workingtimeA>
    <workingtimeB>9:00 AM - 5:30 PM ( Sat - Thurs) </workingtimeB>
    <workingtimeC>8:00 AM - 5:00 PM ( Sun - Thurs)</workingtimeC>
    <workingtimeD>9:00 AM - 8:00 PM ( Sat - Thurs)  - 4:00 PM - 8:00 PM (Fri)</workingtimeD>
    <!--<workingtimeA>7:30 AM - 5:00 PM ( Sun - Thurs)</workingtimeA>-->
    <!--<workingtimeB>9:00 AM - 6:30 PM ( Sat - Thurs)</workingtimeB>-->
    <!--<workingtimeC>8:00 AM - 5:30 PM ( Sun - Thurs)</workingtimeC>-->
    <!--<workingtimeD>9:00 AM - 10:00 PM ( Sat - Thurs) - 4:00 PM - 10:00 PM (Fri)</workingtimeD>-->
    <PKTnumber>PKTnumber</PKTnumber>
    <PKTinfo>PKT information</PKTinfo>
    <NumberOfCartons>Number of cartons</NumberOfCartons>
    <Totalweight>Total Weight</Totalweight>
    <Shippingaddress>Shipping Address</Shippingaddress>
    <shipingmethod>Shiping Method</shipingmethod>
    <stock>Stock</stock>
    <Countcartons>carton Number</Countcartons>
    <weightcartons>Carton Weight</weightcartons>
    <Addproduct>Add Product</Addproduct>
    <Addcartons>Add New carton</Addcartons>
    <Report>Report</Report>
    <Closes>Close</Closes>
    <onlinebookEditor>Online Book Editor</onlinebookEditor>
    <onlineInteractiveStoriesBuilder>Online Interactive Stories Editor</onlineInteractiveStoriesBuilder>
    <OnlineQuizCreator>Online Quiz Creator</OnlineQuizCreator>
    <OnlineStoriesEditor>Online Stories Editor</OnlineStoriesEditor>
    <NoItems>Select Items</NoItems>
    <msgNoItems>Your cart is empty , please select Items</msgNoItems>
    <InvalidCreditCard>Please, enter valid credit card number</InvalidCreditCard>
    <booksinfo>books_info</booksinfo>
    <daralmanhalbooksinformations>Dar Al Manhal Books Information</daralmanhalbooksinformations>
    <BookInformationDesc1>
        <![CDATA[ <p class="inner-paragraph">Dar Al-Manhal makes your kid a little reader through its cultural programmes, educational content, children's books (curricula), preschool books and high-level projects that enrich his/her knowledge and expand his/her horizons.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">It also seeks to help developing kids through a wide range of Arabic books, English books, and curricula: Math Thinking, نادي الحاسوب, سلسلة العلوم الإسلامية, نادي العربية, ..., as well as kindergarten books: نادي الرياضيات, هيا إلى العربية, براعم الإسلام, واحة العلوم, English Club, ..., which are written by our experts to achieve the academic and professional goals.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">All you need to do is]]></BookInformationDesc1>
    <BookInformationDesc2>
        <![CDATA[ browse Dar Al-Manhal books</a> to find the right books for kids.</p>]]></BookInformationDesc2>
    <electronicbooksinfo>electronic-books-info</electronicbooksinfo>
    <daralmanhalelectronicbooksinformations>Dar Al Manhal Electronic Books Information
    </daralmanhalelectronicbooksinformations>
    <electronicbooksinfoDesc1>
        <![CDATA[<p class="inner-paragraph">Dar Al-Manhal believes in the importance of providing professional electronic services (eservices) to assist in time use, and provide an amazing reading books experience through the Internet, through rich e-library that offers online books to read for kids, opens the window of e-learning for all students, and provides the best tools that increase the effectiveness of reading, studying and learning.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">Dar Al-Manhal website provides all curricula and children's books online, whether they are Arabic books or English books in professional e-books (eform), which supports distance learning making it available to students from all school levels. The user can browse any of the e-books immediately online on a mobile phone or tablet or any electronic device at ease. Besides, Dar Al-Manhal website enables users to buy books online, all from Dar Al-Manhal editions.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">We also provide an easy way to create e-books in a professional manner without having any per-knowledge of programming; through effective tools and options offered by the rapid e-books editor available on the Internet.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">]]></electronicbooksinfoDesc1>
    <electronicbooksinfoDesc2><![CDATA[Browse e-books offered from Dar Al-Manhal.</a></p>]]></electronicbooksinfoDesc2>
    <interactivebooksinfo>electronic-books-info</interactivebooksinfo>
    <daralmanhainteractivebooksinformations>Dar Al Manhal Interactive Books Information
    </daralmanhainteractivebooksinformations>
    <interactivebooksinfoDesc1>
        <![CDATA[<p class="inner-paragraph">Dar Al-Manhal seeks to provide interactive books for kids to make learning more fun and effective. Through these interactive books, we cover all kids-related subjects, and grades to enrich the kids reading experience by using the innovative interaction which makes our little readers happy.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">These new kids’ interactive books offered by Dar Al-Manhal contain exercises, games, texts, interactive images, and it is considered a great way for interactive learning, which supports teaching kids with the latest e-learning and interactive techniques.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">Certainly, kids will want to touch things to see what will happen next! In each page of the interactive book, a lot of surprises await them, like sound effects, the change in colours, music, animations and other forms of entertainment.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">]]></interactivebooksinfoDesc1>
    <interactivebooksinfoDesc2>
        <![CDATA[Browse interactive books offered from Dar Al-Manhal.</a></p>]]></interactivebooksinfoDesc2>
    <TheCVVtext>Security Code (CVV Number) on VISA® or MasterCard® is a 3 digit number.</TheCVVtext>
    <storiesinfo>stories-info</storiesinfo>
    <daralmanhalstoriesinformations>Dar Al Manhal Stories Information</daralmanhalstoriesinformations>
    <storiesinfoDesc1>
        <![CDATA[ <p class="inner-paragraph">Reading is a world of fun and knowledge enriching, so we offer in Dar Al-Manhal a group of comprehensive and distinctive children stories in Arabic, English and even in French, in order to instil the love of reading in the hearts of children and help them to acquire sound habits and values.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">Dar Al-Manhal also provides bags of short stories for kids divided into levels according to children age group, including selected short stories from Dar Al-Manhal's stories.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">]]></storiesinfoDesc1>
    <storiesinfoDesc2><![CDATA[Browse stories offered from Dar Al-Manhal.</a></p>]]></storiesinfoDesc2>
    <electronicstoriesinfo>electronic-stories-info</electronicstoriesinfo>
    <daralmanhalelectronicstoriesinformations>Dar Al Manhal Electronic Stories Information
    </daralmanhalelectronicstoriesinformations>
    <electronicstoriesinfoDesc1>
        <![CDATA[<p class="inner-paragraph">What is the best than using technology in education and instilling the love of reading stories in the hearts of children? E-stories are the best entertaining option to achieve this.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">We aim through Dar Al-Manhal's website to provide a huge e-library of kid's story, which includes a large collection of online stories and children's books to read illustrated in Arabic language and English language that satisfy their desire in reading stories. Dar Al-Manhal provides these amazing e-stories, which combines images, graphics, texts, sounds, sound effects, sound tracks, to attract the kid's attention to the e-story till the end. Besides, Dar Al-Manhal website enables users to buy kids stories online, all from Dar Al-Manhal editions.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">]]></electronicstoriesinfoDesc1>
    <electronicstoriesinfoDesc2>
        <![CDATA[Browse e-stories offered from Dar Al-Manhal.</a></p>]]></electronicstoriesinfoDesc2>
    <Purchasedhasbeendonesuccessfully>Purchased has been done successfully</Purchasedhasbeendonesuccessfully>
    <Toviewordersclickon>To view orders, click on</Toviewordersclickon>
    <Toviewpurchasedproductsclickon>To view purchased products, click on</Toviewpurchasedproductsclickon>
    <ordersA>Orders</ordersA>
    <interactivestoriesinfo>interactives-stories-info</interactivestoriesinfo>
    <daralmanhainteractivestoriesinformations>Dar Al Manhal Interactive Stories Information
    </daralmanhainteractivestoriesinformations>
    <interactivestoriesinfoDesc1>
        <![CDATA[<p class="inner-paragraph">Children's stories are their window for the outside world that is so full of exciting adventures. With the interactive stories that are offered by Dar Al-Manhal, your child will not be need to read kids’ story books in the traditional way anymore, as he can share us the fun of browsing, and interacting with them at any time.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">Dar Al-Manhal offers a large collection of short stories for kids in an amazing electronic and interactive way which adding the fun factor, with games, exercises, texts, images, sound effects, colours, music, animations and other forms of entertainment.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">Also, interactive stories for kids from Dar Al-Manhal, opens e-learning portal for them, including providing fun and useful options of interactive learning.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">For more effectiveness and ease of use, Dar Al-Manhal provides multi-platform interactive stories; which are supported by all operating systems (IOS, Android and Windows).</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">]]></interactivestoriesinfoDesc1>
    <interactivestoriesinfoDesc2>
        <![CDATA[Browse interactive stories offered from Dar Al-Manhal.</a></p>]]></interactivestoriesinfoDesc2>
    <educationalgamesinfo>educational-games-info</educationalgamesinfo>
    <daralmanhaeducationalgamesinformations>Dar Al Manhal Educational Games Information
    </daralmanhaeducationalgamesinformations>
    <educationaltoolsinfoDesc1>
        <![CDATA[ <p class="inner-paragraph">In Dar Al-Manhal, we expand our circle constantly to reflect the needs of education in the present time, and we help to discover and develop the capabilities of modern children in creative ways through a wide range of educational tools that contribute to develop their mental and linguistic skills.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">Our educational tools include fast display cards (flashcards), audio publications, and enriching educational posters (posters), and amazing stickers. The audio publications are considered an important achievement aims to teach children listening skills that precedes teaching reading and teaching writing, and developing their speech. They include beautiful children stories and distinctive songs performed by the amazing childish voices within educational framework. We also provide wonderful educational posters (posters) to create a distinctive learning environment supported by means of visual illustration for children, along with a variety of stickers containing pictures of beautiful words to boost the children's performance. It presents educational topics, like numbers, Arabic language, English language, letters and words, along with CDs in Arabic and English languages which have been designed to be easily used by children.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">]]></educationaltoolsinfoDesc1>
    <educationaltoolsinfoDesc2>
        <![CDATA[Browse educational tools offered from Dar Al-Manhal.</a></p>]]></educationaltoolsinfoDesc2>
    <educationaltoolsinfo>educational-tools-info</educationaltoolsinfo>
    <daralmanhaeducationaltoolsinformations>Dar Al Manhal Educational Tools Information
    </daralmanhaeducationaltoolsinformations>
    <educationalgamesinfoDesc1>
        <![CDATA[ <p class="inner-paragraph">Which is more fun: homework or educational games? Do you want to access educational games for kids that enable you to build their skills and teach them at the same time? Then, you are in the right place.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">We are in Dar Al-Manhal believe that e-learning through educational games is an effective way to teach children and students, and develop the required skills in the curriculum; therefore, we provide enjoyable and meaningful online games for children in pre-kindergarten, elementary, as well as secondary stages. Through animations and colourful music that add vital element to the learning games and through different platforms, (iPhone, tablet, iPad, and PC… etc, you can learn at home and in any other place mathematic basics, reading, languages, science and so on.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">We provide the students a virtual world, which enables them experience with us the fun of interactive learning at any time, in any place, instead of the boring traditional lessons!!</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">]]></educationalgamesinfoDesc1>
    <educationalgamesinfoDesc2>
        <![CDATA[ Browse educational games offered from Dar Al-Manhal.</a></p>]]></educationalgamesinfoDesc2>
    <applicationinfo>application-info</applicationinfo>
    <daralmanhaapplicationinformations>Dar Al Manhal Application Information</daralmanhaapplicationinformations>
    <applicationinfoDesc1>
        <![CDATA[<p class="inner-paragraph">There is no doubt that modern technology plays an important role in our daily lives, especially, regarding developing the skills and abilities of our children. But, how can children achieve the greatest benefit from this technological development in an easy and fun way? And how it helps them to develop their skills and acquire new skills?</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">Dar Al-Manhal aspires to be a reference to children's learning for all age groups over the internet and through providing children with the most distinctive and the most attractive e-learning techniques, which are kids applications of interactive stories and exciting educational games.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">Dar Al-Manhal produces, through passion and creativity, the best kids’ applications to serve the educational process and the development of children's skills, and adds the fun element in teaching children through interactive education, including games, and amazing interactive stories supported with graphics, sound effects, and the possibility of changing the colours, music, animations and other forms of entertainment.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">These applications from Dar Al-Manhal are characterized by having multi-platforms; which are supported by all operating systems (IOS, Android and the internet).</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">]]></applicationinfoDesc1>
    <applicationinfoDesc2><![CDATA[Browse applications offered from Dar Al-Manhal.</a></p>]]></applicationinfoDesc2>
    <childrensfurnitureinfo>childrens-furniture-info</childrensfurnitureinfo>
    <daralmanhchildrensfurnitureinformations>Dar Al Manhal Children's Furniture Information
    </daralmanhchildrensfurnitureinformations>
    <childrensfurnitureinfoDesc1>
        <![CDATA[<p class="inner-paragraph">Both playing environment and learning environment leave a significant impact on children. And because it seeks to be a leader in providing the best for children and meet all their needs; Dar Al-Manhal, the exclusive agent in Jordan for  (EduFun), the global specialized company in children's furniture and kindergarten supplies, provides a wide range of children's furniture, kindergarten equipments, school equipments; chairs, tables, cabinets, wall libraries, playing areas, playing screens, panels, carpets ..., in practical suitable and convenient designs, to achieve the requirements of children in early stages.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">]]></childrensfurnitureinfoDesc1>
    <childrensfurnitureinfoDesc2>
        <![CDATA[ Browse children's furniture offered from Dar Al-Manhal.</a></p>]]></childrensfurnitureinfoDesc2>
    <worksheetsinfo>worksheets-info</worksheetsinfo>
    <daralmanhworksheetsinfoinformations>Dar Al Manhal Worksheets Information</daralmanhworksheetsinfoinformations>
    <worksheetsinfoDesc1>
        <![CDATA[ <p class="inner-paragraph">The variety of teaching means and methods chosen by the teacher is necessary for effective learning process, in which students will reach their best levels within a group of learners</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">Therefore; Dar Al-Manhal offers a huge group of wonderful educational worksheets for students, which is one of the most successful methods of teaching, because of their impact in treating learning disabilities among students, and for achieving educational skills, enhancing and strengthening the learning and development of talented and gifted students' abilities.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">Our educational worksheets are prepared in a systematic and orderly manner; as for each worksheet, there is a name, title and it ranges in levels to serve students in all cultural levels and age groups. The worksheets include mathematics, science, the Arabic language, English language and other school materials. Worksheets also include entertaining coloring pages</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">]]></worksheetsinfoDesc1>
    <worksheetsinfoDesc2>
        <![CDATA[ Browse educational worksheets offered from Dar Al-Manhal.</a></p>]]></worksheetsinfoDesc2>
    <interactiveworksheetsinfo>interactive-worksheets-info</interactiveworksheetsinfo>
    <daralmanhinteractiveworksheetsinfoinformations>Dar Al Manhal Interactive Worksheets Information
    </daralmanhinteractiveworksheetsinfoinformations>
    <interactiveworksheetsinfoDesc1>
        <![CDATA[<p class="inner-paragraph">Dar Al-Manhal allows students and teachers to the possibility of experiencing interactive learning through the varied and entertaining interactive worksheets which are available on Dar Al-Manhal platform.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">The interactive worksheets cover all subjects, and kids' school stages, and enrich the learning process, using innovative interaction. The worksheets also include entertaining coloring pages, with printing feature.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">]]></interactiveworksheetsinfoDesc1>
    <interactiveworksheetsinfoDesc2>
        <![CDATA[Browse interactive worksheets offered from Dar Al-Manhal.</a></p>]]></interactiveworksheetsinfoDesc2>
    <soundinfo>sound-info</soundinfo>
    <daralmanhsoundinfoinformations>Dar Al Manhal Sound Information</daralmanhsoundinfoinformations>
    <soundinfoDesc1>
        <![CDATA[ <p class="inner-paragraph">We are in Dar Al-Manhal care about the integration of the educational process by providing all possible media to enrich it, including the audios associated with our products; songs, CDs accompanying the educational books, and other audio versions.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">]]></soundinfoDesc1>
    <soundinfoDesc2>
        <![CDATA[Dar Al-Manhal provides the educational audio versions on its platform.</a></p> ]]></soundinfoDesc2>
    <videoinfo>video-info</videoinfo>
    <daralmanhvideoinfoinformations>Dar Al Manhal Video Information</daralmanhvideoinfoinformations>
    <videoinfoDesc1>
        <![CDATA[ <p class="inner-paragraph">In the framework of its endeavour to supply teaching kids with the latest products that aid them in their educational journey, Dar Al-Manhal provides one of the effective multimedia means that is educational videos. </p> <p class="inner-paragraph">The educational videos for kids provided by Dar Al-Manhal characterized by being a simple and easy learning means to use, which range in difficulty depending on the kid’s age, and present useful supporting educational materials that support school curricula.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">]]></videoinfoDesc1>
    <videoinfoDesc2><![CDATA[Browse educational videos offered from Dar Al-Manhal.</a></p>]]></videoinfoDesc2>
    <teachersguidesinfo>teachers-guides-info</teachersguidesinfo>
    <daralmanhteachersguidesinfoinformations>Dar Al Manhal Teachers Guide's Information
    </daralmanhteachersguidesinfoinformations>
    <teachersguidesinfoDesc1>
        <![CDATA[ <p class="inner-paragraph">The teacher's guides provide new ways and ideas to help the teachers in their innovative work and facilitate the process of teaching the curriculum to present the curriculum in the best possible way.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">Therefore; Dar Al-Manhal took notice that each curriculum should be accompanied with a Teacher's Guide to help him/her improve their professional performance being the most effective and influential element in the educational process and it is the responsibility of the new generation.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">]]></teachersguidesinfoDesc1>
    <teachersguidesinfoDesc2>
        <![CDATA[Dar Al-Manhal provides a platform for the teacher's guides</a> in its curricula, with the possibility of uploading them.</p>]]></teachersguidesinfoDesc2>
    <exercisesinfo>exercises-info</exercisesinfo>
    <daralmanhcurriexercisesinfoinformations>Dar Al Manhal Exercises Information
    </daralmanhcurriexercisesinfoinformations>
    <exercisesinfoDesc1>
        <![CDATA[ <p class="inner-paragraph">Dar Al-Manhal has always sought to provide the utmost help and support to parents and children through various, and constructive teaching aids, including supporting exercises in the curricula.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">Dar Al-Manhal provides its users with a set of exercises that support and enrich the learning process and allow children to exercise their preferred hobby which is using electronic devices. ]]></exercisesinfoDesc1>
    <exercisesinfoDesc2>
        <![CDATA[Dar Al-Manhal provides these exercises for students on its platform.</a></p>]]></exercisesinfoDesc2>
    <coloringworksheetinfo>coloring-worksheet-info</coloringworksheetinfo>
    <daralmanhcoloringworksheetinfoinformations>Dar Al Manhal Coloring Worksheet Information
    </daralmanhcoloringworksheetinfoinformations>
    <coloringworksheetinfoDesc1>
        <![CDATA[ <p class="inner-paragraph">Dar Al-Manhal is concerned with the young kids' education and it discovers their artistic energy, and enhances their abilities through colouring worksheets.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">Our Printable Colouring worksheets include entertaining images and graphics in different subjects that enable the kids drawing and colouring in a very easy way.</p> <p class="inner-paragraph">]]></coloringworksheetinfoDesc1>
    <coloringworksheetinfoDesc2>
        <![CDATA[Browse coloring worksheets offered from Dar Al-Manhal.</a></p> ]]></coloringworksheetinfoDesc2>
    <ElectronicStories>Electronic Stories</ElectronicStories>
    <InvalidSecurityCode>Invalid security code</InvalidSecurityCode>
    <PKT>Packet</PKT>
    <Printpickandpackorder>Print Pick and Pack Order</Printpickandpackorder>
    <pickandpackorder>Pick and Pack Order</pickandpackorder>
    <INVNumber>INV Number</INVNumber>
    <EmployeeName>Employee's Name</EmployeeName>
    <Cartons>Cartons</Cartons>
    <AreyousureDeleteprodect>Are you sure you want delete this prodect</AreyousureDeleteprodect>
    <Areyousureyouwantaddcarton>Are you sure you want add carton</Areyousureyouwantaddcarton>
    <PaymentMethods>Payment Methods</PaymentMethods>
    <Deliveryisavailableinallcountriesoftheworld>Worldwide delivery services
    </Deliveryisavailableinallcountriesoftheworld>
    <EDUCATIONALADVISOR>Educational Advisor</EDUCATIONALADVISOR>
    <Askouredcationaladvisornow>Ask our educational advisor now</Askouredcationaladvisornow>
    <Ask>Ask</Ask>
    <Signinhere>Sign in here</Signinhere>
    <Signupnow>Sign up now</Signupnow>
    <PleaseSaveErrorNumToSolve>Please save the error number to solve and foloow up this problem
    </PleaseSaveErrorNumToSolve>
    <Sounds>Sounds</Sounds>
    <Videos>Videos</Videos>
    <TeachersGuides>Teacher's Guides</TeachersGuides>
    <Applicationdesc1>There is no doubt that modern technology</Applicationdesc1>
    <videoDesc>In the framework of its endeavour to supply teaching kids</videoDesc>
    <UPrice>U.Price</UPrice>
    <DarAlmanhalWorksheet>Dar Al-manhal WorkSheets</DarAlmanhalWorksheet>
    <DarAlmanhalWorksheet>Dar Al-manhal WorkSheets</DarAlmanhalWorksheet>
    <WorksheetsT>WorkSheets</WorksheetsT>
    <InteractiveWorksheetsT>Interactive WorkSheets</InteractiveWorksheetsT>
    <DarAlmanhalAudio>Dar Al-manhal Audios</DarAlmanhalAudio>
    <AudiosT>Audios</AudiosT>
    <DarAlmanhalVideo>Dar Al-manhal Video</DarAlmanhalVideo>
    <VideoT>Video</VideoT>
    <worksheetsDescription>Contains educational worksheets in mathematics, science, Arabic Language, English Language,
        and other curricula. Worksheets also are printable.
    </worksheetsDescription>
    <worksheetsDescriptionT1>**** worksheets interested in teaching **** for kids, offered **** lessons simply and
        supported by practical activities and coloring pages.
    </worksheetsDescriptionT1>
    <worksheetsDescriptionT2>**** worksheets teach **** lessons for kids supported by activities and exercises.
        Worksheets include variety topics like ---- that teach ----.
    </worksheetsDescriptionT2>
    <worksheetsDescriptionT3>Contains worksheets in mathematics, science, Arabic Language and other curricula.
        Worksheets include many topics like: ----; aims to teach ----.
    </worksheetsDescriptionT3>
    <worksheetKeywords>Worksheets,Electronic Worksheets,Interactive Worksheets,Online Worksheets,Educational
        Worksheets,kids Worksheets,buy worksheets online
    </worksheetKeywords>
    <audioDescription>Contains educational audios in math, science, Arabic language, English language, and other
        curricula. Audios are offered on Dar Al Manhal platform.
    </audioDescription>
    <audioDescriptionT1>Audios for **** interested in teaching **** for kids simply, supported educational materials
        that support school curricula.
    </audioDescriptionT1>
    <audioDescriptionT2>Audios for **** teach **** lessons for kids simply. Audios offers materials support curricula
        like ----.
    </audioDescriptionT2>
    <audioDescriptionT3>Contains audios in mathematics, science, Arabic Language and other curricula. Audios include
        many topics like ----.
    </audioDescriptionT3>
    <audioKeywords>Audios,Electronic Audios,Interactive Audios,Online Audios,Educational Audios,kids Audios,buy audios
        online
    </audioKeywords>
    <videoDescription>Contains educational videos in math, science, Arabic Language, English Language, and other
        curricula. videos are offered on Dar Al Manhal platform.
    </videoDescription>
    <videoDescriptionT1>**** videos interested in teaching **** for kids, offered **** lessons simply, supported
        educational materials that support school curricula.
    </videoDescriptionT1>
    <videoDescriptionT2>**** videos teach **** lessons for kids simply. supported by activities and exercises. Videos
        offers materials support curricula like ----.
    </videoDescriptionT2>
    <videoDescriptionT3>Contains videos in mathematics, science, Arabic Language and other curricula. Videos include
        many topics like: ----; aims to teach ----.
    </videoDescriptionT3>
    <videoKeywords>Videos,Electronic Videos,Interactive Videos,Online Videos,Educational Videos,kids Videos,buy videos
        online
    </videoKeywords>
    <TeacherBook>Teacher Book</TeacherBook>
    <KidsStories>Kids Stories</KidsStories>
    <signintoyouraccount>Sign in to your account</signintoyouraccount>
    <search>search</search>
    <Advansedsearch>Advanced Search</Advansedsearch>
    <PayWith>Pay With</PayWith>
    <EXPLORE>Explore</EXPLORE>
    <teachersguides>teachers-guides</teachersguides>
    <Activatecode>Activate code</Activatecode>
    <Activatecodeis>Activation code is needed to download the file . Please insert the activation code</Activatecodeis>
    <Noactivation>No activation code ?</Noactivation>
    <ifyounothave>if you not have an activation code, you can request one ,by click the purchase button and follow the
        instructions.
    </ifyounothave>
    <StudentsBook>Student's Book</StudentsBook>
    <StudysPlans>Study Plans</StudysPlans>
    <ApprovalsoftheMinistryofEducation>Approvals of the Ministry of Education</ApprovalsoftheMinistryofEducation>
    <DownloadPDF>Download PDF</DownloadPDF>
    <DownloadEXE>Download Desktop App</DownloadEXE>
    <LoginToDownload>Please sign in to download book</LoginToDownload>
    <InvalidActivationCode>Invalid activation code</InvalidActivationCode>
    <TeacherPDF>Teacher PDF</TeacherPDF>
    <TeacherEXE>Teacher EXE</TeacherEXE>
    <educationaltools>educational tools</educationaltools>
    <educationaltoolsh1>educational tools</educationaltoolsh1>
    <booklessons>Lessons</booklessons>
    <tooltipother>If you didn’t find your city name, please choose "others"</tooltipother>
    <careersParagraph1>With us … achieve your goal quickly and flexibly</careersParagraph1>
    <careersParagraph2>Dar Al-Manhal mission is to continuously innovate in publishing, lead the dynamic publishing
        market, to let children find electronic books and interactive books easily, and also help them to enjoy
        electronic stories and interactive stories.
    </careersParagraph2>
    <careers>Careers</careers>
    <location>Location</location>
    <Resume>Resume</Resume>
    <careersDesc>If you're ready to join the company and inspire millions of students and educators around the globe,
        send your C.V. now.
    </careersDesc>
    <uploadFile>Upload File</uploadFile>
    <careers>careers</careers>
    <SentSuccessfullyCV>Sent Successfully</SentSuccessfullyCV>

    <!--new oday-->
    <Frequentlyaskedquestions>Frequently Asked Questions</Frequentlyaskedquestions>
    <Stillhavequestions>Still have questions?</Stillhavequestions>
    <EmailUs>Email Us</EmailUs>
    <NeedNoorcomforyourschooldistrictorgroup>Need manhal.com for your school, district, or group?</NeedNoorcomforyourschooldistrictorgroup>
    <Join>Subscribe</Join>
    <UsersAccounts>Users Accounts No.</UsersAccounts>
    <Users15>Users</Users15>
    <Users610>Users</Users610>
    <costperuser>(cost per user)</costperuser>
    <costperusers>cost per user</costperusers>
    <Annual>Annual</Annual>
    <Monthly>Monthly</Monthly>
    <Findtherightresourcesforyou>Find the right resources for you ...</Findtherightresourcesforyou>
    <LearningResources>Learning Resources</LearningResources>
    <LearningResourcesA>200+ electronic books that open the window of e-learning, and provide the best tools to increase the effectiveness of reading, studying and learning.</LearningResourcesA>
    <LearningResourcesB>60+ electronic story providing the best entertainment options for children to develop their reading habit.</LearningResourcesB>
    <LearningResourcesC>300+ Games and exercises to help teachers and students finding fun and integrate technology with learning.</LearningResourcesC>
    <LearningResourcesE>1000+ educational printable worksheets with a large variety of subjects like alphabet, letters, tracing, coloring, shapes, patterns, numbers and more.</LearningResourcesE>
    <LearningResourcesF>200+ multimedia educational materials. For example: sounds, videos, powerful audio versions.</LearningResourcesF>
    <LearningResourcesg>Our products run on various platforms and operating systems; whether it's an Android device, an iPad or a desktop computer.</LearningResourcesg>
    <LearningResourcesk>Our products come in both Arabic and English.</LearningResourcesk>
    <LearningResourcesh>200+ interactive books for kids to make learning more fun and effective with clickable elements, games, videos, interactive exercises, texts, animations, notes, images, sound effects, worksheets, music, and other forms of entertainment.</LearningResourcesh>
    <LearningResourcesi>60+ interactive stories for kids which combine images, graphics, texts, sounds, sound effects, sound tracks, to attract the kid's attention to the e-story till the end.</LearningResourcesi>
    <LearningResourcesj>400+ interactive worksheets for kids that allow experiencing interactive learning and cover all subjects, and kids' school stages.</LearningResourcesj>
    <LearningResourcesl>Quiz creator: it’s a powerful tool that gives the ability to create quizzes without needing to know any programming or have any experience with coding to get started. Quiz creator is a simple way to make your own quizzes, right on your PC, tablet or mobile whatever it is the operating system you are using (iOS, Android or Windows).</LearningResourcesl>
    <LearningResourcesm>Subscription doesn't include the E-books</LearningResourcesm>
    <moreAnd></moreAnd>
    <Plansandpricing>Pricing</Plansandpricing>
    <Accesstomillionsofresources>Access to our powerful learning resources,</Accesstomillionsofresources>
    <GamesExercisesVideosSoundsWorksheetsEBook>Games,Exercises, Videos, Sounds, Worksheets</GamesExercisesVideosSoundsWorksheetsEBook>
    <Families1>Family</Families1>
    <Schools>School</Schools>
    <YourMembership>Your Subscription</YourMembership>
    <ContactUsforMoreInfo>Contact us for more information</ContactUsforMoreInfo>
    <JobTitle>Job</JobTitle>
    <SchoolorOrganizationName>School or Organization Name</SchoolorOrganizationName>
    <AccountType>Account Type</AccountType>
    <NumberofStudents>Number of Students</NumberofStudents>
    <Activation>Activation</Activation>
    <Activationparagraph>By activating your account, you will derive benefit from Dar Al-Manhal great contents whether it’s a school account which helps teachers to save time and engage students, or a family account which helps children to learn more and get ahead.</Activationparagraph>
    <PleaseEntertheActivationCode>Please enter the activation code</PleaseEntertheActivationCode>
    <ActivationCode>Activation Code</ActivationCode>
    <NeedtoActivationCodeGETIT>Need an activation code? Get it now</NeedtoActivationCodeGETIT>
    <GO>Activate</GO>
    <perUser>Per User</perUser>
    <SchoolName>School Name</SchoolName>
    <CashOnDeliverySubscribe>Cash or Check or Bank Transfer</CashOnDeliverySubscribe>
    <Toviewordersclickon2>Our team will contact you soon, to view orders, click on</Toviewordersclickon2>
    <clickHereToActivate>To know your subscription details and get the activation code</clickHereToActivate>
    <TeachersAccounts>Teachers Accounts No.</TeachersAccounts>

    <renew>Renew</renew>
    <upgrade>Upgrade</upgrade>
    <Subscriptionstatus>Subscription status</Subscriptionstatus>
    <BillingDate>Start Date</BillingDate>
    <ExpirationDate>Expiration Date</ExpirationDate>
    <MemberDetails>Subscription Details</MemberDetails>
    <Numberofmember>Number of users</Numberofmember>
    <MemberActive>Activated Accounts No.</MemberActive>
    <MemberAvailable>Users Accounts No.</MemberAvailable>
    <Active>Active</Active>
    <Expired>Expired</Expired>
    <TypeofMembership>Type of Subscription:</TypeofMembership>
    <Cost>Cost</Cost>
    <Membership>Subscription</Membership>
    <youDontHaveMembership>Don't have a subscription?</youDontHaveMembership>
    <toUseOurServiceSubsc>To use all Dar Al-Manhal e-learning resources please subscribe with us</toUseOurServiceSubsc>
    <clickHeretosub>Click here to subscribe</clickHeretosub>

    <ActivationNO>Activation Code:</ActivationNO>
    <Cost>Cost:</Cost>
    <CostperUser>Cost per User:</CostperUser>
    <UsersAccounts>Users Accounts Cost:</UsersAccounts>
    <Teachers>Teachers</Teachers>
    <NumberofTeacher>Number of Teachers</NumberofTeacher>
    <TeacherActive>Activated Accounts No.</TeacherActive>
    <TeacherAvailable>Users Accounts No.</TeacherAvailable>
    <NumberofStudent>Number of Students</NumberofStudent>
    <StudentActive>Activated Accounts No.</StudentActive>
    <StudentAvailable>Users Accounts No.</StudentAvailable>
    <Students>Students</Students>
    <pleaseEnterCity>Please enter the city name</pleaseEnterCity>
	<PleaseEnterActCo>Please enter the activation code</PleaseEnterActCo>
    <ActivationSuccess>Your account has been activated successfully</ActivationSuccess>
    <AccountMaximumReachStudent>You have reached the maximum number of allowed students accounts</AccountMaximumReachStudent>
    <AccountMaximumReachTeacher>You have reached the maximum number of allowed teachers accounts</AccountMaximumReachTeacher>

    <AccountCodeExpiered>This activation code has been expired</AccountCodeExpiered>
    <AccountCannotActivate>This account is already activated.</AccountCannotActivate>
    <whatsapp>whatsapp</whatsapp>
    <clever>الذكاء المتعدد</clever>


    <myquizzes>My Quizzes</myquizzes>
    <Confirmation>Confirm</Confirmation>
    <Areshuredeletequestion>Do you want to delete the question?</Areshuredeletequestion>
    <Yes>Yes</Yes>
    <Cancel>Cancel</Cancel>
    <QuestionType>Question Type</QuestionType>
    <Selectitemnewquestion>Select the question type</Selectitemnewquestion>
    <Setting1>Settings</Setting1>
    <Published>Published</Published>
    <private>Private</private>
    <Public>Public</Public>
    <Faild>Failed</Faild>
    <QuizFaild>Quiz Failed</QuizFaild>
    <Editvideo>Edit video</Editvideo>
    <Editimage>Edit image</Editimage>
    <EditSound>Edit Sound</EditSound>
    <QuestionAndanswer>Question and answer</QuestionAndanswer>
    <Correctpoint>Points</Correctpoint>
    <Incorrectpoint>Incorrect point</Incorrectpoint>
    <MultipleChoice>Multiple Choice</MultipleChoice>
    <Fillintheblank>Short Answer</Fillintheblank>
    <ShortAnswer>Short Answer</ShortAnswer>
    <EnteryourAnswer>Enter your Answer</EnteryourAnswer>
    <ShortEssay>Short Essay</ShortEssay>
    <Sequence>Sequence</Sequence>
    <Item0> Item 0</Item0>
    <WordBank>Word Bank</WordBank>
    <Dragyouranswer>Drag your answer:</Dragyouranswer>
    <Two>Two</Two>
    <Four>Four</Four>
    <Three>Three</Three>
    <ClickMap>Click Map</ClickMap>
    <MultipleResponse>Multiple Response</MultipleResponse>
    <Trueorfalse>True &amp; False</Trueorfalse>
    <Matching>Matching</Matching>
    <TypeYourQuestion>Type Your Question ? </TypeYourQuestion>


    <addinvoice>Add Invoice</addinvoice>
    <editinvoice>Edit Invoice</editinvoice>
    <productname>Product Name</productname>
    <Invoicenumber>Invoice number</Invoicenumber>
    <Invoicestatus>Invoice status</Invoicestatus>
    <invoices>Invoices</invoices>
    <YourInvoice>Your Invoice</YourInvoice>
    <depth>depth</depth>
    <titleAr>Title Ar</titleAr>
    <titlEn>Title En</titlEn>
    <size>Size</size>
    <OldPrice>Old Price</OldPrice>
    <pec>Pec</pec>
    <Color>Color</Color>
    <company>Company</company>
    <writeYourquestion>Write your question</writeYourquestion>


    <subscribe>How to Subscribe?</subscribe>
    <subscribetutorialtitle1>Subscription and activation on Dar Al-Manhal Publishers' platform</subscribetutorialtitle1>
    <subscribetutorialparagraph1>Dar Al-Manhal publishers' platform offers a huge electronic educational content which includes e-books, e-stories, e-games, e-exercises, printable and interactive worksheets, videos, sounds as well as many other valuable learning sources, covering all topics and stages enriching the education process.</subscribetutorialparagraph1>
    <subscribetutorialtitle2>Subscription:</subscribetutorialtitle2>
    <subscribetutorialparagraph2>In order for a user to be able to fully browse the website and take the advantage of its content, he must subscribe to the platform by clicking the "subscribe" option in the footer.</subscribetutorialparagraph2>
    <subscribetutorialparagraph3>Then, the Subscription page appears allowing the user to subscribe to the site.</subscribetutorialparagraph3>
    <subscribetutorialtitle3>The Subscription page offers two types of subscriptions, which are:</subscribetutorialtitle3>
    <subscribetutorialol1>Family:</subscribetutorialol1>
    <subscribetutorialol2>School:</subscribetutorialol2>
    <subscribetutorialparagraph4>It allows families to subscribe to an account the users of which range from one to three users, on a monthly or yearly basis.</subscribetutorialparagraph4>
    <subscribetutorialparagraph5>A school can subscribe with any number of users -not less than 10 students- providing a teacher's account to every 10 students, on a monthly or yearly basis.</subscribetutorialparagraph5>
    <subscribetutorialul1>By clicking the “Subscribe” option, payment options and subscription information will appear.</subscribetutorialul1>
    <subscribetutorialtitle4>To complete the subscription process, the user has to choose payment method:</subscribetutorialtitle4>
    <subscribetutorialul2>credit cards (Mastercard or Visa)</subscribetutorialul2>
    <subscribetutorialul3>PayPal</subscribetutorialul3>
    <subscribetutorialparagraph51>And by clicking “Continue”, the subscription process will be completed.</subscribetutorialparagraph51>
    <subscribetutorialparagraph61>After the completion of subscription, a screen appears confirming that the process has been successfully completed.</subscribetutorialparagraph61>
    <subscribetutorialparagraph611>It moves you to the subscription information screen by clicking the link shown in the below figure.</subscribetutorialparagraph611>
    <subscriptioninformationscreen> subscription information screen</subscriptioninformationscreen>
    <subscribetutorialparagraph71>ways to access subscription screen</subscribetutorialparagraph71>
    <subscribetutorialparagraph81>From the main menu, choose “Subscribe”</subscribetutorialparagraph81>
    <subscribetutorialparagraph91>The subscription information screen appears.</subscribetutorialparagraph91>
    <subscribetutorialul4>Subscription information screen (Family Account):</subscribetutorialul4>
    <subscribetutorialul5>Subscription information screen (School Account):</subscribetutorialul5>
    <subscribetutorialparagraph101>This screen shows:</subscribetutorialparagraph101>
    <subscribetutorialul6>Subscription status (account validity, start date and expiration date)</subscribetutorialul6>
    <subscribetutorialul7>Subscription type and cost</subscribetutorialul7>
    <subscribetutorialul8>Subscription information (number of users, number of activated accounts, number of nonactivated accounts and the activation code)</subscribetutorialul8>
    <subscribetutorialtitle5>Activation: </subscribetutorialtitle5>
    <subscribetutorialparagraph111>The activation of an account is required to browse the content of the website. A subscriber's account is activated once the subscription process is completed. If a subscriber has more than one account, he must do the activation manually by :</subscribetutorialparagraph111>
    <subscribetutorialparagraph211>copying the activation code that appears on the subscription information screen and pasting it on the activation box in the activation screen.</subscribetutorialparagraph211>
    <subscribetutorialparagraph121>	From the main menu, choose “Activation”</subscribetutorialparagraph121>
    <subscribetutorialparagraph131>From the “activation screen”, the user can paste the activation code and then click “Activation”.</subscribetutorialparagraph131>
    <postalcode>Postal Code</postalcode>
    <information>Information</information>
    <byseries>By Series</byseries>
    <Performanceevaluation>Companies Performance Evaluation</Performanceevaluation>
    <ElectronicBooks>Electronic Books</ElectronicBooks>
    <NumberOfMonths>Number of months</NumberOfMonths>
    <NumberOfYears>Number of years</NumberOfYears>
    <DeleteQuiz>DeleteQuiz</DeleteQuiz>

    <Result>Result</Result>
    <Quiztime>Quiz time</Quiztime>
    <categoryname>Category Name</categoryname>
    <QustionType>Qustion Type</QustionType>
    <QustionScore>Qustion Score</QustionScore>
<QuizResultDetails>Quiz Result Details</QuizResultDetails>
    <paymenttype>Payment Type</paymenttype>
    <Subscribetype>Subscribe Type</Subscribetype>
    <subscription>Subscription</subscription>
    <editsubscription>Edit Subscription</editsubscription>
    <accountnumber>Account Number</accountnumber>
    <AllowedStudents>Allowed Students</AllowedStudents>
    <AllowedTeachers>Allowed Teachers</AllowedTeachers>
    <ActiveTeachers>Active Teachers</ActiveTeachers>
    <ActiveStudents>Active Students</ActiveStudents>
    <yearly>yearly</yearly>
    <UserCode>User Code</UserCode>
    <TeacherCode>Teacher Code</TeacherCode>
    <StartDate>Start Date</StartDate>
    <VISA>VISA</VISA>
    <MASTERCARD>MASTERCARD</MASTERCARD>
    <cod>cod</cod>
    <ios>ios</ios>
    <android>android</android>
    <Purchasedhasbeendonesuccessfully1>You have successfully subscribed to our website</Purchasedhasbeendonesuccessfully1>
    <clickhere>click here</clickhere>
    <Item1>Item 1</Item1>
    <Item2>Item 2</Item2>
    <Move>Move</Move>

    <AnswerQusetion>Answer</AnswerQusetion>
    <helpDrag>Add video, text, image, and sound to the question</helpDrag>
    <helpSetting>Insert the quiz information (title, language, category, age ...)</helpSetting>
    <helpfeed>Add feedback and points to the question</helpfeed>
    <helptutorial>Show or hide the help tips</helptutorial>
    <helpaddquestion>Add new question</helpaddquestion>
    <helpmovethecircle>Help move the cycle</helpmovethecircle>
    <helpselecttheanswer>Choose the right answer</helpselecttheanswer>
    <helpadditem>Add new answer</helpadditem>
    <DragAnswer>Drag Answer</DragAnswer>
    <PassedPlaceholder>Ex: Excellent, you passed the quiz</PassedPlaceholder>
    <FailedPlaceHolder>Ex: You failed.. Study harder</FailedPlaceHolder>
    <correctqfeedback>Ex: That's right</correctqfeedback>
    <incorrectqfeedback>Ex: This is incorrect. The correct answer is …</incorrectqfeedback>
    <PurchaseInvoiceSuccess>Payment has been processed successfully</PurchaseInvoiceSuccess>
    <InvoiceHasbeenDone>Payment is already processed</InvoiceHasbeenDone>
    <minimumusersacc>Minimum users accounts can be renewed is </minimumusersacc>



    <InteractiveWorksheetsDescription>Contains educational interactive worksheets in mathematics, science, Arabic Language, English Language, and other curricula, besides coloring pages.</InteractiveWorksheetsDescription>
    <InteractiveWorksheetsDescriptionT1>**** interactive worksheets teach **** lessons for kids supported by activities and exercises, including variety topics like **** that teach ****.</InteractiveWorksheetsDescriptionT1>
    <InteractiveWorksheetsDescriptionT2>**** interactive  worksheets teach **** lessons for kids supported by activities and exercises. including variety topics like ---- that teach ----.</InteractiveWorksheetsDescriptionT2>
    <InteractiveWorksheetsDescriptionT3>Contains interactive worksheets in math, science, Arabic Language... Interactive Worksheets include many topics like: ----; aims to teach ----.</InteractiveWorksheetsDescriptionT3>

    <TextURL>Text URL</TextURL>
    <ImageURL>Image URL</ImageURL>
    <AccountMaximumReach>You have reached the maximum number of allowed users accounts</AccountMaximumReach>
    <Purchase_Details>Purchase Details</Purchase_Details>
    <Iframe>Iframe</Iframe>
    <EnterURL>Enter URL</EnterURL>
    <Slider>Slider</Slider>
    <Scratcher>Scratcher</Scratcher>
    <BackgroundIMG>Back Image</BackgroundIMG>
    <FrontIMG>Front Image</FrontIMG>
    <FontSize>Font Size</FontSize>
    <PopOut>Pop Out</PopOut>
    <PopUpImg>Popup image</PopUpImg>
    <TransparentVideo>Transparent Video</TransparentVideo>
    <image360>image 360</image360>
    <images>images</images>
    <ImageLink>Image Link</ImageLink>
    <TextLink>Text Link</TextLink>
    <Aworldofwonders>A World of Wonders</Aworldofwonders>
    <Thejoyoflearning>The Joy of Learning</Thejoyoflearning>
    <Watchandlearn>Watch and Learn</Watchandlearn>
    <newvisioninlearning>New Learning vision</newvisioninlearning>
    <book1>book</book1>
    <EbooksTitle>Electronic Books | E-Books | Online Books | Dar AlManhal E-books</EbooksTitle>
    <CDcopy>CD copy</CDcopy>
    <DoYouWantDeleteUnit>Do you want delete this unit ?</DoYouWantDeleteUnit>
    <RUSure>Are you sure ?</RUSure>
    <unitdeletedsuccess>unit has been deleted successfully</unitdeletedsuccess>
    <DoYouWantDeleteLesson>Do you want delete this lesson ?</DoYouWantDeleteLesson>
    <Lessondeletedsuccess>lesson has been deleted successfully</Lessondeletedsuccess>
    <Mobileandwhatsapp> <![CDATA[Mobile & Whatsapp  ]]></Mobileandwhatsapp>
    <fakeID>Fake ID</fakeID>
    <productnumber>Product number</productnumber>
    <EducationalLessons>Educational Lessons</EducationalLessons>
    <Standardnumber>Standard Number</Standardnumber>
    <GuidedlessonAr>Guided lesson Ar</GuidedlessonAr>
    <GuidedlessonEn>Guided lesson En</GuidedlessonEn>




    <AddEducationalLesson>Add Educational lesson</AddEducationalLesson>
    <AddEducationalTools>Add Educational Tools</AddEducationalTools>
    <EditEducationalLesson>Edit Educational lesson</EditEducationalLesson>
    <EditEducationalTools>Edit Educational Tools</EditEducationalTools>
    <AddFurniture>Add Furniture</AddFurniture>
    <EditFurniture>Edit Furniture</EditFurniture>
    <EditSeries>Edit Series</EditSeries>
    <StoriesCategory>Stories Category</StoriesCategory>
    <EditMedia>Edit Media</EditMedia>
    <EditGames>Edit Games</EditGames>
    <paymentinformation>Payment Information</paymentinformation>
    <Packetinformation>Packet Information</Packetinformation>
    <DoyouKnow>Do you Know?</DoyouKnow>
    <Iframe>iframe</Iframe>
    <NoBackground>No Background</NoBackground>
    <Border>Border</Border>
    <NoBorder>No Border</NoBorder>
    <Appearance>Appearance</Appearance>
    <appearanceofobjectwithouttiming>Without Timing</appearanceofobjectwithouttiming>
    <DailyTime>Time Delay</DailyTime>
    <Sec>Sec.</Sec>
    <RightBallon>Right Callout</RightBallon>
    <LeftBallon>Left Callout</LeftBallon>
    <ImportfromPDF>Import from PDF</ImportfromPDF>
    <ImportfromePUB>Import from ePub</ImportfromePUB>
    <ExportfromePUB>Export from ePub</ExportfromePUB>
    <General>Story Information</General>
    <PublishPrice> <![CDATA[Publish and Price]]></PublishPrice>
    <CoverScreenshoots> <![CDATA[Cover and Screenshots]]></CoverScreenshoots>
    <pageview>Page View</pageview>
    <pageflip>Page Flip</pageflip>
    <Onepage>One Page</Onepage>
    <Towpage>Two Pages</Towpage>
    <Normal>Normal</Normal>
    <Flipping>Flipping</Flipping>
    <Package>Package</Package>
    <Democover>Demo Cover</Democover>
    <helpDragstory>Add text, image ,do you know? ,iframe ,callouts, and sound to the story</helpDragstory>
    <helpSettingstory>Insert story information (title, language, category, age ...)</helpSettingstory>
    <helptutorialstory>Show or hide the help tips</helptutorialstory>
    <helpaddquestionstory>Add New Page</helpaddquestionstory>
    <helpaddnewgame>Add New Page</helpaddnewgame>
    <helpmovethecirclestory>Help move the cycle</helpmovethecirclestory>
    <helpadditemstory>Add New Page</helpadditemstory>
    <LMS>LMS</LMS>
    <Configurationsetting>LMS setting</Configurationsetting>
    <SchoolNameAr>School Name Ar</SchoolNameAr>
    <SchoolNameEn>School Name En</SchoolNameEn>
    <Create>Create</Create>
    <Link>URL</Link>
    <Logo>Logo</Logo>
    <YourLMSLink>Your LMS Link </YourLMSLink>
    <InvalidArTitle>invalid arabic title</InvalidArTitle>
    <InvalidEnTitle>invalid english title</InvalidEnTitle>
    <SubDomainExist>subdomain already exist</SubDomainExist>
    <UserHaveNoSubscription>user don't have any subscription</UserHaveNoSubscription>
    <CannotCreateLMSAcct>cannot create Cpanel account</CannotCreateLMSAcct>
    <CannotCreateSubdomain>cannot create subdomain</CannotCreateSubdomain>
    <CannotCreateDB>cannot create database</CannotCreateDB>
    <CannotCopyLMS>cannot copy LMS files</CannotCopyLMS>
    <CannotConfigLMS>cannot call LMS configuration file</CannotConfigLMS>
    <CannotSaveToDB>cannot save LMS instant info to database</CannotSaveToDB>
    <InvalidSubDomainFormat>Invalid Subdomain format ,subdomain must start with charachtar and just contain charachtar and number and dash - </InvalidSubDomainFormat>
    <SubdomainExist>This subdomain already exist , please chose another one</SubdomainExist>
    <ThisAcctHaveLMS>LMS already exist for this account , please contact us to solve this problem</ThisAcctHaveLMS>
    <LMSSettingsNote>School's LMS URL Once saved, it can’t be changed</LMSSettingsNote>
    <LMSSettingsDesc>To start using your school's LMS, please configure it by filling the required information just for the first time.</LMSSettingsDesc>
    <noPermession>no permission</noPermession>
    <MustSubscribeAsSchoolLMS>You must subscribe as school to use LMS features</MustSubscribeAsSchoolLMS>
    <LMSNotConfigured>LMS not set</LMSNotConfigured>
    <ContactAdminToSetLMS>please contact your administrator to setup LMS system</ContactAdminToSetLMS>
    <CannotinstallSSL>Can not install SSL certificate</CannotinstallSSL>
    <newTab>New Tab</newTab>
    <lmshelpmessage>maybe this process take a while , please wait</lmshelpmessage>
    <PlayList>Playlist</PlayList>
    <AddPlaylist>Add Playlist</AddPlaylist>
    <PlaylistType>Playlist Type</PlaylistType>
    <EditPlaylist>Edit Playlist</EditPlaylist>
    <Awards>Awards</Awards>
    <Progressrate>Progress rate</Progressrate>

    <messagenumberofbookcanbuy>The minimum amount of curriculum books you can buy through our website is 25 books</messagenumberofbookcanbuy>
    <Dearcustomer>Dear customer:</Dearcustomer>
    <Dearcustomer1>- When you buy 25 paper books you get the activation code of the e-book for free.</Dearcustomer1>
    <Dearcustomer2>- You can’t buy the e-book separately from the paper book.</Dearcustomer2>
    <Dearcustomer3>- The minimum amount of curriculum books you can buy through our website is 25 books.</Dearcustomer3>
    <Dearcustomer4>- You can buy enriched e-book separately or with the paper copy by a separate price. </Dearcustomer4>
    <Bringtofront>Bring to front</Bringtofront>
    <Sendtoback>Send to back</Sendtoback>
    <mystories>My Stories</mystories>
    <DeleteStory>Delete Story</DeleteStory>
    <AreyousureDeleteStory>Are you sure you want delete this story ?</AreyousureDeleteStory>

    <Activateacct>Activate Account</Activateacct>
    <YouhadfinishedFreepages>You’ve finished reading the free pages, if you like the story subscribe now and enjoy reading.</YouhadfinishedFreepages>
    <subscribeNow>Subscribe Now</subscribeNow>
    <orEnterActCode>or enter the activation code</orEnterActCode>
    <clickHereTogetCode>Subscribe now and get the activation code to read the entire story pages and to enjoy many other services and features on the platform.</clickHereTogetCode>
    <mystories>My Stories</mystories>
    <Areshuredeletepage>Do you want delete this page?</Areshuredeletepage>
    <atLeastOnePage>Last page can't be deleted</atLeastOnePage>
    <ok>ok</ok>

    <ActivateAccount>Activate Account</ActivateAccount>
    <Youfinishedbrowsingfreepages><![CDATA[ You’ve finished browsing the free pages; subscribe now to complete browsing the book]]></Youfinishedbrowsingfreepages>
    <Subscribenow>Buy now</Subscribenow>
    <orenteractivationcode>or enter the activation code</orenteractivationcode>
    <Informationcard>Information card</Informationcard>
    <Subscribenowgetactivation>Subscribe now and get the activation code to browse the entire book pages and to enjoy many other services and features on the platform</Subscribenowgetactivation>
    <BookEnrichments>Book Enrichments</BookEnrichments>
    <BookIndex>Book Index</BookIndex>
    <Enrichments>Enrichments</Enrichments>
    <QRCode>QR Code</QRCode>
    <Bookmarks>Bookmarks</Bookmarks>
    <Notes>Notes</Notes>
    <Pageenrichments>Page enrichments</Pageenrichments>

    <INFORMATION>Information</INFORMATION>
    <EDITPAGE>Edit Background</EDITPAGE>
    <Image>Background</Image>
    <Thumb>Thumbnail</Thumb>
    <SETTINGS>Settings</SETTINGS>
    <prek>Pre-K</prek>
    <Layers>Layers</Layers>
    <Negative>Negative</Negative>
    <buttons>Buttons</buttons>
    <slideroptions>Slider options</slideroptions>
    <Arrow>Arrow</Arrow>
    <Dots>Dots</Dots>
    <autoplay>Autoplay</autoplay>
    <infinite>Infinite</infinite>
    <SelectAction>Select Action</SelectAction>
    <addinginteractionstoyourstory>add interactions to your story</addinginteractionstoyourstory>
    <Symbols>Symbols</Symbols>
    <lineHeight>Line height</lineHeight>

    <On>On</On>
    <Button>Button</Button>
    <ClickorTab>Click or Tab</ClickorTab>
    <RightClick>Right-Click</RightClick>
    <DoubleClick>Double-Click</DoubleClick>
    <MouseOver>Mouse Over</MouseOver>
    <Do>Do</Do>
    <GotoSpecificPage>Go to Specific Page</GotoSpecificPage>
    <Openpopup>Open popup</Openpopup>
    <GotoURL>Go to URL</GotoURL>
    <GotoNextPage>Go to Next Page</GotoNextPage>
    <GotoPreviousPage>Go to Previous Page</GotoPreviousPage>
    <PlayObject>Play Object</PlayObject>
    <ShowObject>Show Object</ShowObject>
    <HideObject>Hide Object</HideObject>
    <Showmessage>Show message</Showmessage>
    <Target>Target</Target>
    <ThumbName>Thumb Name</ThumbName>
    <TypeMessagehere>Type Message here</TypeMessagehere>
    <SoundEffect>Sound Effect</SoundEffect>
    <StartAnimation>Start Animation</StartAnimation>
    <EndAnimation>End Animation</EndAnimation>
    <voiceRecorder>Voice Recorder</voiceRecorder>

    <Animation>Animation</Animation>
    <AnimationPane>Animation Pane</AnimationPane>
    <ShowEffect>Show Effect</ShowEffect>
    <WithPrevious>With Previous</WithPrevious>
    <AfterPrevious>After Previous</AfterPrevious>
    <Timer>Timer</Timer>
    <Duration>Duration</Duration>
    <Time>Time</Time>
    <Start>Start</Start>

    <click>click</click>
    <arrow>arrow</arrow>
    <camera>camera</camera>
    <laser>laser</laser>
    <without>without</without>
    <AnimateObject>Animate Object</AnimateObject>

    <donateForAlhussain>Donate to </donateForAlhussain>
    <KingHussein>King Hussein Cancer Center </KingHussein>
    <donationfor>Donation for King Hussein Cancer Center </donationfor>
    <donatecampaignP1><![CDATA[ Dar Al Manhal Publishers, driven by its responsibility towards society, mindful of the need to build effective partnerships with national bodies, in support of efforts made by the biggest community foundation fighting cancer in Jordan, and out of concern to build an educated generation of young people armed with knowledge, Dar Al Manhal Publishers in partnership with King Hussein Cancer Centre launches a national campaign entitled “<span>A New Book ... A Chance of Recovery</span>” to be the first ofits kind to spread education and knowledge and save children cared for by the Centre. ]]></donatecampaignP1>
    <donatecampaignP2>Now you could be part of it and support the Centre’s patients for only half a dinar added to your invoice and Dar AL Manhal Publishers will donate the same amount. </donatecampaignP2>
    <ourshops>Our shops</ourshops>
    <transitions>Transitions</transitions>
    <Align>Align</Align>
    <Vertical>Vertical</Vertical>
    <Horizontal>Horizontal</Horizontal>
    <DrawingTool>Drawing Tool</DrawingTool>
    <ONShow>ON Show</ONShow>
    <imanhal>iManhal</imanhal>
    <imanhalparagraph1>IManhal is a system to support systematic education both within the classroom and at home. It enables teachers to create e-lessons, manage them effectively, and benefit from the educational content available on Dar Al Manhal platform, within an environment that is rich with tools to support the educational process.</imanhalparagraph1>
    <interactiveBook>interactive Book</interactiveBook>
    <toptitle>Innovative Learning Solutions</toptitle>
    <topparagraph>Interactive content for schools and kindergartens</topparagraph>
    <imanhalparagraph2>It contains various types multimedia that enrich the book's material and support it such as exercises, games, animations, videos, songs, images, sound effects and many more that make learning fun.</imanhalparagraph2>
    <imanhalparagraph3>A huge library in both Arabic and English, featuring images and sound effects that add fun to the story and attract young readers to the end. Our stories are compatible with various smart devices and operating systems.</imanhalparagraph3>
    <imanhalparagraph4>The system includes various types of learning resources that support the educational process through play and entertainment and help teachers to integrate technology with education, and create the right environment for that.</imanhalparagraph4>
    <advUL1>Pre-designed lessons</advUL1>
    <advUL2>Tracking reports</advUL2>
    <advUL3>Homework and quizzes</advUL3>
    <advUL4>Lessons editor</advUL4>
    <advUL5>Homework editor</advUL5>
    <advUL6>Badges</advUL6>
    <advUL7>Student progress</advUL7>
    <advUL8>School schedule and calendar</advUL8>
    <advUL9>Notifications and messages</advUL9>
    <advUL10>Apps for students and parents</advUL10>
    <ElectronicContent>Digital Content</ElectronicContent>
    <ElectronicContenttitle1>Exercises</ElectronicContenttitle1>
    <ElectronicContenttitle2>Videos</ElectronicContenttitle2>
    <ElectronicContenttitle3>Applications</ElectronicContenttitle3>
    <ElectronicContenttitle4>Lessons</ElectronicContenttitle4>
    <ElectronicContenttitle5>Quizzes</ElectronicContenttitle5>
    <ElectronicContenttitle6>Worksheets</ElectronicContenttitle6>
    <towweeks>For Two Weeks</towweeks>
    <bgAnimation>Bg Animation</bgAnimation>
    <Bybrand>By Brand</Bybrand>
    <brand>Brand</brand>

    <publisher>publisher</publisher>
    <EditPublisher>Edit Publisher</EditPublisher>
    <AddPublisher>Add Publisher</AddPublisher>
    <Store>Store</Store>
    <Toys>Toys</Toys>
    <ByPublisher>By Publisher</ByPublisher>
    <ByDepartment>By Department</ByDepartment>


    <Manufacturer>Manufacturer</Manufacturer>
    <Department>Department</Department>
    <Activities>Activities</Activities>
    <Activity>Activity</Activity>
    <Fontfamily>Font family</Fontfamily>
    <Curriculum>Curriculum</Curriculum>


    <Domains>Domains</Domains>
    <Alignedstandards>Aligned standards</Alignedstandards>
    <Code>Code</Code>
    <Pivots>Pivots</Pivots>
    <Standards>Standards</Standards>
    <Grades>Grades</Grades>
    <Outcomes>Outcomes</Outcomes>
    <Units>Units</Units>
    <Courses>Courses</Courses>

    <helpaddnewgame>Add New Game</helpaddnewgame>
    <choosetemplate>Choose Template</choosetemplate>
    <level>Level</level>
    <tags>Tags</tags>
    <isPublish>Published</isPublish>
    <Move>Move</Move>

    <WordGame1>الكلمة وضدها</WordGame1>
    <myactivities>My Activities</myactivities>
    <AddActivity>Add Activity</AddActivity>

    <WordGame2>تحليل الكلمة</WordGame2>

    <DeleteMedia>Delete Media</DeleteMedia>
    <AreyousureDeleteMedia>Are you sure you want delete this media ?</AreyousureDeleteMedia>


    <!--store language-->
    <Dashboard>Dashboard</Dashboard>
    <TotalCustomers>Total Customers</TotalCustomers>
    <TotalDrivers>Total Drivers</TotalDrivers>
    <OnlineDrivers>Online Drivers</OnlineDrivers>
    <TotalBookingscompleted>Total Orders completed</TotalBookingscompleted>
    <TotalBookingsCancelled>Total Orders Cancelled</TotalBookingsCancelled>
    <TotalBookingsinprogress >Total Orders inprogress</TotalBookingsinprogress>
    <Revenue>Revenue</Revenue>
    <Revenuecurrentweek>Revenue current week</Revenuecurrentweek>
    <Revenuecurrentmonth>Revenue current month</Revenuecurrentmonth>
    <RevenueToday>Revenue today</RevenueToday>
    <RevenueToday>Revenue today</RevenueToday>
    <NoOfBookings>N.O Orders</NoOfBookings>


    <Completed>Completed</Completed>
    <CompletedOrders>Completed Orders</CompletedOrders>
    <InProgress>In Progress</InProgress>
    <Cancelled>Cancelled</Cancelled>
    <OnHold>On Hold</OnHold>
    <OrderID>Order ID</OrderID>
    <Custumer>Custumer</Custumer>
    <destination>Destination</destination>
    <Driver>Driver</Driver>
    <Amount>Amount</Amount>
    <drivercash>Driver cash</drivercash>
    <iscashcollection>Is cash collection</iscashcollection>
    <collect>collect</collect>
    <notcollect>Not collect</notcollect>
    <more1>More</more1>
    <MoreDetails>More Details</MoreDetails>
    <RequestID>Request ID</RequestID>

    <patternName>Pattern Name</patternName>
    <orderdate>orderdate</orderdate>
    <Pickupdate>Pickup date</Pickupdate>
    <DropOff>Drop Off Date</DropOff>
    <Fare>Fare</Fare>
    <CancelledOrders>Cancelled Orders</CancelledOrders>

    <fillblank>أملأ الفراغ - جمل طويلة</fillblank>
    <fillblankShort>أملأ الفراغ - جمل قصيرة</fillblankShort>
    <truefalse>صح او خطأ</truefalse>
    <Help>Help</Help>
    <sorting>Sorting</sorting>
    <sortingWord>تصنيف - كلمات</sortingWord>
    <sortingWordHorizontal>توصيل نص وصورة -  بالطول</sortingWordHorizontal>
    <sortingWordVertical>توصيل نص وصورة -  بالعرض</sortingWordVertical>
    <matching>توصيل</matching>
    <ExtractParagraph>أستخرج - فقرة</ExtractParagraph>
    <selctWord>اختيار الإجابة - نص طويل</selctWord>
    <DuplicatePage>Duplicate Page</DuplicatePage>
    <outofstock>Out Of Stock</outofstock>





<!--start tasweq-->
<StudentBook_ActivityBook_EBook>Student Book + Activity Book</StudentBook_ActivityBook_EBook>
<StudentBook_pupilsBook_EBook>Pupil's Book + Activity Book</StudentBook_pupilsBook_EBook>
<StudentBook_EBook>Student Book</StudentBook_EBook>
<ActivityBook_EBook>Activity Book</ActivityBook_EBook>
<TeacherBook>Teacher Book</TeacherBook>
<sale>25% OFF</sale>
<sale1>50% OFF</sale1>
<removeItem>Remove Item</removeItem>
<HotOfferOFF>Hot Offer</HotOfferOFF>
<NoThanks>No Thanks</NoThanks>
<Yes>Yes</Yes>
<Do_you_want_to_add_the_Sonoono_string_to_the_cart>Do you want to add the Sonoono string to the cart ?</Do_you_want_to_add_the_Sonoono_string_to_the_cart>
<upsalemessage1> is usually purchased with the following products:</upsalemessage1>
<!--<upsalemessage2><![CDATA[Get the Sonoono Stories series now at a special <b style="color: #eb0c0c">50% discount</b> for one time]]></upsalemessage2>-->
<upsalemessage2><![CDATA[Get it/them now at a special   <b style="color: #eb0c0c;font-weight: normal !important;font-size: 13px;"></b>  for one time!]]></upsalemessage2>
<OverHappyCustomers>Over 5,500+ Happy Customers.</OverHappyCustomers>
<SecurePayments>100% Secure Payments.</SecurePayments>
<BuyTowItem>Buy Tow Item or more and get Free Shipping.</BuyTowItem>
<AboutSeries>About Series</AboutSeries>
<AboutBook>About Book</AboutBook>
<stories6>6 Stories</stories6>
<stories30>30 Stories</stories30>
<levelStart>Start Reading</levelStart>
<levelOne>Level 1</levelOne>
<levelTow>Level 2</levelTow>
<levelThree>Level 3</levelThree>
<levelFour>Level 4</levelFour>
<levelOnetow>Level 1 + Level 2</levelOnetow>
<Garden>KG1</Garden>
<Primer>KG2</Primer>
<AllLevel>All Level</AllLevel>

    <levelStart1>Start Reading (9 stories available)</levelStart1>
    <levelOne1>Level 1 (6 stories available)</levelOne1>
    <levelTow1>Level 2 (9 stories available)</levelTow1>
    <levelThree1>Level 3 (7 stories available)</levelThree1>
    <levelFour1>Level 4 (6 stories available)</levelFour1>

<!--stories-->
<AboutSeriesparagraphS1English><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify">A series of 6 stories taking place in Palestine at different points of time. The author blended the past and the present on the one hand, and fantasy and reality on the other hand making use of expressive drawings and the amusing suspenseful method.</p><p style="text-align:justify">The series tells the relationship between Aqsa mosque and Haram mosque, the splendor of Qubbat Al Sakhra (Dome of the Rock) in addition to the honorable positions of Al Aqsa young people in the defense of Al Quds (Jerusalem). </p>]]></AboutSeriesparagraphS1English>
<AboutSeriesparagraphS1Arabic><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify;direction:rtl;font-family:'Droid Arabic Kufi';font-size:13px">مجموعة من ست قصص تدور أحداثها في فلسطين عبر التاريخ، حيث مزج المؤلف الماضي بالحاضر والخيال بالواقع برسومات معبّرة وأسلوب قصصي ممتع. تروي السلسلة علاقة المسجد الأقصى بالمسجد الحرام وروعة بناء قبّة الصخرة إضافة إلى مواقف معبّرة عن تصميم أشبال وزهرات الأقصى على حماية القدس والدفاع عنها. </p>]]></AboutSeriesparagraphS1Arabic>
<AboutSeriesparagraphS2English><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify">Is a series of short stories presented by Dar Al Manhal Publishers. It aims at developing children’s cognitive and language skills and teaching the alphabet in an entertaining method with age appropriate language and illustrations. The series is available as a pack of 30 short stories each introducing one of the 28 Arabic letters in a thoughtful loving approach and practical amusing activities.</p>]]></AboutSeriesparagraphS2English>
<AboutSeriesparagraphS2Arabic><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify;direction:rtl;font-family:'Droid Arabic Kufi';font-size:13px">حكايات الحروف هي سلسلة قصص قصيرة للأطفال مقدمة من دار المنهل، تنمي قدرات الطفل المعرفية واللغوية، وتهدف إلى تعليم الحروف العربية للأطفال بشكل جديد ومسلي بالصور والكلمات. تضم سلسلة حكايات الحروف ثلاثين قصة، تعرف كل حكاية في السلسلة الطفل على حرف من حروف اللغة العربية في مرحلة مبكرة، وبأسلوب تعليمي محبب ومنظم، وأنشطة عملية مسلية. تباع السلسلة كمجموعة واحدة كي تؤدي الهدف المطلوب في تعليم الأطفال الحروف الهجائية. </p>]]></AboutSeriesparagraphS2Arabic>
<AboutSeriesparagraphS3English><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify">With its 30 stories coming in 3 age groups, Al Zarafah series is directed to (5-10) years old children marked by diversity of topics, simplicity and suitability age-appropriate language. It aims at teaching children moral values along with some aspects of animal life. </p><p style="text-align:justify">Each story is followed by diverse activities to improve children’s language skills, raise their environmental awareness and amuse them with character coloring activities.</p>]]></AboutSeriesparagraphS3English>
<AboutSeriesparagraphS3Arabic><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify;direction:rtl;font-family:'Droid Arabic Kufi';font-size:13px">ثلاثون حكاية ممتعة وهادفة في ثلاث مجموعات، تخاطب الأطفال بعمر 5-10 سنوات، تمتاز بتنوع موضوعاتها وتهدف إلى إيصال المعارف والقيم والعادات الحسنة للأطفال بأسلوب بسيط وفكاهي على لسان الحيوانات. مع إبراز بعض أنماط الحياة للحيوانات الواردة في القصص التي صيغت بكلمات وألفاظ سهلة تناسب عمر الطفل. يتبع كل قصة أنشطة مختلفة تركز على تنمية معرفة الطفل بالبيئة من حوله، إضافة إلى أنشطة تٌنمي المهارات اللغوية، كما يستمتع الطفل بتلوين شخصيات القصة على صفحة خاصة. </p>]]></AboutSeriesparagraphS3Arabic>
<AboutSeriesparagraphS4English><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify">A series of picture books presented by Dar Al Manhal Publishers urging the little ones to read and developing their knowledge and positive attitudes. The series contains five short stories based on moral values with the purpose of developing children’s imagination, urging them to think wisely; be cooperative, loving and self-reliant. Saba Stories are supported with expressive drawings and words that are age appropriate.</p>]]></AboutSeriesparagraphS4English>
<AboutSeriesparagraphS4Arabic><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify;direction:rtl;font-family:'Droid Arabic Kufi';font-size:13px">حكايات صبا هي سلسلة قصص مصورة مقدمة من دار المنهل، تشجع الأطفال الصغار على القراءة وتكسبهم العديد من المعارف والسلوكيات الإيجابية. تضم السلسلة خمس قصص قصيرة، يتعلمون من خلالها قيمًا أخلاقية جميلة، وتنمي لديهم الخيال والحكمة وحب التعاون والصداقة والاعتماد على النفس برسوم ومشاهد معبرة ومفردات تناسب الأطفال.</p>]]></AboutSeriesparagraphS4Arabic>
<AboutSeriesparagraphS5English><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify">A series of 5 progressive levels directed to preschoolers to 10-year olds. It contains diverse short stories supported with lovely drawings and simple language which contribute to vocabulary building.    </p>]]></AboutSeriesparagraphS5English>
<AboutSeriesparagraphS5Arabic><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify;direction:rtl;font-family:'Droid Arabic Kufi';font-size:13px">تأتي سلسلة نادي القراءة في 5 مستويات متتابعة، موجهة للأطفال في مرحلة ما قبل المدرسة إلى الأطفال بعمر 10 سنوات. تضم السلسلة قصص قصيرة ومتنوعة، تعرض من خلال رسوم جميلة معبر عنها بكلمات بسيطة وتشكل حصيلة لغوية هامة للطفل.</p>]]></AboutSeriesparagraphS5Arabic>
<LevelStratdesc>A series of short stories directed to preschoolers with diverse subjects including behavioral and environmental concepts. The series is supported with lovely drawings and simple language. </LevelStratdesc>
<LevelOnedesc>Directed to 6 to 7-year olds, it has a diverse of topics including some moral attitudes like self-reliance, love of work, dental care, problem solving and social relationships, etc. The series is supported with lovely drawings and age appropriate language.  </LevelOnedesc>
<LevelTowdesc>Directed to 7-8 years old children, it provides stories of simple language and expressive illustrations addressing concepts like trustworthiness, cooperation, altruism, preservation of the environment in a way that improves children’s vocabulary and reading skills.  </LevelTowdesc>
<LevelThreedesc>It’s directed to 8-9 years old children. It addresses some concepts in age appropriate language like good manners, cooperation, showing obedience to parents, problem solving and it urges children to think and be creative. It aims at improving children’s awareness and language skills.</LevelThreedesc>
<LevelFourdesc>It’s directed to 9 to 10-year olds with advanced language and values suitable for the target age group including showing respect to the old, problem solving, self-reliance and other attitudes that contribute to the development of critical thinking and language and reading skills. The Level urges children to follow positive examples and be creative.   </LevelFourdesc>
<AboutLevelTow>The minimalist collaboration features chairs, lightening, Shelves, Sofas, Desks and various home accessories, all offering form and function at the same point.We use high-strength clamps and joinery techniques specially designed for engineered wood beds. Ergo, no irksome creaks - and you can sleep like a baby, well into adulthood! The minimalist collaboration features chairs, lightening, Shelves, Sofas, Desks and various home accessories, all offering form and function at the same point.We use high-strength clamps and joinery techniques specially designed for engineered wood beds.</AboutLevelTow>
<AboutLevelthree>The minimalist collaboration features chairs, lightening, Shelves, Sofas, Desks and various home accessories, all offering form and function at the same point.We use high-strength clamps and joinery techniques specially designed for engineered wood beds. Ergo, no irksome creaks - and you can sleep like a baby, well into adulthood! The minimalist collaboration features chairs, lightening, Shelves, Sofas, Desks and various home accessories, all offering form and function at the same point.We use high-strength clamps and joinery techniques specially designed for engineered wood beds.</AboutLevelthree>



<!--Books-->
<BookArabicFriendparagraphEnglish><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify">An educational series for teaching Arabic language in six consecutive levels. Each levels consists of a comprehensive range of teaching materials: the Student's Book, the Activity Book, and the Teacher's Book, in addition to supporting media: a CD, educational posters, and stories, etc. It took account of learners’ need to master the four basic skills of Arabic, namely: listening, speaking, reading and writing.</p>]]></BookArabicFriendparagraphEnglish>
<BookArabicFriendparagraphArabic><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify;direction:rtl;font-family:'Droid Arabic Kufi';font-size:13px">سلسلة تعليمية لتعليم اللغة العربية، تشمل ستة مستويات متتابعة. يتكون كل مستوى من ثلاث مواد تعليمية رئيسة هي: كتاب الطالب، وكتاب النشاط، وكتاب المعلم بالإضافة إلى وسائل تعليمية داعمة هي: قرص مدمج وبطاقات تعليمية، وبوسترات، وقصص، ... وقد روعي فيها حاجة المتعلم إلى إتقان المهارات الأساسية في تعلم اللغة العربية وهي: الاستماع، والمحادثة، والقراءة، والكتابة.</p>]]></BookArabicFriendparagraphArabic>

<BookbraemparagraphEnglish><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify">The series is designed to teach children the basic skills of the Arabic language: listening, speaking, reading and writing. It is concerned with teaching the Arabic language through various activities, purposeful language games, useful stories, and songs. Based on the child's environment and surroundings, it is an easy-to-learn series. </p>]]></BookbraemparagraphEnglish>
<BookbraemparagraphArabic><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify;direction:rtl;font-family:'Droid Arabic Kufi';font-size:13px">تأتي سلسلة براعم العربية لتعليم الأطفال المهارات الأساسية في اللغة العربية وهي: الاستماع، والمحادثة، والقراءة، والكتابة.</p>]]></BookbraemparagraphArabic>

<!--a1-->
<bookcontents>Book Contents</bookcontents>

<bookcontentsDesc1>The series comes in 6 consecutive levels:</bookcontentsDesc1>
<bookcontentsDesc2>It comes in two levels:</bookcontentsDesc2>
<bookcontentsDesc3>يأتي منهاج العب وتعلم مع الحروف في كتابين:</bookcontentsDesc3>
<bookcontentsDesc4>It also aims to educate Muslim children in the Arab and Islamic world, as well as the children of Islamic communities in foreign countries and provide them with an honorable and easy image of the principles of Islam. Each level is accompanied by a Teacher's Book that contains the necessary steps, experiences and ideas for the teacher to deliver the information the book offers. It also includes CDs for the songs that serve to learn the concepts presented by the series.</bookcontentsDesc4>
<bookcontentsDesc5>bookcontentsDesc</bookcontentsDesc5>
<bookcontentsDesc6>The topics of the series are appropriate for the age group it addresses in terms of content and presentation. The Quranic verses and Prophetic hadiths presented in Arabic were illustrated, translated and transliterated in English. Activities follow lessons to assess children’s understanding.  </bookcontentsDesc6>

<!--a1-->
    <ArabicFriendsBustanStudent><![CDATA[<p>Friends of Arabic KG1 / Student’s Book is directed to kindergarten children. It aims to introduce children to the twenty-eight Arabic letters; their forms, sounds and pronunciation. It trains children to form individual letters and join different letters to form words and sentences. It presents the material in an entertaining way that motivates the child to love Arabic and practice it outside of the classroom.</p><p>The book is divided into eight units, each unit has four lessons with topics varying to include the following areas: my home, my kindergarten, my farm, my computer, my health, my personal hygiene, my toys, my senses.</p>]]></ArabicFriendsBustanStudent>
<ArabicFriendsBustanactivity>It offers a variety of distinctive and interesting exercises designed to consolidate what the pupils have learnt in the Student’s Book.</ArabicFriendsBustanactivity>
<ArabicFriendsBustanTeacher>It offers information, instructions and ways of teaching the material. There are also step-by-step suggestions on how to do the exercises to achieve the outcomes of the lesson.   </ArabicFriendsBustanTeacher>

<!--a2-->
<ArabicFriendstamhidiStudent>It is directed to kindergarten children, and takes into account the child's need to master the basic skills of learning Arabic language. It is divided into 32 lessons, aimed at teaching children the Arabic letters; their sounds and shapes. in addition, it teaches children to form words and syllables. Each lesson begins with a picture scene to elicit language in children.</ArabicFriendstamhidiStudent>
<ArabicFriendstamhidiactivity>It offers a variety of distinctive and interesting exercises designed to consolidate what the pupils have learnt in the Student’s Book.</ArabicFriendstamhidiactivity>
<ArabicFriendstamhidiTeacher>It offers information, instructions and ways of teaching the material. There are also step-by-step suggestions on how to do the exercises to achieve the outcomes of the lesson.</ArabicFriendstamhidiTeacher>

<!--a3-->
<ArabicFriendsOneStudent><![CDATA[<p>Its focus is to help learners understand what they listen to, pronounce letters and words correctly, read texts fully supported with diacritics (Tashkeel), follow proper writing rules, and use linguistic structures in communication.</p><p>The book consists of eight units each has been divided into two lessons. The units have been conveniently distributed in the two academic semesters. The book aims to improve children’s observation and make them read letters, words and sentences, and combine them together.</p><p>The units were graded in the educational plan from the private environment at home to the general environment in the same country and in the countries of the world, as follows: at home, at school, relatives, children’s playground, city market, personal hygiene, happy Eid, my country.</p>]]></ArabicFriendsOneStudent>
<ArabicFriendsOneactivity>The Activity Book contains various activities that reinforce what the children have learned in the Student’s Book. The focus of the book is primarily on letters, syllables, words and sentences where the activities vary to include different patterns of reading and writing to enable children to speak and spell correctly.</ArabicFriendsOneactivity>
<ArabicFriendsOneTeacher>It offers information, instructions and ways of teaching the material. There are also step-by-step suggestions on how to do the exercises to achieve the outcomes of the lesson.</ArabicFriendsOneTeacher>

<!--a4-->
<ArabicFriendsTowStudent><![CDATA[<p>Its focus is to help learners understand what they listen to, pronounce letters and words correctly, read texts fully supported with diacritics (Tashkeel), follow proper writing rules, and use linguistic structures in communication.</p><p>Each lesson in the book starts with a dialogue to improve learners’ reading, comprehensions and conversation skills with easy vocabulary coupled with impressive illustrations related to daily life, such as: Good morning, Adnan and the dentist, Allah the Provider, the elephant’s trunk, in the amusement park, etc.</p><p>The book aims to teach punctuation marks, interrogative and exclamatory methods, and the distinction between masculine and feminine, in addition to the use of the singular and plural, adverbs, relative nouns, pronouns, and others.</p><p>The book includes activities that cover the outcomes of the lessons, especially those that improve the skills of reading, observation, and making links and conclusions. They vary to include different methods of reading and writing, and learning of basic skills to enable learners to correctly read and spell the vocabulary presented by the lesson.</p>]]></ArabicFriendsTowStudent>
<ArabicFriendsTowactivity>It offers a variety of distinctive and interesting exercises designed to consolidate what the pupils have learnt in the Student’s Book.</ArabicFriendsTowactivity>
<ArabicFriendsTowTeacher>It offers information, instructions and ways of teaching the material. There are also step-by-step suggestions on how to do the exercises to achieve the outcomes of the lesson.</ArabicFriendsTowTeacher>

<!--a5-->
<ArabicFriendsThreeStudent><![CDATA[<p>Its focus is to help learners understand what they listen to, pronounce letters and words correctly, read texts fully supported with diacritics (Tashkeel), follow proper writing rules, and use linguistic structures in communication.</p><p>Each lesson in the book starts with a dialogue to improve learners’ reading, comprehensions and conversation skills with easy vocabulary coupled with impressive illustrations related to daily life, such as: the physical activity of walking, at library, I apologize, at the market, hospitality, the two friends, etc.</p><p>The book aims at teaching the punctuation marks, singular, dual and plural nouns, demonstrative pronouns, relative pronouns, forms of verbs, interrogative and exclamatory methods, number-gender agreement, etc.</p><p>The book includes activities that cover the outcomes of the lessons, especially those that improve the skills of reading, observation, and making links and conclusions. They vary to include different methods of reading and writing, and learning of basic skills to enable learners to correctly read and spell the vocabulary presented by the lesson.</p>]]></ArabicFriendsThreeStudent>
<ArabicFriendsThreeactivity>It offers a variety of distinctive and interesting exercises designed to consolidate what the pupils have learnt in the Student’s Book.</ArabicFriendsThreeactivity>
<ArabicFriendsThreeTeacher>It offers information, instructions and ways of teaching the material. There are also step-by-step suggestions on how to do the exercises to achieve the outcomes of the lesson.</ArabicFriendsThreeTeacher>

<!--a6-->
<ArabicFriendsFourStudent><![CDATA[<p>The book aims at helping learners identify main points of audio contents, produce language correctly and read short stories. It also improves learners’ ability to properly follow grammar rules and use language patterns.</p><p>It also aims at teaching verb tenses in Arabic (Past, Present and imperative), prepositions, nominal sentences, punctuation marks, singular, dual and plural nouns, different kinds of pronouns, interrogative and exclamatory methods, number-gender agreement, etc.    </p><p>Each lesson in the book starts with a dialogue to improve learners’ reading, comprehensions and conversation skills with easy vocabulary coupled with impressive illustrations related to daily life, such as: an enjoying trip, the Dead Sea, work is life, at the restaurant, the Eskimos, etc.</p><p>The book includes activities that cover the outcomes of the lessons, especially those that improve the skills of reading, observation, and making links and conclusions. They vary to include different methods of reading and writing, and learning of basic skills to enable learners to correctly read and spell the vocabulary presented by the lesson.</p>]]></ArabicFriendsFourStudent>
<ArabicFriendsFouractivity>It offers a variety of distinctive and interesting exercises designed to consolidate what the pupils have learnt in the Student’s Book.</ArabicFriendsFouractivity>
<ArabicFriendsFourTeacher>It offers information, instructions and ways of teaching the material. There are also step-by-step suggestions on how to do the exercises to achieve the outcomes of the lesson.</ArabicFriendsFourTeacher>

<!--b1-->
<braemOneStudent><![CDATA[<p>It primarily focuses on teaching reading, but is also concerned with the other skills of the language. It is considered the main book in Baraem Al Arabia series. </p><p>The material covered by the book comes in eight units including topics related to children’s life, and based on their surrounding environment. It presents the following titles: at the play park, on the farm, my computer, with the neighbors, Eid holiday, traffic lights, at sea, my favorite sport.</p><p>Each unit starts with a scene picture of a children story to elicit and teach vocabulary. The scene pictures cover all the vocabulary presented in the four lessons composing the unit.    </p><p>All of the eight units teach the Arabic letters and the vowels, in addition to the vowel marks (the fatha, the damma, the kasra, the sukoon, and the shadda). The three vowels were introduced first so that the child could join letters to form syllables and words through various gradual activities and exercises that suit the child's growth.</p>]]></braemOneStudent>
<braemOneTeacher>The Teacher's Book offers a detailed explanation of the material with how-to-teach instructions, as well as detailed methods for teaching reading for beginners. It includes the Alphabet stories charecterized by simple vocabulary and structures from the child's environment. It also includes educational games proposed to implement the activities of the book, which develop child’s observation, concentration, and composition skills. </braemOneTeacher>

<!--b2-->
<braemTowStudent><![CDATA[<p>It primarily focuses on teaching reading, but is also concerned with the other skills of the language. It is considered the main book in Baraem Al Arabia series. </p><p>The material covered by the book comes in seven units including topics related to children’s life, and based on their surrounding environment. It presents the following titles: My friends, on the field, with the T.V, at the marketplace, Let’s work, rain and swimming. </p><p>Each unit starts with a scene picture of a children story to elicit and teach vocabulary. The scene pictures cover all the vocabulary presented in the lessons composing the unit.  </p><p>All of the seven units teach the Arabic letters and the vowel marks (the fatha, the damma, the kasra, the sukoon, and the shadda) in an easy way that leads to mastering the skills of the language, especially the skills of joining and dividing syllables. </p>]]></braemTowStudent>
<braemTowactivity>It includes a variety of exercises and activities that take into account the level of the child, and reinforce what he has learned in the first level of different language skills.</braemTowactivity>
<braemTowTeacher>The Teacher's Book offers a detailed explanation of the material with how-to-teach instructions, as well as detailed methods for teaching reading for beginners. It includes the Alphabet stories charecterized by simple vocabulary and structures from the child's environment. It also includes educational games proposed to implement the activities of the book, which develop child’s observation, concentration, and composition skills.</braemTowTeacher>
<!--b2-->

<!---c1-->
<BookPlayAndLearnWithlettersparagraphEnglish><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify">An educational series designed to teach the alphabet through play and varying activities in a simple way to develop thinking and teach vowel marks and long syllables as an introduction to gradually improve reading and writing skills connecting previous experiences to new ones.</p>]]></BookPlayAndLearnWithlettersparagraphEnglish>
<BookPlayAndLearnWithlettersparagraphArabic><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify;direction:rtl;font-family:'Droid Arabic Kufi';font-size:13px">يعتمد منهاج العب وتعلم مع الحروف على تعليم الأطفال حروف اللغة العربية عن طريق الألعاب والأنشطة بأسلوب مبسط ينمي التفكير ويعلم الحروف والمقاطع والحركات والقراءة والكتابة بتدرج هرمي يربط الخبرات السابقة باللاحقة.</p>]]></BookPlayAndLearnWithlettersparagraphArabic>
<PlayAndLearnWithlettersOneStudent>It is based on the two basic skills of breaking up words into different syllables and joining different letters to form syllables. The book starts at the introduction of the three vowel sounds (aa, oo, ee) and aims at enabling children to recognize the phonetic sound an alphabetic letter makes through a picture scene to elicit language that include that letter covering its different shapes. </PlayAndLearnWithlettersOneStudent>

<!--c2-->
<PlayAndLearnWithlettersTowStudent>It presents the vowel marks (Fatha, Dhamma, Kasra and sukoun) focusing on their relationships with letters and syllables through reading and writing. </PlayAndLearnWithlettersTowStudent>

<!---d1-->
<BookHeiaElaEmanparagraphEnglish><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify">An Educational series designed to teach the principles and morals of Islam in English. It combines theory and practice to teach children good manners.</p><p style="text-align:justify">Each level of the series presents different topics, including the Holy Qur'an, the Prophet's Sunnah, the biography of Prophet Muhammad (PBUH), worship, and some jurisprudential topics in a progressive manner.</p>]]></BookHeiaElaEmanparagraphEnglish>
<BookHeiaElaEmanparagraphArabic><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify;direction:rtl;font-family:'Droid Arabic Kufi';font-size:13px">سلسلة لتعليم الأطفال مبادئ الدين الإسلامي وآدابه السامية مقدمة من دار المنهل، تجمع بين النظرية والتطبيق لتعليم وتنمية الخلق القويم عند الأطفال. تعالج السلسلة في كل مستوى موضوعات مختلفة تشمل القرآن الكريم والسنة النبوية وسيرة الرسول صلى الله عليه وسلم والعبادات وبعض المواضيع الفقهية بطريقة متدرجة. </p>]]></BookHeiaElaEmanparagraphArabic>
<HeiaElaEmanBustanStudent>The topics of Hayya Ela Al Eman KG1 varied to cover different topics such as: Surahs from the Holy Qur’an (Surat Al-Fatihah, Surat Al-Ikhlas, Surat Al-Nas, Surat Al-Nasr, Surat Al-Kawthar, Surat Al-Fil, Surat Quraish, Surat Al-Falaq, Surat Al-Qadr, Surat Al-Asr ), Prophet's Sunnah, Pillars of Islam and Eman, some daily supplications, in addition to positive attitudes through educational picture stories illustrating the overall meaning of the verses and hadiths. The book is also directed to children in Muslim communities. A CD for the songs is attached to the book</HeiaElaEmanBustanStudent>

<!---d2-->
<HeiaElaEmanOneStudent>The topics of the book varied to include thirty-one lessons focusing on various topics such as: Surahs from the Holy Qur’an (Surat Al-Kafirun, Surat Al-Masd, Surat Al-Tin, Surat Al-Sharh, Surat Al-Ma’un), the pillars of Islam, the two testimonies (Shahadah), the Tashahhud, the lineage of the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH), in addition to a number of prophetic hadiths, supplications, and others. The book also includes educational songs.</HeiaElaEmanOneStudent>
<HeiaElaEmanOneTeacher>The Teacher's Book presents a brief and specific definition of the concept of planning for teaching with its two types: the daily plan and the semester plan, with a model for an annual teaching plan, and another one for a daily teaching plan. It includes the general outcomes of level 1 and the fundimentals of teaching the course: function of knowledge, development of thinking, and individual differences) with some general directions that the teacher is advised to use or to be guided by in his teaching. It also includes an analysis for the content of one lesson from the book.</HeiaElaEmanOneTeacher>

<!---d3-->
<HeiaElaEmanTowStudent>The topics of the book diversified to include thirty-one lessons focusing on various topics such as: Surahs from the Holy Qur’an (Surat Al-Alaq, Surat Al-Hamza, Surat Al-Takathur, Surat Al-Qari’a, Surat Al-Dhuha, Surat Al-Zalzalah), Pillars of Iman (faith), revelation (Wahi), call to prayer (Athan), in addition to a number of Prophetic hadiths and supplications, etc. The book has a CD of educational songs.</HeiaElaEmanTowStudent>
<HeiaElaEmanTowTeacher>The Teacher's Book presents a brief and specific definition of the concept of planning for teaching with its two types: the daily plan and the semester plan, with a model for an annual teaching plan, and another one for a daily teaching plan. It includes the general outcomes of level 1 and the fundimentals of teaching the course: function of knowledge, development of thinking, and individual differences) with some general directions that the teacher is advised to use or to be guided by in his teaching. It also includes an analysis for the content of one lesson from the book.</HeiaElaEmanTowTeacher>

<!--d4-->
<HeiaElaEmanThreeStudent>The topics of the book varied to include thirty-one lessons focusing on various topics such as: Surahs from the Holy Qur’an (Surat Al-Muddathir, Surat Al-Shams, Surat Al-Tariq, Surat Al-Balad, Surat Al-Adiyat), miracles of the Messengers, miracles of Prophet Muhammad (PBUH), Khadijah bint Khuwaylid, fasting the holy month of Ramadan, in addition to a number of Prophetic hadiths, supplications, etc. The book also includes educational songs.</HeiaElaEmanThreeStudent>

<!---e1-->
<BookBraamElaEmanparagraphEnglish><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify">A series directed to kindergarten children at two levels. It introduces age-appropriate principles of Islam and instills Islamic values in children where they are urged to notice Allah’s ability in His creatures, learn some verses from the holy Quran, hadeeths of Prophet Muhammad (PBUH), as well as athkars. It also presents information about Prophet Muhammad’s (PBUH) life including his birth, his lineage, and his manners as a role model who should be followed when dealing with the family and the surrounding environment.</p>]]></BookBraamElaEmanparagraphEnglish>
<BookBraamElaEmanparagraphArabic><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify;direction:rtl;font-family:'Droid Arabic Kufi';font-size:13px">سلسلة موجهة لرياض الأطفال في مستويين تعرف الطفل بمبادئ التربية الإسلامية التي تناسب المرحلة وتغرس المعاني الإيمانية والأخلاق السامية فيتعرف  بعض آثار قدرة الله تعالى في الخلق ويحفظ بعض السور الكريمة والأحاديث الشريفة والأدعية والأذكار، ويتعرف مولد (الرسول صلى الله عليه وسلم) ونسبه وطفولته وبعض آداب الإسلام في الحياة اليومية والتعامل مع الأسرة والبيئة المحيطة.</p>]]></BookBraamElaEmanparagraphArabic>
<BraamElaEmanOneStudent>It teaches the principles of Islam and its etiquette through sixteen lessons focusing on various age-appropriate topics (4-5 years). It presents some Suras from the Holy Qur’an: (Surat Al-Fatihah, Surat Al-Kawthar, Surat Al-Falaq, Surat Al-Nas, Surat Al-Nasr), some supplications, athkar, and manners. It also presents information about Prophet Muhammad (PBUH): his lineage, his childhood, etc.</BraamElaEmanOneStudent>

<!--e2-->
<BraamElaEmanTowStudent>It teaches the principles of Islam and its etiquette through sixteen lessons focusing on various age-appropriate topics (5-6 years). It presents some Suras from the Holy Qur’an: (Surat Al-Asr, Surat Al-Masad, Surat Al-Maoon), the pillars of Islam, fasting the holy month of Ramadan, the two Shahadas, call to prayer, prayer times. It also covers some information about prophet Muhammad’s life: his birth, his life, etc.</BraamElaEmanTowStudent>
<Pupil_EBook>Pupil's Book</Pupil_EBook>


<!---f1-->
<BookCallToFaithparagraphEnglish><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify">An Educational series designed to teach the principles and morals of Islam in English. Its topics varied to include the Noble Qur’an, the Sunnah, the Islamic Creed, the life of Prophet Muhammad PBUH and acts of worship. It features the practical meaning of worship and moral aspects through activities, stories and drawings that clarify the meaning making education more fun and exciting. This series fulfills the needs of the Islamic community schools in foreign countries.</p>]]></BookCallToFaithparagraphEnglish>
<BookCallToFaithparagraphArabic><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify;direction:rtl;font-family:'Droid Arabic Kufi';font-size:13px">سلسلة لتعليم مبادئ الدين الإسلامي وآدابه باللغة الإنجليزية، تنوعت موضوعاتها لتشمل القرآن الكريم والسنة النبوية والعقيدة والسيرة والعبادات وتؤكد على المعنى التطبيقي العملي فيما يتعلق بالجانبين العبادي والأخلاقي من خلال أنشطة وحكايات ورسومات توضح المعنى وتجعل التعليم أكثر متعة وتشويقاً، وهذه السلسلة تلبي حاجة مدارس الجاليات الإسلامية في البلاد الأجنبية.</p>]]></BookCallToFaithparagraphArabic>
<CallToFaithOneStudent>The topics of Call to Faith 1 / Pupil’s Book varied in thirty lessons to cover different topics such as: Surahs from the Holy Qur’an (Surat Al-Fatihah, Surat Al-Ikhlas, Surat Al-Nas, Surat Al-Nasr, Surat Al-Kawthar, Surat Al-Fil, Surat Quraish, Surat Al-Falaq, Surat Al-Qadr, Surat Al-Asr ), the etiquette of reciting the Holly Qur’an, the greeting of Islam, the etiquette of sleeping, cleanliness, Prophet Muhammad PBUH, etc.</CallToFaithOneStudent>
<CallToFaithOneTeacher>It includes exercises covering the lessons in the Student's Book. It aims to consolidate children’s knowledge. </CallToFaithOneTeacher>

<!--f2-->
<CallToFaithTowStudent>The topics of Call to Faith 2 / Pupil's Book varied to include thirty lessons covering different topics such as: Surahs from the Holy Qur’an (Surat Al-Kafirun, Surat Al-Masd, Surat Al-Tin, Surat Al-Sharh, Surat Al-Ma’un), the two testimonies, the pillars of Islam, Allah the One, Well of Zamzam, etc.</CallToFaithTowStudent>
<CallToFaithTowTeacher>It includes exercises covering the lessons in the Student's Book. It aims to consolidate children’s knowledge.</CallToFaithTowTeacher>

<!--f2-->
<CallToFaithThreeStudent>The topics of Call to Faith 3 / Pupil’s Book 3 varied to include thirty lessons covering different topics such as: Surahs from the Holy Qur’an (Surat Al-Alaq, Surat Al-Humazah, Surat Al-Takathur, Surat Al-Qariah, Surat Al-Dhuha, Surat Al-Zalzalah), the pillars of Eman, Allah the Able, Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) Meets Buhairah, Secret Invitation to Islam, etc.</CallToFaithThreeStudent>
<CallToFaithThreeTeacher>It includes exercises covering the lessons in the Student's Book. It aims to consolidate children’s knowledge.</CallToFaithThreeTeacher>

<!--f2-->
<CallToFaithFourStudent>The topics of Call to Faith 4 / Pupil’s Book 3 varied to include thirty lessons covering different topics such as: Surahs from the Holy Qur’an (Surat Al-Mudather, Surat Al-Shams, Surat Al-Tareq, Surat Al-Balad, Surat Al-Adiyat), good manners, Allah, the Merciful, Belief in the Prophets and their holy Books, Al Taraweeh, Honesty, Fasting the holy month of Ramadan, etc.</CallToFaithFourStudent>
<CallToFaithFourTeacher>It includes exercises covering the lessons in the Student's Book. It aims to consolidate children’s knowledge.</CallToFaithFourTeacher>



<EducationalCards>Educational Cards</EducationalCards>
    <Posters>Posters</Posters>
    <AboutEducationalCards>About Educational Cards</AboutEducationalCards>
    <cardEnParagraph>Educational cards by Dar Al Manhal Publishers especially designed to supplement the series ‘Friends of Arabic’. They are divided into groups to teach letters, diacritics, syllables and words. They enable the teacher to implement purposeful entertainment games such as pattern and matching games which develop sensorimotor skills and concentration and focus skills and help improving small and big muscles along with vocabulary development.</cardEnParagraph>
    <cardArParagraph><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify;direction:rtl;font-family:'Droid Arabic Kufi';font-size:13px">بطاقات تعليمية أعدت لتناسب سلسلة أصدقاء العربية الصادرة عن دار المنهل، تضم مجموعات لتعليم الحروف والحركات والمقاطع والكلمات. وتمكن المعلم من تنفيذ العديد من الألعاب التعليمية الهادفة كألعاب الأنماط والمطابقة والتي تنمي التآزر الحسي الحركي ودقة الملاحظة والتركيز، العضلات الكبيرة والصغيرة، والثروة اللغوية للطفل.</p>]]></cardArParagraph>
    <GardenParagraph>GardenParagraph</GardenParagraph>


    <AboutEducationalposterOne>About Educational Poster</AboutEducationalposterOne>
    <posterOneEnParagraph>Educational picture scenes by Dar Al Manhal Publishers especially designed to supplement the series ‘Friends of Arabic’ and engage children’s learning. </posterOneEnParagraph>
    <posterOneArParagraph><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify;direction:rtl;font-family:'Droid Arabic Kufi';font-size:13px">لوحات تعليمية مميزة من حيث الرسوم والمحتوى، تناسب سلسلة أصدقاء العربية الصادرة عن دار المنهل.</p>]]></posterOneArParagraph>



    <posterTowEnParagraph>Educational picture scenes by Dar Al Manhal Publishers especially designed to supplement the series ‘Bara’em of Arabic’ and engage children’s learning.</posterTowEnParagraph>
    <posterTowArParagraph><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify;direction:rtl;font-family:'Droid Arabic Kufi';font-size:13px">لوحات تعليمية مميزة من حيث الرسوم والمحتوى، تناسب سلسلة براعم العربية الصادرة عن دار المنهل.</p>]]></posterTowArParagraph>
    <levelOneposterTowParagraph>levelOneposterTowParagraph</levelOneposterTowParagraph>


    <Return_Policy>Shipping And Return</Return_Policy>
    <ShippinginfoParag>International orders are dealt with individually, but we aim to use the quickest means possible.</ShippinginfoParag>
    <Shippinginfopoint1>- Domestic Shipping (In Jordan): your order will be delivered within 3 - 6 working days from order placement date.</Shippinginfopoint1>
    <Shippinginfopoint2>- Cargo Shipping (Outside Jordan): your order will be delivered within 4 - 9 working days from order placement date.</Shippinginfopoint2>
    <ShippinginfoParag1>You can inquire into the status of your order by e-mail to:</ShippinginfoParag1>
    <ShippinginfoParag2>or via WhatsApp:</ShippinginfoParag2>


    <OrderCancellation>Order Cancellation</OrderCancellation>
    <OrderCancellationParag1>A customer may cancel an order between placing the order and it is shipped. If the cancellation happens after the goods have been processed and dispatched then a refund will not be offered until the goods have been returned. Original delivery costs in this case are non-refundable, as is the shipping cost. </OrderCancellationParag1>
    <OrderCancellationParag2>This does not apply to eBooks, as the cancellation is within one day only and the amount is refunded without the PayPal commission of 3%.</OrderCancellationParag2>

    <ImportDuties>Import Duties</ImportDuties>
    <ImportDutiesParag>When we ship books outside Jordan, the recipient is liable for any local taxes or import duties that may be payable. Dar Al Manhal can take no responsibility for this. If the goods are returned due to unpaid tax, the costs will not be refunded.</ImportDutiesParag>

    <DamagedBooks>Damaged Books</DamagedBooks>
    <DamagedBooksParag1>If you have purchased an item from Dar Al Manhal and it is damaged upon receipt, please advise us within 3 days. The time limit for return is 7 days for your convenience. The cost of the item will be refunded along with the cost of shipping to you.</DamagedBooksParag1>
    <DamagedBooksParag2>If the return is due to an error that we or our delivery company have made, we will gladly refund both the original delivery charge and the cost of return shipping.</DamagedBooksParag2>
    <DamagedBooksParag3>If you are not completely satisfied with your purchase, you may return it to us in its original condition. To qualify for a refund, you must first contact us via email or WhatsApp within 3 working days and then send the unwanted items back to us within 7 days. Upon receipt of the items in their original condition we will refund you. This will not include the cost of shipping to you or the reshipping cost.</DamagedBooksParag3>
    <DamagedBooksParag4>Please email us for further support:</DamagedBooksParag4>


    <ReturnProcedure>Return Procedure</ReturnProcedure>
    <ReturnProcedureParag1>All returns should be securely wrapped and sent, with the original packing slip and reason for the return, to the following address: Dar Al Manhal Publishers</ReturnProcedureParag1>
    <ReturnProcedureParag2>Areej Commercial Complex, near Al-Assaf traffic lights, Wasfi al-tal Str. Amman - Jordan</ReturnProcedureParag2>




<!--ads stories-->

    <addsstoriesOne1>One of the bestsellers</addsstoriesOne1>
    <addsstoriesOne2>Special discount for a limited time</addsstoriesOne2>
    <addsstoriesOne3>Suitable for 10-14 year olds </addsstoriesOne3>
    <addsstoriesOne4>Comes in 5 Titles</addsstoriesOne4>
    <addsstoriesOne5>Age-appropriate language and illustrations</addsstoriesOne5>

    <addsstoriesTow1>One of the bestsellers</addsstoriesTow1>
    <addsstoriesTow2>Special discount for a limited time</addsstoriesTow2>
    <addsstoriesTow3>Suitable for 4-6 year olds </addsstoriesTow3>
    <addsstoriesTow4>Comes in 30 titles</addsstoriesTow4>
    <addsstoriesTow5>Each title corresponds to one of the 30 letters </addsstoriesTow5>

    <addsstoriesThree1>One of the bestsellers</addsstoriesThree1>
    <addsstoriesThree2>Special discount for a limited time</addsstoriesThree2>
    <addsstoriesThree3>Suitable for 5-10 year olds </addsstoriesThree3>
    <addsstoriesThree4>Comes in 3 levels, 10 titles each</addsstoriesThree4>
    <addsstoriesThree5>Age-appropriate language and illustrations</addsstoriesThree5>

    <addsstoriesFour1>One of the bestsellers</addsstoriesFour1>
    <addsstoriesFour2>Special discount for a limited time</addsstoriesFour2>
    <addsstoriesFour3>Suitable for 4-12 year olds </addsstoriesFour3>
    <addsstoriesFour4>Comes in 5 titles</addsstoriesFour4>
    <addsstoriesFour5>Age-appropriate language and illustrations</addsstoriesFour5>

    <addsstoriesFive1>One of the bestsellers</addsstoriesFive1>
    <addsstoriesFive2>Special discount for a limited time</addsstoriesFive2>
    <addsstoriesFive3>Suitable for 4-10 year olds </addsstoriesFive3>
    <addsstoriesFive4>Comes in 5 levels</addsstoriesFive4>
    <addsstoriesFive5>Age-appropriate language and illustrations</addsstoriesFive5>
    <!--ads stories-->

    <!--   ads books-->
    <addsBooksA1>One of the bestsellers</addsBooksA1>
    <addsBooksA2>Special discount for a limited time</addsBooksA2>
    <addsBooksA3>Suitable for non-Arabic speakers</addsBooksA3>
    <addsBooksA4>Suitable for 4-14 year olds </addsBooksA4>
    <addsBooksA5>Comes in 6 levels</addsBooksA5>

    <addsBooksB1>One of the bestsellers</addsBooksB1>
    <addsBooksB2>Special discount for a limited time</addsBooksB2>
    <addsBooksB3>Suitable for 4-6 year olds </addsBooksB3>
    <addsBooksB4>Comes in 2 levels</addsBooksB4>
    <addsBooksB5>Teaches the basic skills of Arabic language</addsBooksB5>

    <addsBooksC1>One of the bestsellers</addsBooksC1>
    <addsBooksC2>Special discount for a limited time</addsBooksC2>
    <addsBooksC3>Suitable for 4-6 year olds </addsBooksC3>
    <addsBooksC4>Comes in 2 levels</addsBooksC4>
    <addsBooksC5>Teaches the Arabic alphabet </addsBooksC5>

    <addsBooksD1>One of the bestsellers</addsBooksD1>
    <addsBooksD2>Special discount for a limited time </addsBooksD2>
    <addsBooksD3>Suitable for 5-8 year olds </addsBooksD3>
    <addsBooksD4>Comes in 4 levels</addsBooksD4>
    <addsBooksD5>Directed to children in the Arab and Islamic worlds and Islamic communities in foreign countries </addsBooksD5>

    <addsBooksE1>One of the bestsellers</addsBooksE1>
    <addsBooksE2>Special discount for a limited time</addsBooksE2>
    <addsBooksE3>Suitable for 4-6 year olds </addsBooksE3>
    <addsBooksE4>Comes in 2 levels</addsBooksE4>
    <addsBooksE5>Teaches the basics and the manners of Islam</addsBooksE5>

    <addsBooksF1>One of the bestsellers</addsBooksF1>
    <addsBooksF2>Special discount for a limited time</addsBooksF2>
    <addsBooksF3>Suitable for 6-9 year olds </addsBooksF3>
    <addsBooksF4>Comes in 4 levels</addsBooksF4>
    <addsBooksF5>Directed to Islamic community children in foreign countries</addsBooksF5>

    <!--   ads books-->
    <!--   ads cards-->
    <addscards1>One of the bestsellers</addscards1>
    <addscards2>Special discount for a limited time</addscards2>
    <addscards3>Suitable for 4-6 year olds </addscards3>
    <addscards4>Age-appropriate language and illustrations</addscards4>
    <!-- ads cards-->

    <!-- ads posters-->
    <addspostersA1>One of the bestsellers</addspostersA1>
    <addspostersA2>Special discount for a limited time</addspostersA2>
    <addspostersA3>Suitable for 4-8 year olds </addspostersA3>
    <addspostersA4>Age-appropriate language and illustrations</addspostersA4>

    <addspostersB1>One of the bestsellers</addspostersB1>
    <addspostersB2>Special discount for a limited time</addspostersB2>
    <addspostersB3>Suitable for 4-6 year olds </addspostersB3>
    <addspostersB4>Age-appropriate language and illustrations</addspostersB4>
    <Itcontains6stories>It contains 6 stories</Itcontains6stories>
    <Itcontains30stories>It contains 30 stories</Itcontains30stories>

    <!--   ads posters-->

</Language>
